<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<!DOCTYPE corpus SYSTEM
  "lexical-sample.dtd">
  <corpus lang='english'>

    <lexelt item="bar.n">

<instance id="bar.40001" docsrc="bnc_CGC_62">
<answer instance="bar.40001" senseid="U"/>
<context>
I have been to both places and can assure you, there is a great difference. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Mock manifesto [/head] [p]
What we would demand given half a chance: Electro-shock treatment for anyone with home-made tattoos.
The electric chair for those with spelling mistakes.
The designer sunglasses of your choice available free on the NHS.
National Rodney King Day, when the victims of police injustice can stop, search and use &bquo;reasonable force&equo; on officers of their choice.
A 7pm curfew on all tourists in London during the summer.
That London Underground bring back their chocolate vending machines.
A night out was not complete without a gamble on the station machine, when the agony of nine successive defeats would be replaced by euphoria when you actually got your <head>bar</head> . [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
</context>
</instance>
    </lexelt>

<lexelt item="chair.n">

<instance id="chair.40002" docsrc="bnc_CJK_548">
<answer instance="chair.40002" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The spacious lounge with its well-stocked bar is furnished in soft peachy colours and attractive cane-backed chairs. [/p] [p]
Colin and Sue Humber took over Claremont House in early 1989, from myself and my partner Mary Behar.
It had been my first venture into the hotel business and probably my last &mdash; I take my hat off to anyone who makes it work.
It is hard work.
Mary and I upgraded the hotel considerably, but the strain of running two businesses at once proved too much.
Colin and Sue took it off our hands and have made further excellent improvements.
I may be a little biased about this one, but I now consider it to be of a very high standard.
Amongst the many things Sue and Colin have worked on, the walled garden is much improved with very pretty herbaceous borders and a lawn laid out with parasoled tables and <head>chairs</head> , where guests can relax with a drink on a warm summer's evening. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40003" docsrc="bnc_ANU_604">
<answer instance="chair.40003" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The war had left its mark, too, on the home of the two uncles whom Abu Khadra so often recalled visiting.
Abu Khadra Street had now become Gerulot Street, but the white-stone house was still there, with its three fine, tall windows of delicate iron tracery.
The embossed iron doors were rusting and one of them had fallen off its hinges.
On the south wall, there were some faint shrapnel marks; several deep bullet holes could be seen beside a window.
The ground floor consisted of a key-cutter's stall and some small shops, just as it did when Abu Khadra knew it.
Up the flight of steps was a very old door, covered in flaking green paint. [/p] [p]
I knocked on it but it was so dilapidated that I could see right through the door frame and into a large room where a man was sitting in a kitchen <head>chair</head> , dressed in trousers and vest.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40005" docsrc="bnc_A73_2050">
<answer instance="chair.40005" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The curtains were of dark chintz patterned with medallions.
A small chandelier caught the sun and made rainbow spot patterns on the ceiling.
Wexford thought the place was just like the sitting room of a person of taste.
There were dozens like it in Kingsmarkham.
But this was just a dentist's waiting room and it made him wonder what the rest of the house would be like.
He was in for a surprise.
He was admiring a stylish flower arrangement, observing how cunningly a spray of jasmine had been made to tremble half in, half out of the vase and trail against the console table, when the girl came back and told him Mr Vigo would see him now. [/p] [p]
Wexford followed her into the surgery. [/p] [p]
There was nothing out of the ordinary here, just the usual <head>chairs</head> and trays of instruments and contraptions of tubes and clamps and wires.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40006" docsrc="bnc_CFR_1149">
<answer instance="chair.40006" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The new Kappa-float glazing on all the windows, and the exceptionally high quality of insulation, earned the lodges the coveted MEDALLION AWARD for energy saving efficiency.
Our homes are warm and cosy on even the coldest day, and well ventilated during the summer months. [/p] [p]
[hi]No expense has been spared [/hi] to make each home the ultimate in luxury.
From the plush Connolly hide leather sofa and chairs in the living room to the Bang and Olufsen stereo, and remote control television complete with video, you're surrounded by the HIGHEST QUALITY. [/p] [p]
The inlaid chequerboard top of the coffee table houses all kind of games, including backgammon, chess and Scrabble.
You'll also find a selection of books, from Queen Victoria's Highland journals, to the very latest bestselling thriller. [/p] [p]
The dinner table and <head>chairs</head> are elegant yet comfortable, and you can be assured of the finest tableware and crystal for meals at home. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40008" docsrc="bnc_CCY_410">
<answer instance="chair.40008" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Coat one end of the dowel with a pva woodworking adhesive and tap firmly into the arm.
Clean off surplus adhesive [/item] [label]
6 [/label] [item]
Now coat the other end of the dowel with glue&hellip; [/item] [label]
7 [/label] [item]
&hellip; and the rim of the hole into which it will fit.
This ensures that adhesive is carried down into the hole [/item] [label]
8 [/label] [item]
Glue was also needed where the arm fitted into the chair back [/item] [label]
9 [/label] [item]
The arm was then pushed into the <head>chair</head> back&hellip; [/item] [label]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40010" docsrc="bnc_A5M_358">
<answer instance="chair.40010" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
More than 820 people have died in and around Beirut in battles between General Aoun's forces and Syrian and Syrian-backed Muslim militias since mid-March, after the general's declaration of a &bquo;war of liberation&equo; against the occupying Syrians.
An Arab League-sponsored ceasefire has been in force since 23 September. [/p] [p]
Muslim deputies here said they were optimistic that a working group of senior deputies could agree on the reforms, which give the Muslims equal representation in parliament and transfer executive powers from the Christian president to a cabinet led by a Sunni Muslim prime minister. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Britain will seek something new at Commonwealth summit [/head] [head]
By JOHN BULLOCH, Diplomatic Editor [/head] [p]
THE HEADING is innocuous enough: Executive Session 3, Reports of Special Committees, presented by Joe Clarke, the Foreign Minister of Canada, with Kenneth Kaunda, President of Zambia in the <head>chair</head> and Bob Hawke, Prime Minister of Australia, to speak.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40012" docsrc="bnc_CFC_1902">
<answer instance="chair.40012" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Chelmsford's Tory MP Simon Burns is the chairman of the appeal fund. [/p] [p]
He is delighted and yesterday said: &bquo;This is extremely good news because it is imperative that the cathedral has the ability to maintain its justifiably high standard of music, and a new organ is badly needed as the existing one is now beyond repair.&equo; [ptr][/p] [caption]
Benefit [/caption] [p]
Other Essex groups to benefit from the Foundation for Sports and Arts grants are: [list] [item]
University of Essex Sports Centre, &pound;5,554, towards fitness assessment equipment. [/item] [item]
High Roding Cricket Club, &pound;7,500, to extend the club premises and provide wheelchair access. [/item] [item]
Thaxted Festival Foundation, &pound;32,000, for stage and <head>chairs</head> for the annual classical musical and arts celebration. [/item] [item]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40013" docsrc="bnc_CJF_2173">
<answer instance="chair.40013" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
He wanted to ask &bquo;Is she often like this?&equo;, but instead, he drew the boy out and closed the door.
He had never liked questioning a child about its parents and he didn't propose to do it now.
It was a common enough tragedy, but it was a job for the Juvenile Bureau not for him and the sooner one of their officers arrived the better.
He was fretted by the thought of Kate, back at the scene of crime by now, and he felt a spurt of resentment against Dalgliesh who had involved him in this irrelevant mess.
He asked: [/p] [p]
&bquo;Where do you sleep, Darren?&equo; [/p] [p]
The boy pointed to a back bedroom and Massingham pushed him gently before him. [/p] [p]
It was very small, hardly more than a box room, with a single high window.
Under it was a narrow bed covered with a brown army blanket and beside it a <head>chair</head> with a collection of objects neatly arranged.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40015" docsrc="bnc_CK0_1064">
<answer instance="chair.40015" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;Take it easy, son,&equo; said Dr Curtis.
&bquo;I'm a doctor.
I only want to help you.&equo;
He waited while I soothed Bill.
&bquo;All right, son?
Do you understand now your nurse has explained?
Good.
Good.&equo; [/p] [p]
When I went off that morning Bill did not recognize me.
He did not even know his father.
I left the General sitting stiffly in his hard <head>chair</head> , one hand on one stick handle, the other resting on his son's bed.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40016" docsrc="bnc_CFH_845">
<answer instance="chair.40016" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
The mere fact of being on the streets, ill-clothed and ill&rehy;fed makes such children criminals in the eyes of the police, and easy targets for death squads. [/p] [p]
The corpse of Patricio Hilario da Silva, aged 9, was dumped in the fashionable Rio de Janeiro suburb of Ipanema on 22 May, 1989.
A note tied around his neck read: &bquo;I killed you because you didn't study and had no future&hellip;
The government must not allow the streets of the city to be invaded by kids.&equo; [/p] [p]
While Brazil prepares to greet the world's leaders, one child per day is being murdered by its death squads. [pb] [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
MEMBERS [/head] [caption]
DOING MORE&hellip;
FINDING NEW WAYS TO CAMPAIGN: HUMPHREY SOUTHALL AND HEDLEY SUTTON, RESPECTIVELY THE <head>CHAIR</head> AND SECRETARY OF THE ACTIVE MEMBERSHIP WORKING GROUP, INTRODUCE THE QUESTIONNAIRE ON PAGE 21 WHICH AIMS TO FIND OUT MORE ABOUT AMNESTY'S MEMBERS. [/caption] [caption]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40019" docsrc="bnc_AM6_805">
<answer instance="chair.40019" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Another member of the group will be sitting on the chair with eyes closed and will point in the direction of the slightest sound.
The attempt fails if the volunteer is caught in the process of removing the stick. [/p] [p]
The teacher adapts a fairly well-known game to serve his purposes here, generally known as &bquo;Keeper of the [pb] Keys&equo;.
(In its traditional form, a bunch of keys is placed under the chair in the centre of a large circle.
The &bquo;keeper&equo; sits on the chair and is blindfolded.
A volunteer tries to retrieve the keys without being caught out and, if successful, becomes the new &bquo;keeper&equo;).
Since the teacher has already used a stick as a sign of Beowulf's authority he decides to give this additional prominence by making it the object to be retrieved from under the <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40020" docsrc="bnc_C8A_1645">
<answer instance="chair.40020" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Using a self-adhesive laminate in a smart new woodgrain finish, we resurfaced these doors and drawers in a day.
The vinyl is cut to size the a craft knife, the backing peeled off and the laminate simply stuck in place.
New chrome stirrup handles add the finishing touch. [/p] [p]
[hi]&bquo;Zelda&equo; Fablon Laminate for Kitchen Doors [/hi] by Forbo-CP, &pound;9.99 a roll &mdash; sufficient for approximately four 500mm kitchen base units. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
Budget tip [/head] [p]
Keep paint oddments for quick jobs like these.
Invert tin so skin forms under, not over, the paint. [ptr][/p] [caption]
The fabric that you choose will set the theme [/caption] [/div3] [div3] [head]
Floral transformation [/head] [p]
Four ordinary <head>chairs</head> have been transformed into inviting seats with simple loose covers.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40023" docsrc="bnc_BNN_398">
<answer instance="chair.40023" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The Liverpool Street dungeon was known, incongruously, as the gymnasium, presumably in memory of its intended purpose, though it had long been used for general storage.
In preparation for the [hi]Kindertransporte [/hi], the room was cleared of boxes and other flotsam.
Close to the door, rows of slatted chairs were set out behind a rope barrier.
At the far end was hung a large tarpaulin.
[pb] A large handwritten notice was propped up by the door &mdash; [hi]B&uuml;rge bleibt hier [/hi] (guarantors' seats here) &mdash; with an arrow pointing that way.
Behind the tarpaulin there were tables and <head>chairs</head> for the RCM workers, mostly, as an American journalist noticed, elegantly turned-out young ladies who looked &bquo;a good deal more like a junior league committee getting together to discuss a costume ball than officials waiting to sort out a trainload of Jewish refugee children&equo;. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40025" docsrc="bnc_CN3_2476">
<answer instance="chair.40025" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
He was surprised at the hard muscle he felt under his strong grip.
&bquo;Before we go I'd better check this guy for a piece &mdash; or a tape recorder. &bquo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;The uniformed guard in the hall did just that.&equo;
Newman looked up at Galvone.
&bquo;Frank, kindly remove your hand or I may remove it myself.
Painfully.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Try it, smart ass&hellip;&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Your impetuosity is showing again,&equo; Hauser remarked.
&bquo;Do I have to remind you Mr Newman is a guest?
An honoured guest?&equo; [/p] [p]
As he spoke he pressed a concealed button in the arm of his <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40027" docsrc="bnc_APM_2238">
<answer instance="chair.40027" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;He decided not to.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;How do you know?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;You should change your style.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I know, I'm trying to, I can't, the power has been withdrawn.
I can't [hi]learn [/hi] again now.
It's all to do with bloody Marcus.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Why blame him?&equo; [/p] [p]
The sun was casting a pleasant subdued clear radiance through the brown blinds which had been drawn over the south-facing skylight.
Jack kept his studio as empty as possible.
His finished paintings were stored at the gallery, or in a room downstairs.
The studio contained two easels, <head>chairs</head> , stools, a desk, a bronze dancing Shiva about three feet high over which, today, one of Jack's overalls had been thrown. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40028" docsrc="bnc_CHU_818">
<answer instance="chair.40028" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
And she was worried about his health.
Horsley was being slowly crippled by a rare type of paralysis spreading from his ankle, which meant that he now had to walk with a stick, and which it was feared would eventually put him in a wheelchair.
Frequent travel made his leg swell up, and caused him a considerable amount of discomfort.
Olwen didn't know at that time that the commitment was soon to become twenty-four hours a day, seven days a week.
At one point she told Nick that if Hayling &mdash; whom she referred to as &bquo;that nice-looking young man with the curly hair&equo; &mdash; came round again she would refuse to let him in.
But she did, and was another won over by the famous charm. [/p] [p]
Horsley cheerfully admitted when he took up the post of <head>Chair</head> that he knew nothing about newspapers.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40030" docsrc="bnc_A1V_69">
<answer instance="chair.40030" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Also, because as served in 99 out of 100 Chinese restaurants, they would arrive sticky with grease and boiled to a hue of nauseously vivid waxy-yellow.
Nor could you just shut your eyes and throw them down the hatch; because the whole pleasure of a chicken's foot would come from sucking and nibbling it slowly, seeking out the tasty skin and the fragments of flesh like the last moments of a particularly luscious spare rib.
You have to like them as feet. [/p] [p]
Zen, a newly-opened offshoot of the British restaurant group, is in the basement of a just-finished office and shop development called Pacific Place.
Its translucent glass, bare concrete ceilings, exposed pipework and Rennie Mackintosh-ish <head>chairs</head> are miles away from the gilt-and-gingerbread kitsch of the Hong Kong restaurant mainstream. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40031" docsrc="bnc_A0X_98">
<answer instance="chair.40031" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
However, the [hi]TTJ [/hi] also report that if you want the real cause of bird's eye features, don't ask a scientist.
When they put it to an expert they received the bewildering reply: &bquo;Bird's eye figure is formed as a result of local suppressions in divisions of cambial tissue that cause indentation to develop.
This retardation effect continues for several growing seasons and produces an indented conical depression.&equo; [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Toying with the BTG [/head] [p]
A major restructuring of the British Toymakers Guild has been recommended at their Annual General Meeting.
Unfortunately insufficient members turned up to achieve a quorum, but ex-chairman, Robin Brookes, took the opportunity to state that the guild could not continue to be run on a rotation of volunteers.
Clive Green has now taken Robin's place in the <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40033" docsrc="bnc_BPA_1103">
<answer instance="chair.40033" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Although Grant was the expert of the group, they both knew enough to realise that the equipment stacked around was sophisticated, and far too much for Titron if she had been but an ordinary container ship. [pb] [/p] [p]
And by now they knew she was not. [/p] [p]
A red light above the panel showed the equipment was on, supplied by automatic power, probably from batteries. [/p] [p]
Forster moved further into the room. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Looks more like the communications centre of a nuclear sub.&equo; [/p] [p]
They searched carefully until they were satisfied that the sensitive area was not armed for self-destruction, as many were. [/p] [p]
Delaney finally thumbed the button on the speaker set. [/p] [p]
The static roared out from the earphones, stronger than ever.
He held the headset away from him, using only one ear as they tried several wavelengths.
It was hopeless. [/p] [p]
Delaney gave up, shutting it off and swivelling out of the <head>chair</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40034" docsrc="bnc_BMW_847">
<answer instance="chair.40034" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
It clicked irritatingly and Hugo pushed it aside, swivelling his chair around to face the window and the panoramic view of Manhattan. [/p] [p]
Hugo Varna's showrooms occupied an entire floor of the 550 building and from the moment a potential client stepped out of the brass elevator she was treated to an ambience of unashamed luxury.
The vast foyer was carpeted in the softest green imaginable, the walls were even paler, so that at first glance they might have been taken for white, and the venetian blinds were a perfectly blended shade of moss.
The minimum of furniture emphasised the impressive size of the foyer &mdash; only small modern tables bearing huge smoked glass ash trays, two or three low <head>chairs</head> and a huge arrangement of dried ferns and foliage in shades of brown and gold graced the enormous expanse.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40036" docsrc="bnc_CA9_2241">
<answer instance="chair.40036" senseid="easy_chair-0"/>
<context>
It's out of the question. [/p] [p]
A shadow fell across my sunny table and I looked up to find Kenneth who'd been on a recce of the hospital, so after a lunch of ribs, skins, wings and blueberry pie, he was able to lead me through the appropriate doors of the vast, multi-entranced building. [/p] [p]
Stanford University Hospital is the Hippocratic show-piece of America, whose government-sponsored research surges forward free of the confines of budget.
A Champs Elys&eacute;e corridor led us to an escalator and the plush basement waiting room of the cancer clinic.
An apricot cave of pastel carpet and toning walls, soft lights, Mozart and easy <head>chairs</head> gave it a &bquo;late evening lounge&equo; feel, at odds with a white-capped staff bristling with efficiency behind the computerised reception. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40037" docsrc="bnc_CH8_267">
<answer instance="chair.40037" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The last thing you want is to start an involved conversation because when you come to do it for real, it can all seem a bit stale.
Also, it could give my guests time to go off the whole idea. [/p] [p]
About ten minutes before the show begins, the audience is seated &mdash; not too comfortably, we like them to stay awake.
On the set itself we've had, more or less, a different arrangement for every series.
First we had the idea of a desk, but I'm not supposed to be a bank manager.
On the other hand, I could put all my notes on it, and it would be somewhere to rest the elbows.
Johnny Carson in America always looks comfortable and authoritative behind a desk, and in a way I was sorry we abandoned that idea. [/p] [p]
For the first series, we had little sit-up <head>chairs</head> on which we perched and swivelled, but then we were still experimenting.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40039" docsrc="bnc_CA9_1273">
<answer instance="chair.40039" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Sound engineers, lighting technicians, set designers, carpenters and electricians have been working night and day, high on the adrenalin that 90 minutes of live T.V. induces.
There's a stretch-steel tension in the normally soothing make-up room, where nine intently concentrating make-up girls are tending the terrified contestants &mdash; and this is only a dress-run.
Admittedly there's an audience.
We have to try out the master scoreboard, a slick computerised monster and a change from the usual &bquo;Spaghetti Junction&equo;, so need the audience to check the theatre's voting system. [/p] [p]
The contestants are always attended to first.
I slip into make-up whenever and wherever there's a spare <head>chair</head> , and today Lynette Braid, head of the department, is the miracle worker who paints out the dots and dashes [pb] and lines and circles. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40040" docsrc="bnc_ASN_2399">
<answer instance="chair.40040" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
His face was grotesquely puffed and had taken on the colour of dark purple.
Sandison did not even bother to check his pulse or try to revive him.
Maidstone was dead.
The old lady, following Sandison into the tiny bedroom, dropped to her knees, crossed herself and started up a high-pitched wailing, interspersed with fragments of speech which Sandison found completely incomprehensible.
He decided that the best thing for him to do was to leave as soon as possible, before other people arrived and the situation became very complicated.
After all, there was nothing he could do to help Maidstone now.
He backed out of the bedroom, leaving the old lady still on her knees before the bed.
He glanced round the small untidy sitting room and saw Maidstone's jacket on the back of a <head>chair</head> , presumably placed there by Franco.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40042" docsrc="bnc_DCH_768">
<answer instance="chair.40042" senseid="U"/>
<context>
One, one [pause] er stress in my, on what happens so that, that it's companying it's been manufacturing leg irons that's been going out there to the Nile, hasn't it, wasn't it to [unclear]. [/u][u]
They didn't mention [unclear], they'd mentioned somewhere else, but erm [/u][u]
Somewhere. [/u][u]
I think it was Central America wasn't it? [/u][u]
Wasn't it Saudi?. [/u][u]
No. [/u][u]
[ptr]Saudi they had some sort of electronic torture chamber [ptr][/u][u]
[ptr]Thing [unclear] electric [unclear] was [ptr][/u][u]
Oh yeah, the erm, the house of [unclear] or something. [/u][u]
Yeah. [/u][u]
Wasn't one of the <head>chair</head> was, though the man held up, held [unclear] arms was it? [/u][u]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40043" docsrc="bnc_B2F_178">
<answer instance="chair.40043" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
Typically a group might have a system of going round the table, letting everyone have their say.
It might also instigate a system of writing up the objective in large letters for all to see. [/p] [/item] [item] [p]
The need for strong leadership is frequently emphasized.
In a formal group this means ensuring that people stick to the procedures, don't argue, don't interrupt one another and so on.
Strong leadership is seen as the solution to the problems of the chaotic stage.
If the group fails, the leader is criticized for not being strong enough! [/p] [/item] [item] [p]
Different people in the group will be given specific roles such as time keeper, secretary; and there will be explicit rules of behaviour such as only speaking through the <head>chair</head> , considering one idea at a time, recapping frequently from the secretary's minutes and so on. [/p] [/item] [item] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40046" docsrc="bnc_AJV_471">
<answer instance="chair.40046" senseid="rocking_chair-0"/>
<context>
In the '70s, the family enjoyed a number of hits on Stax and, while Pop retains a firm belief in the efficacy of prayer, he continues to wrap his social and spiritual concerns in the funkiest of backbeats. [/p] [p]
Staples has a reedy, careworn voice that is oddly uplifting, and his music has a country sense of space.
The family reunite on the Los Lobos-penned title track, Bonnie Raitt and Jackson Browne sing on the opening World In Motion, and Ry Cooder produces the album's highspot: a version of the traditional Down in Mississippi that sounds truly Muddy. [/p] [p]
Naturally, Pop worries over the state of his people in songs like America and Miss Cocaine, but his caring stoicism is a voice from the rocking <head>chair</head> that seems almost too dignified and decent for the '90s neighbourhood. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40047" docsrc="bnc_B1H_2275">
<answer instance="chair.40047" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
What major differences are there in the choices made at various times for starting steel works at Sheffield, Rotherham and Scunthorpe? [pb] [gap] [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Energy for modern industry and homes [/head] [p]
[hi]A. [/hi] There are many obvious ways in which we use energy, or fuel.
What are these? [/p] [p]
Some ways are less obvious.
Consider a plateful of baked beans on toast.
Electricity was used to mill the flour, to bake the bread, for driving milking machines and then butter churns, to cook the beans in the factory, to mould the tin can, to make the paper for the label and to print it, and finally to heat the beans and make the toast.
Coal was used to smelt the steel for the tinplate and petrol to transport all the parts and goods.
Altogether a lot of energy has been put into it. [/p] [p]
What energy went into each of these: the <head>chair</head> and table, the knife and fork, the plate and the saucepan? [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40049" docsrc="bnc_CER_136">
<answer instance="chair.40049" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
Everyone's environmental awareness was sharpened: &bquo;Pollution free energy from fusion&equo; was the cry; if there was a time ripe for exploiting the story, Easter 1989 could hardly have been bettered. [/p] [p]
A premature release of the story in London, picked up by the BBC World Service and the news wire services, led to the University of Utah being inundated with eager news reporters for the press conference.
Television cameras, radio microphones and hundreds of fascinated spectators brought to remote Utah the sort of attention usually reserved for an important visiting head of state in Washington or New York. [/p] [p]
And if what they were hearing was really true, then this was indeed more important than most of those East Coast press conferences.
Pons, [pb] the <head>chair</head> of the university chemistry department, told them &bquo;we have sustained a controlled nuclear fusion reaction by means which are considerably simpler than conventional&equo;.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40050" docsrc="bnc_A0X_1789">
<answer instance="chair.40050" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
For woodworkers inspired by furniture and cabinetmaking, the September issue of [hi]Woodworker [/hi] will be filled with potential projects, ideas and techniques.
Michael Burley charts the progression of his collector's cabinet, explaining how to make the piece with veneers, MDF and solid timber.
Adrian Jones, who studied for a number of years at Parnham House, has made a similar cabinet, and in the September issue he displays that piece and talks bout his work as a successful furniture-maker. [/p] [p]
Any readers attempting to furnish a home should find ample material in the September issue.
Ralph Sinnott makes a desk and chair, while Hazel Rogers moves from the box she wrote about in the April issue, to a nest of tables.
Brian Cook shows how to make a coffee table, and Steve Goulden will be moving to the second part of his feature on <head>chair</head> design and construction.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40053" docsrc="bnc_CDN_2167">
<answer instance="chair.40053" senseid="easy_chair-0"/>
<context>
She was delighted when the story of Hank fell into her lap; an interview with his mother would fill half a column nicely.
Her pleasure was, however, short lived.
Like all good stories unearthed by such lady editors, it was snatched away from her, and, barring wars and acts of God, as Donny O'Brien reported to Mr Pascall, the bookseller, it would be a front-page headline on Monday.
It was, therefore, no quiet lady columnist to whom Mrs Stych opened the door that evening, but an eager male reporter keen on a front-page story. [/p] [p]
He shot through the door almost as soon as it was opened, closely followed by a small, bald-headed individual carrying what looked like a suitcase. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Hank Stych!&equo; he hailed a startled Boyd, who had half risen from an easy <head>chair</head> , scattering the papers on which he had been working.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40055" docsrc="bnc_APX_1325">
<answer instance="chair.40055" senseid="U"/>
<answer instance="chair.40055" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Typical of the unusual and smart staircases marketed by Staircase Solutions of Alexandra Palace is the Niviv &mdash; a steel design which gives maximum flexibility, is self-supporting up to 16 risers, adjustable on site, suitable for internal or external use and is supplied in a range of colours, as well as stainless steel.
Other stairs available include British, Danish and French systems.
Reader enquiry number 124 [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Wood Laminate [/head] [p]
Suitable for internal use, Formica's new Lignaform range for decorative laminates incorporates real wood veneers to combine the appearance of a genuine wood surface with the durability of a high pressure decorative laminate.
Six wood veneers in Natural or Surfaced finishes are currently available and it is anticipated that appropriate applications will be for wall panelling and furniture.
Reader enquiry number 125 [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Restaurant <head>Chair</head> [/head] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40058" docsrc="bnc_A0X_1179">
<answer instance="chair.40058" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
It has gone very sweetly ever since but that was a good deal of production time that was lost that cost me a lost more money than I had anticipated.
Certainly if I had been doing all the restoration work myself it wouldn't have cost me so much because I am the cheapest worker in this outfit. [/p] [p]
So now if I need a &bquo;new&equo; piece of equipment I go to a reputable second-hand wood working machinery dealer.
Next month I will take you to meet Brian Stacey of Daltons in Nottingham. [ptr][ptr][ptr][pb] [/p] [caption]
Space around a bandsaw is vital [/caption] [caption]
Doubtless the door helps for extra length over the planer [/caption] [caption]
Unfortunately, for boards over 10ft long, David has to thickness elsewhere [/caption] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Three dimensions of <head>chair</head> design [/head] [caption]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40059" docsrc="bnc_AJU_876">
<answer instance="chair.40059" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
Gen Nwachukwu rejected criticism that Nigeria was acting prematurely in establishing contact with South Africa before the white minority regime had ended.
He said Mr Babangida was meeting Mr de Klerk in his role as Organisation of African Unity (OAU) chairman and to assist in the Codesa process. [/p] [p]
Mr de Klerk visited several African countries last year, despite an OAU motion to continue boycotting South Africa.
Mr Pik Botha, South Africa's Foreign Minister, said on arrival in Abuja this week that Pretoria would seek OAU membership. [/p] [p]
Preparations for a Nigerian visit by Mr de Klerk last year were put on ice because of ANC pressure on Mr Babangida, diplomatic sources said.
Nigeria's term in the OAU <head>chair</head> is due to expire in a few months, and Mr Babangida is determined to contribute to a South African settlement before leaving office. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40062" docsrc="bnc_CAB_2211">
<answer instance="chair.40062" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;It ent usually like this,&equo; said Carrie. [/p] [p]
&bquo;They've had to get an extra teacher,&equo; added her sister. [/p] [p]
&bquo;And,&equo; said George, 'we have to share the school with some Catholics.
We're havin' it in turns.
Look!&equo; and he [pb] pointed in the direction of two nuns surrounded by a horde of children.
&bquo;If it stays like this we ent goin' to have much school at all,&equo; and he grinned with pleasure. [/p] [p]
The five of them went into the hall together.
The black-out curtains which were rolled neatly above the windows stood out starkly against the light green walls and wooden skirting boards.
Mr Bush was seating the small children cross-legged on the polished wooden floor.
The older children were to sit in the back half of the hall which was filled with rows of <head>chairs</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40064" docsrc="bnc_ATE_3188">
<answer instance="chair.40064" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Did they they think the bloody Turks would leave it open for them?
And where was Churchill when the bullets were flying?
Crying his eyes out about that bloody poof, Rupert Brooke?
There is a corner of a foreign field alright.
It's Turkish and its thick with ANZAC dead and the guilty party therefrom is forever England!&equo;
And the Aussies cheered, daring the policemen to make a move. [/p] [p]
In 1916, conscription was introduced in Britain.
The Old Contemptibles had become a compulsory and unwilling army.
On Easter Monday rebels in Dublin led by James Connolly and Padraig Pearse proclaimed an Irish Republic.
All seven leaders were later executed.
Connolly was allowed to recover from his wounds in hospital and was then taken from Kilmainham Gaol to Dublin Castle and shot by firing squad sitting in a <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40066" docsrc="bnc_CK9_1234">
<answer instance="chair.40066" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;Just in case somebody takes a fancy to it.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;No-one would run off with a hand-cart.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Well, they've done it before.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Really?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Yes, rea-lly!
Get yourself down those steps, and see if I can follow you.&equo; [/p] [p]
The stone steps were narrow, and she didn't like stone steps, they were greasy when wet, but she [pb] made the bottom of them and inserted the key in the lock.
She followed the child into the room, but there she stood aghast.
It was a cellar, stone-floored and stone-walled, and stone cold.
It was obviously partitioned into two rooms by a rough wooden screen.
In the part in which she was standing was a small table and two <head>chairs</head> and an iron contraption that looked as if it might be used for some form of heating.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40068" docsrc="bnc_ACE_1484">
<answer instance="chair.40068" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The Sergeant came rushing in from next door. [/p] [p]
&bquo;You all right, sir?&equo; [/p] [p]
Was that a shot?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Oh Thank Gawd!
Man with a live round still in his breech.
Stupid devil might have killed someone.
Good job he missed you.
Look!
There's the hole right enough, see &mdash; in the panelling just above your head, sir&hellip; and it went&hellip; through the gents&equo;&hellip;
No-one usin' it at the time so that was lucky too.&equo; [/p] [p]
A shaken Charles followed the line of the bullet and sat down in the nearest <head>chair</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40071" docsrc="bnc_A0X_1211">
<answer instance="chair.40071" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
During a study of the various styles, it became apparent to me that if the back legs are set into the seat rails at an angle, this angle, together with the curvature of the rear legs and backward slope of the chair back can regulate the flair: if the legs are mounted at right angles to the rear seat rail, there would be no flair.
Increasing this angle increases the flair very sensitively, up to the maximum deflection of the curve of the rear leg, if it were to be (impractically!) mounted in the plane or the rear seat rail. [/p] [p]
The requirement for robustness also demands that there be leg braces to create a strong rectangle around the rear seat joint, the point of maximum strain in all chairs.
Anyone who has had to reglue chairs will be painfully aware of this fact.
A crossmember between these two braces helps; people frequently put their legs back under their chair seats, and a cross brace between the front legs would be in the way. [/p] [p]
The above design conclusions have profound implications for the construction details of my <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40072" docsrc="bnc_CCM_2336">
<answer instance="chair.40072" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;They've cancelled my appointments for this morning&hellip;.
Maybe you'd walk me down to the Shelbourne for a taxi?&equo; he asked Jack. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I could get one here, and come home with you.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;No, no, you know I don't want that.
Stay here in the waiting room, will you, Jack?&equo; [/p] [p]
Jack moved into the over-bright room with the yellow walls.
Two girls sat at a table.
One of them was a spectacularly pretty blonde; the other, a big girl with long chestnut hair tied back in a bow, had a bandage on her foot.
He realised they must have been in the accident. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Was it terrible?&equo; he asked, looking questioningly at the empty chair, as if asking their permission to sit down.
They pulled the <head>chair</head> forward and told him about it.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40074" docsrc="bnc_AMB_2393">
<answer instance="chair.40074" senseid="reclining_chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;Endill,&equo; she said softly.
&bquo;I want to talk to you.
Come to the sick bay with me.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I&hellip; er&hellip; can't,&equo; said Endill, not wanting to waste any time.
&bquo;I'm busy.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;It's about the Book creature,&equo; Matron whispered.
&bquo;When I check up on him in the morning he asks for you.
Do you want to tell me about it?
Don't worry, you can trust me.&equo; [/p] [p]
Endill followed her to the sick bay.
He was a little hesitant at first but soon had told her everything; how he met the Bookman, [pb] his funny habits, his endless knowledge, their pranks, sitting in the sun on reclining <head>chairs</head> and leaping through the shelves. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40075" docsrc="bnc_CA6_1030">
<answer instance="chair.40075" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
It is difficult to believe that a writer who writes such drivel as does Paul Gallico could be so unpleasantly deluded with grandeur.
Angel wasn't in it.
There was a sinister and often rehearsed entrance wearing a long cloak and looking like Count Dracula.
&bquo;Mr [hi]Wilson's [/hi] kind, but [hi]he [/hi] makes me feel out of it,&equo; whispered Mrs H. Mr Wilson was indeed [pb] kind.
I could not have got through it without him.
He is funny too.
I liked him so very much.
He &mdash; in his little bit, sitting on a different spindly <head>chair</head> &mdash; had the presence of mind to take the opportunity of delivering an onslaught on the Snow school of criticism, the stranglehold they have, their implication that there are worthwhile characters who &bquo;matter&equo; and others that cannot have any importance.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40077" docsrc="bnc_ARJ_1435">
<answer instance="chair.40077" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Think of ways to make life more fun together.
When both partners work to make life more delightful, a marriage is constantly revitalised and thoughts of straying aren't likely to arise. [/p] [p]
Convey a sense of trust in your partner.
Trust is essential to intimacy, and intimacy is at the core of a successful marriage.
Yes, trust is sometimes betrayed, but much more often it is fulfilled.
Believing in the other person &mdash; extending trust &mdash; helps to create and sustain constancy and trustworthiness. [ptr][/p] [caption]
High fidelity: &bquo;Couples can enhance their relationships, making their marriages so solid that infidelity is unlikely to occur&equo; [/caption] [/div2] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Clash of the TARTANS [/head] [caption]
Plates, tiles, carpeting, <head>chairs</head> : everything in Anne and Lachlan Stewart's home is tartan.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40078" docsrc="bnc_ALL_309">
<answer instance="chair.40078" senseid="U"/>
<answer instance="chair.40078" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;They and others of the citizens are pulling the theatre down, and the soldiers from the Gallowgate Barracks are awa'!&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Are they indeed?&equo;
The frown looked almost benign. [/p] [p]
&bquo;And the actors have fled.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Have they indeed?&equo;
It seemed for the barest fraction of an instant that a smile might be knocking at the underside of that granite jaw. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Aye, Reverend,&equo; continued the Elder, getting his wind.
&bquo;The hale contraption, painted trees, stage, tents, all down and trampled underfoot.&equo; [/p] [p]
The Reverend Whitefield sat back and made a steeple of his fingers, secure in his knowledge of the power and the professionalism of his performance. [pb] [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
GET YOUR HORSE OFF MY <head>CHAIR</head> 1753 A.D. [/head] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40080" docsrc="bnc_APR_839">
<answer instance="chair.40080" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
She did not remark on this.
The walls of the paternoster were mirror-tiled, bronze-lit; she flashed at him from wall to wall, hotly.
Out again she came precisely; he tripped on this threshold too, the floor lifting beneath him. [/p] [p]
Her room was glass-walled on one side, and lined floor to ceiling with books on the others.
The books were arranged rationally, thematically, alphabetically, and dust-free; this last was the only sign of housekeeping in that austere place.
The beautiful thing in that room was Maud Bailey herself, who went down on one knee very gracefully to plug in a kettle, and produced from a cupboard two blue and white Japanese mugs. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Take a seat,&equo; she said crisply, indicating a low upholstered bright blue <head>chair</head> where students no doubt sat to have their work handed back.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40081" docsrc="bnc_CG6_215">
<answer instance="chair.40081" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Here, the argument is presented that conceptual levels of understanding are necessary precursors to the emergence of spoken language, since language is, in effect, the linguistic realisation of those conceptual distinctions already established at a non-verbal level.
When conceptual distinctions are expressed in language they are referred to as [hi]semantic [pb] relations [/hi].
While emphasising the interdependence between semantic expres&rehy;sions and underlying cognitive concepts, this approach also implies that not all of a child's understanding of a particular experience may be expressed in language, and that a child may [hi]intend [/hi] to express more than she is actually able to encode formally in language structures.
For example, Chapter 1 discussed the ways in which researchers have introduced the notion of a &bquo;rich interpretation&equo; of utterances such as &bquo;sweater <head>chair</head> &equo;, &bquo;Daddy car&equo; in order to disambiguate alternative meanings. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40083" docsrc="bnc_ADY_1044">
<answer instance="chair.40083" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;He does.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;It makes you think a bit.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;What about?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I mean, he's just Dad.&equo;
He struggled to get it right.
&bquo;Everyone's two people, aren't they?&equo; [/p] [p]
I said with interest, &bquo;That's profound.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Get away.&equo;
He felt awkward at the compliment.
&bquo;I'm glad for him, anyway.&equo; [/p] [p]
He snaked off again and within minutes the throng began moving towards dinner, dividing into ten to a table, lowering bottoms onto inadequate <head>chairs</head> , fingering menus, peering at the print through candlelight, scanning their allotted neighbours.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40084" docsrc="bnc_CDM_799">
<answer instance="chair.40084" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;I shall be needing them all for the meeting.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;But what am we gooin' ter do?&equo; she wailed tearfully. [/p] [p]
After pausing for a second he must have relented, because he told her that if it was any help she could borrow benches and trestle tables. [/p] [p]
&bquo;That'll do.&equo;
She brightened up visibly.
&bquo;I'll send somebody to fetch 'em in the mornin'.
Yer see it's tomorra the weddin'.
An' yow come yerself if yer like.&equo; [/p] [p]
But the Captain didn't reply.
He just waved her away and turned his back on us, and while he wasn't looking Mum whispered in Billy's ear: &bquo;Yer wunt ter keep that up fer yer bung!&equo;
And with that she dug him in his ribs so hard that he nearly fell off his <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40086" docsrc="bnc_CKD_878">
<answer instance="chair.40086" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Hari moved into them, resting her head wearily against the roughness of his shirt.
He held her close, smoothing back her hair, his big hands so gentle.
She could hear the beating of his heart and she closed her eyes, thankful for his presence for she could not bear to be alone, not now, not yet. [/p] [p]
He released her.
&bquo;You must get back to your work as soon as possible,&equo; he said.
&bquo;Work will ease the pain, in time, believe me.&equo; [/p] [p]
He meant well but how could Hari ever get over the shock of her mother's sudden death? [/p] [p]
He made her tea and sat holding her hand until the light faded and the lamps in the street were lit, shedding a faint light into the room. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I must go out,&equo; Craig said, &bquo;but I promise I won't be long.&equo; [/p] [p]
Hari sat up straighter in her <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40087" docsrc="bnc_C8P_895">
<answer instance="chair.40087" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
So the numbers go round in a circle one, two, three, four, five, six, buzz, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, buzz, fifteen, sixteen, buzz, eighteen, nineteen, twenty, buzz, twenty two, twenty [pb] three, twenty four, twenty five, twenty six, buzz, buzz, twenty nine, thirty. [/p] [p]
An alternative to &bquo;buzz&equo; is to say &bquo;fizz&equo; for five. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
28 Hockey [/head] [p]
Number the children into two equal teams and call two players.
There are then two ways to proceed.
For younger children, one way is to have hockey sticks made of two rolled-up newspapers placed either side of a ball which is put in the middle of the room.
The two players whose numbers have been called pick up the hockey sticks, and the first one to hit the ball gets the point.
For older children, make goals at either end of the room out of <head>chair</head> legs and give the point to the first person to score. [/p] [/div3] [/div2] [div2] [head]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40089" docsrc="bnc_APE_1189">
<answer instance="chair.40089" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
The Committee even considered the possibility that the occupant of the Chair be given a cut-off button or that other devices be employed to override demonstrations or disturbance in the galleries or on the floor of the House, but it rejected such innovations.
It did not want any kind of disorder to be filmed, including unparliamentary behaviour by Members (or even Members trying to attract attention by wearing fancy dress or clothes bearing slogans), and it therefore recommended that in all cases of disruption or disorder the director should cut to wide-angle shots, which would not show the offending incident, or to the occupant of the Chair. [/p] [p]
In practice, the rules regarding the treatment of incidents of serious disorder remain largely untested, as there were few such occasions during the experiment.
The Committee was satisfied that minor incidents of misconduct or defiance of the <head>Chair</head> had been well handled by the directors within the rules.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40090" docsrc="bnc_C8P_1082">
<answer instance="chair.40090" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The first people in each team place the keys down their neck and out through the bottom of their trouser legs or slacks.
The second person then follows so that in the end the whole team is linked together by string. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
53 Give us a clue [/head] [p]
Divide the party into two groups.
One person on each side chooses a book, film or television programme and the rest have to guess what it is, by means of mime.
There are various tricks that are used.
For example &bquo;the&equo; is signalled by two fingers placed together in the shape of a T, touching the ear indicates &bquo;sounds like&equo;, patting your hand on your head means &bquo;name&equo;, and it is often helpful to indicate the number of words by fingers. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
54 Pawn shop [/head] [p]
This is an old family game.
Divide up the party into three or four teams and place a <head>chair</head> in the middle of the room.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40094" docsrc="bnc_CAB_307">
<answer instance="chair.40094" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Willie placed the toasted bread on plates while Tom [pb] spooned a large quantity of steaming scrambled eggs on them.
A bowl of hot, buttered, boiled potatoes stood in the middle of the table. [/p] [p]
&bquo;You can sit down now,&equo; said Tom. [/p] [p]
Willie picked up a potato in his hands, gasped and dropped it onto his plate.
Feverishly he attacked the meal.
His small elbows stuck out at the sides as he cut and ate food in a frenzy.
When the meal was eaten Tom unwrapped a small brown package which contained four pieces of dark, home-made ginger cake. [/p] [p]
&bquo;One fer tonight; one fer tomorrow,&equo; said Tom, handing him a piece. [/p] [p]
Willie had never eaten cake before.
When he had finished it, he leaned back in his <head>chair</head> and, resting his hands on his stomach, he watched Sammy who was making a series of strange noises in his food while his tail continued to wag from side to side. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40096" docsrc="bnc_B3J_1697">
<answer instance="chair.40096" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The smell, still familiar after her years away, hit her immediately.
The mixture of oil, rusty tools, creosote and vegetable seeds, mingled into a unique scent.
Impossible to duplicate or forget. [/p] [p]
An old faded deck chair hung from a six inch nail which had probably been hammered into the shed wall twenty years before.
She unhooked the chair, dusted it off and carried it back to the front lawn. [/p] [p]
The last trace of cloud had disappeared from the sky.
Julie decided to top up her Californian suntan until Kitty Summerville called lunch, after which she would take a casual stroll to another of her favourite haunts as a child, the old summer house on the river bank. [/p] [p]
She lay back in the musty smelling <head>chair</head> , at peace with the world, and allowed the late April sun to [corr] envelop [/corr] her. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40099" docsrc="bnc_AEA_1677">
<answer instance="chair.40099" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Elisabeth had not walked over to the Villa with the other guests, but lagged behind.
&bquo;Yes, I'm coming, but I've one or two things to attend to first,&equo; she explained.
And when she did at last enter the music room &mdash; through the door from the arboretum &mdash; she found herself a seat at the back, at the end of a row.
She had taken pains to arrive only just in time.
Fru M&oslash;ller, seated in the front row, was too busy being pleased at this opportunity to provide her guests with free, unexpected entertainment to think of much else.
She had looked round once to see if her guests were all [hi]in situ [/hi] and observed that almost all the chairs were occupied.
She smoothed her unwrinkled silk dress, fingered the amber beads at her neck and settled into her <head>chair</head> , determined to experience herself being well-pleased.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40100" docsrc="bnc_CHE_1320">
<answer instance="chair.40100" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
I kept them interested for half an hour and now I can't even remember what I said.
It was all off the top of my head.
I had some notes jotted down on a card somewhere, but I quickly went off them and chatted about whatever seemed interesting.
(I've done dozens of lectures now, in front of all sorts of people, and I always make it up as I go along, although I suppose I must have a rough idea about what I'm going to say.)
When I thought I'd run out of things to say I asked the front two rows to move back and the whole place started buzzing.
It was Dawn's turn.
They knew I was going to attempt a display.
There was one kid, however, who didn't move back as far as the rest of his row, so I politely asked him to get in line.
Well, there's always one.
I suppose he thought I was exaggerating the danger and he'd show how tough he was, so he moved his <head>chair</head> back about an inch.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40102" docsrc="bnc_CR6_388">
<answer instance="chair.40102" senseid="easy_chair-0"/>
<context>
Then, assured that the children were all in their beds, she went back to her preparations, humming 8 little tune.
Her last task was to lay thick strips of bacon across the turkey.
Finally she stepped back from the table to admire her handiwork.
Then, picking up the poker from the hearth, she banged it three times against the back of the fireplace.
A few seconds later the banging was answered by two sharp thuds.
Going to the sink she filled the kettle with water and placed it on the gas.
As the kettle came to the boil she heard the back door open and popped her head into the scullery to see her friend Pat Johnstone kicking snow off her shoes. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Get yourself in, Pat, I've got the kettle on.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Oh, Sar, it's brass monkey weather out there tonight!&equo; [/p] [p]
Coming into the kitchen, Pat dropped into an easy <head>chair</head> by the fire.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40105" docsrc="bnc_CD6_61">
<answer instance="chair.40105" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Although certainly no fan of Guns N'Roses and their offensive lyrics, I am pleased that he has spoken about the still largely-hidden subject of male sexual assault.
It is important that men feel able to discuss this issue and not experience ridicule and smug responses from so-called enlightened magazines such as yours.
Comments such as &bquo;a history of childhood abuse is both hip and horrible, the rock'n'roll statement with knobs on&equo; do not encourage other men to discuss the issue, nor do they treat this subject with the seriousness it deserves.
Male survivors of abuse and our society in general pay a high price for the current silence. [/p] [p]
[hi]Correction [/hi] The &bquo;Utsly-Gtsly <head>chair</head> &equo; shown in October's Hype was not, as we were told, the work of &bquo;furniture tailor&equo; Yoichi Nakamura.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40107" docsrc="bnc_BNK_640">
<answer instance="chair.40107" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
support for academic developments through Fellowships, Scholarships and Student Bursaries; [/item] [item]
the provision of more student residences and an improvement in the academic, social and recreational activities of the University. [/item] [/list] [/p] [p]
In real terms these overall objectives have been translated into a series of major development projects.
They include (in no particular order): [list] [item]
expansion of the Engineering Faculty to double its present size; [/item] [item]
a purpose-built home for the Department of Music; [pb] [/item] [item]
enlargement of the Veterinary School for an increased student entry; [/item] [item]
new laboratories for &bquo;Molecular Science and the Environment&equo;; [/item] [item]
a research endowment for the <head>Chair</head> of Medicine; [/item] [item]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40108" docsrc="bnc_ABX_1658">
<answer instance="chair.40108" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
And Mrs Wright wouldn't check when she got back.
Why should she?
She'd asked Philip to help Lee and he'd said he would.
She'd discover he hadn't locked the hen-house when she went to let the hens out in the morning. [/p] [p]
Philip sat down on his bed.
He was hot in his anorak.
As he took it off he remembered the sausage and treacle tart in his pocket.
He didn't feel like them now.
Anyway they'd be pretty disgusting, mixed with the bits in his pocket. [/p] [p]
He could hear someone coming upstairs, his Mum.
She picked his anorak up off the floor and stood there with it over her arm, leaning against his <head>chair</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40111" docsrc="bnc_CKD_206">
<answer instance="chair.40111" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
With a sigh, Hari moved to the back entrance and knocked again.
She waited what seemed an interminably long time before the same young maid again confronted her. [/p] [p]
&bquo;What is your business?&equo;
The maid looked at a point above Hari's head. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I have a delivery for Mr Morris,&equo; Hari said shortly, &bquo;I should have thought that much was obvious even to you.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Step inside.&equo;
The girl didn't deign to rise to the bait.
&bquo;I'll see if Mr Morris will speak with you.&equo; [/p] [p]
After a time, the girl returned and, with obvious reluctance, led Hari into the sitting-room.
It was a high-ceilinged, gracious room with thick carpet under-foot and rich curtains over the windows. [/p] [p]
A visitor sat in a <head>chair</head> near the elegant grate where a huge fire burned, he glanced up at her and his eyes narrowed.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40112" docsrc="bnc_CKU_1614">
<answer instance="chair.40112" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Other fine examples of Central Italian terracotta include several &bquo;Baskets with flowers, fruit and insects&equo; by Giovanni della Robbia (Altomani) and a &bquo;Saint Catherine of Siena&equo; by Lorenzo di Mariano, known as il Marrina (Il Cartiglio).
To the Napoleonic era belong a &bquo;Portrait of General Suvarov&equo; carved in wood by Bonzanigo and a terracotta maquette by Canova for the portrait of Elisa Baciocchi Bonaparte in the guise of &bquo;The Muse Polymnia&equo;, now in Vienna (both exhibited by Antichi Maestri Pittori).
Of more recent origin is a &bquo;Via Crucis&equo; decorating a vase by Leonardo Bistolfi (Liberty &amp; Deco). [/p] [p]
The furniture section includes a few fifteenth-century pieces, including a small intarsia <head>chair</head> (Botticelli), and a painted cassone bearing the arms of the Strozzi-Sacrati family (Altomani).
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40114" docsrc="bnc_CBC_8353">
<answer instance="chair.40114" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
As he grew up he bitterly accused his mother of having shown little interest in him. [/p] [p]
Friends claim he underwent a drastic change when he served his first prison sentence for burglary. [/p] [p]
Former girlfriend Gill Grenfell, the half sister of Vernage's sidekick Peter Grenfell, said: &bquo;He was a very friendly guy.
His mother used to visit his older brother Simon and make a bit of a fuss of him but she totally blanked Nick and he was hurt. [/p] [p]
&bquo;He used to be bitter because his father never visited him either but he never let his feelings out.&equo; [/p] [p]
Gill lost contact with Vernage but a month before his killing spree he reappeared. [/p] [p]
&bquo;He was still nice, or I thought he was.
He didn't treat us any different, but he was a completely changed person. [/p] [p]
&bquo;He would just sit there on a <head>chair</head> and laugh to himself.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40115" docsrc="bnc_AS0_951">
<answer instance="chair.40115" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
He can move forwards, rolling the ball forwards, and then come back almost to sit on his heels.
When he has mastered this type of movement kneeling, more advanced work might involve sitting on his heels and then shifting his weight towards his hemiplegic side to practise controlling his arm and the side of his trunk while some of his bodyweight is transmitted from side to side. [/p] [p]
Kneeling can also be used to help the patient get up from the floor; most patients are taught to do this once they can walk, in case they have a fall.
If the patient can get into the kneeling position and then balance on one knee while bringing the other leg forward, so that he can lever himself onto a <head>chair</head> , he will feel confident that he can always get up, even if he is alone at home. [pb] [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40117" docsrc="bnc_B1X_3436">
<answer instance="chair.40117" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
If anything disastrous should happen to him, such as being dismissed from his job, the urge to seek solace in the whiskey bottle might be far stronger than his strength of will.
If Kinsella were to go on a binge, he would drink his way down to the last penny of whatever money is available, irrespective of who it belongs to.&equo; [/p] [p]
Harrison turned in bewilderment to Major Calder.
&bquo;I don't understand.
What is all this leading up to?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Captain Carew will explain,&equo; Major Calder said. [pb] [/p] [p]
&bquo;We want you,&equo; Carew said, &bquo;to arrange to have Kinsella dismissed from his job.&equo; [/p] [p]
Harrison stared at him in [corr] stony [/corr] silence. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Counsel your men to be discreet,&equo; Carew continued, &bquo;we don't want Kinsella to suspect that the police were involved.&equo;
He relaxed back in the <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40118" docsrc="bnc_A33_494">
<answer instance="chair.40118" senseid="U"/>
<answer instance="chair.40118" senseid="chair-1"/>
<answer instance="chair.40118" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The Wimbledon and United States Open champion, who will also miss next week's grand prix tournament in Sydney and is unlikely to be fit for Tokyo the following week, has now lost any chance of overhauling Ivan Lendl as world No. 1 before the end of the year. [/p] [p]
At least on this occasion, Becker had played his way through to the semi-finals of the eight-man exhibition event, organised by his manager, Ion Tiriac, before pulling out.
Last November he arrived on crutches on the opening day with his left foot in plaster, having chipped an ankle bone. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Probably I started too early after Flushing Meadow,&equo; Becker said yesterday, before visiting his doctor in Munich.
Tiriac reacted with typical eloquence: &bquo;It's my tournament.
In one <head>chair</head> I'm the promoter, in another chair I'm Boris's manager and in another chair I'm his friend.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40120" docsrc="bnc_AC2_606">
<answer instance="chair.40120" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The front was slashed all the way down to her navel to reveal rounded breasts, which rose and fell temptingly like a couple of ripe peaches. [/p] [p]
Just inside the entrance, she turned to survey the [hi]client&egrave;le [/hi], making sure as she did so that all the men got a tantalising glimpse of a very long and elegant leg exposed through a side slit. [/p] [p]
The bar was fairly full, with groups of local worthies and their wives and a clutch of broody businessmen.
From the attention which focused on her, it was obvious that the blonde would make a sale in no time at all.
Eyes turned as she walked slowly across the room, brushing by this man and that.
To his [pb] surprise, she stopped when she reached Mark's <head>chair</head> and took the vacant seat beside him, nodding casually in his direction and flashing a devastating smile as she carefully arranged herself on display.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40121" docsrc="bnc_C9W_233">
<answer instance="chair.40121" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
You would be surprised to know how little alcohol is needed to affect your concentration; you certainly do not have to be drunk.
If you have had more than a little alcohol you would probably become so relaxed that you fell asleep and nothing the therapist was saying would register at all.
You would be wasting not only the therapist's time but your own money too. [/p] [p]
So use your common sense.
A light meal without alcohol about an hour or so before your treatment is just about right. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
What will I have to do? [/head] [p]
All you have to do is to be willing to co-operate with the hypnotherapist as he gently takes you through the relaxation exercise to the hypnotic state.
You will either be lying on a couch or sitting in a comfortable <head>chair</head> with a back high enough to support your head.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40124" docsrc="bnc_CDM_982">
<answer instance="chair.40124" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
When we reached our yard again I could see that Mrs Taylor and her friends had worked hard.
The trestles had been put up and were covered with white tablecloths of American oilcloth.
They were piled with corned-beef sandwiches, cheeses, sausage rolls, sliced pickled onions, beetroot, all kinds of pickles, watercress, pig's pudding and every mouthwatering delicacy you could think of.
And standing in the centre was a two-tiered, iced cake.
At one end of the table there were four stone gallon jars of ale, bottles of stout, gin and whisky.
There was room on the benches for twenty guests each side, facing each other.
We children had a table to one side to ourselves on which were laid out bottles of pop, cakes, buns and bread and jam. [/p] [p]
While the adults sat on their forms we sat ourselves down on an assortment of broken <head>chairs</head> borrowed from the neighbours.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40125" docsrc="bnc_CBN_1776">
<answer instance="chair.40125" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
She experienced a lot of pain and perhaps always would; her privations may have damaged her health permanently.
Her youth was over, and God knows it had been bitter and barren enough.
Again one has the feeling that he speaks of himself when he speaks of her.
The biggest threat, he predicted, was the presence of that &bquo;gloomy shadow master: master Albrecht D&uuml;rer knew it well enough when he placed Death behind the young couple in that beautiful etching.&equo; [/p] [p]
But enough of that: what he felt now was calm and brightness and an inexpressible gratitude.
Up in the large attic was a large bed for them, with the bedding neatly arranged.
The little girl would have his old one.
If he happened to be out when Sien came home, the flowers in front of the window by the wicker <head>chair</head> would let her know he had thought of her.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40128" docsrc="bnc_BP1_611">
<answer instance="chair.40128" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The weeks passed and Sarah and Maggie took in washing to pay the rent, but there was never enough money left to buy more than bread and a few vegetables.
Sarah's arms and legs were getting thinner every day, and the rag mat she'd started making for the hearth became too heavy to have on her lap.
But she was relieved to see Patrick thrive at last now that Maggie had been weaned off gin, and when Rosa's sixth baby arrived she helped with it, gaining experience for when her own time came. [/p] [p]
The more tired she became the more bitterly she blamed James.
To think a few minutes of thoughtless pleasure could end in this.
At the end of the summer she was so hungry she hadn't the energy to move further than Paddy's dilapidated <head>chair</head> and she stitched a baby's gown from her [pb] only decent petticoat.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40129" docsrc="bnc_CJF_2797">
<answer instance="chair.40129" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The subject is unwelcome, and it can surely have had nothing to do with his death.&equo; [/p] [p]
It was a long speech and he could see that it had tired her.
And she could not, thought Dalgliesh, be as naive as that; he was surprised that she could expect him to believe that she was.
He said: [/p] [p]
&bquo;When a man changes the whole direction of his life and is dead &mdash; possibly murdered &mdash; within a week of that decision, it must be relevant, at least to our investigation.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Oh yes, it's relevant to that I've no doubt.
There will be very few privacies in this family which won't be relevant to your investigation, Commander.&equo; [/p] [p]
He saw that in the last few seconds, she had been overcome with exhaustion.
Her body looked diminished, almost shrivelled, in the huge <head>chair</head> , and the gnarled hands on the arms began very gently to shake.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40131" docsrc="bnc_AN9_1162">
<answer instance="chair.40131" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The general public wouldn't be interested in the subtleties of unfair regulations and the clear imbalance of resources.
They would see the anti-nuclear movement as having bottled out.
But unless we could ensure that the voice of the people &mdash; fresh, urgent and heartfelt &mdash; somehow entered the hallowed inquiry chamber, with its unwritten rules and legalistic jargon, we would get stuck in a morass of procedure and paperwork where only the strong, and barristers, could possibly survive. [pb] [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
2 [/head] [p]
The building which housed most of the inquiry sessions was the former chapel of a twelfth-century priory, with a domed glass cupola, ornate floral decorations and tall niches which no doubt once held classical statues.
It was completely refurbished for the event, with smart new tables and rows of pink upholstered <head>chairs</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40132" docsrc="bnc_BMW_1738">
<answer instance="chair.40132" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
She waited for Jean, his girlfriend, to go to the Ladies, and then pounced, flirting madly and [corr] manoeuvring [/corr] him into bartering [pb] with her that he would buy two whole strips if she would have a dance with him.
Then without the slightest compunction she thrust her basin of money and book of tickets into Sally's lap and let him drag her, protesting theatrically, onto the dance floor.
When Jean returned from the Ladies there was no sign of either of them, for at the end of the dance they had slipped unnoticed out of one of the wide-open fire exits and around the back of the hall where only courting couples went. [/p] [p]
Half an hour later they were still missing.
When she finished selling the remaining tickets Sally looked around for them, realised what had happened and went back to sit on one of the hard upright <head>chairs</head> which lined the hall.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40135" docsrc="bnc_CH4_1388">
<answer instance="chair.40135" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
They've been hammered through from the outside, probably by the Trunchbull herself.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Have you ever been in there?&equo;
Lavender asked. [/p] [p]
&bquo;My first term I was in there six times,&equo; Hortensia said.
&bquo;Twice for a whole day and the other times for two hours each.
But two hours is quite bad enough.
It's pitch dark and you have to stand up [pb] dead straight and if you wobble at all you get spiked either by the glass on the walls or the nails on the door. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Why were you put in?&equo;
Matilda asked.
&bquo;What had you done?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;The first time&equo;, Hortensia said, &bquo;I poured half a tin of Golden Syrup on to the seat of the <head>chair</head> the Trunchbull was going to sit on at prayers.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40136" docsrc="bnc_BM1_846">
<answer instance="chair.40136" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
You should also avoid exposure to large doses of synthetic chemicals, [pb] such as from household timber treatment or crop-spraying (see p 249). [/p] [p]
There are also other measures that can improve overall health and make the body more resilient.
These include correcting nutritional deficiencies (see p 261), taking regular exercise, eating a good, healthy diet and reducing stress.
Tackling underlying problems such as [hi]Candida [/hi] overgrowth (see p 183) or hyperventilation (p 155) will also help considerably.
Try to get outdoors, to somewhere with clean air, as often as you can, and take some strenuous exercise to improve your general health and fitness. [/p] [p]
For those with severe chemical sensitivity, creating a chemical-free &bquo;oasis&equo; in the house can be very valuable.
For preference, this should be the bedroom, but there should be comfortable <head>chairs</head> , a table, and whatever else is needed for everyday living.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40138" docsrc="bnc_B28_465">
<answer instance="chair.40138" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
The idea of entitlement probably represents an attempt, during a much longer debate about the need for a &bquo;national&equo; curriculum, to bring into focus the child's individual needs and rights: it is needed to counterbalance any propensity towards the state's collective needs &mdash; totalitarianism if you will &mdash; which a move towards a nationally prescribed curriculum might bring with it. [/p] [p]
Of course debate about the National Curriculum has been around a lot longer, but its popularisation and public debate is a relatively recent phenomenon.
It was a &bquo;secret garden&equo; at least to David Eccles who when Secretary of State for the second time, in 1962, was determined (against the better judgement of many of its guardians) to strip it of its secrecy.
Eccles' vehicle for clearing the garden's secrecy was the Schools Council &mdash; not a very efficient or fast-moving garden Rotavator.
When James Callaghan accelerated the debate in 1976, the quality of discussion was indeed raised, in what turned out to be the Schools Council's declining years, under the combined influence of the <head>Chair</head> , John Tomlinson, and the Secretary, John Mann.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40139" docsrc="bnc_CES_998">
<answer instance="chair.40139" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
I had telephoned various nursing homes in the vicinity whose staff would, I thought, be more conversant with these vagaries of conduct, but they were all full up and I'd been starting to feel desperate.
But, hosannas in the highest, all was now well. [/p] [p]
The move itself could have been worse &mdash; but not much.
However, everyone has experienced it, though not, I dearly hope, in the same circumstances.
I had sold the contents of the cottages to the incoming purchaser, as well as several large pieces from the melin which would have been quite out of place in a modern house.
Owing to the scale of the former, artefacts needed to be the size of pantomime props to appear remotely in proportion, and I had acquired them accordingly. [/p] [p]
One such was one of those oval rattan wicker <head>chairs</head> which hung from a beam far above.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40142" docsrc="bnc_A6N_254">
<answer instance="chair.40142" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
In fact, he instinctively stepped backwards into the plantation as the car door was thrown open.
Without moving he watched McQuaid struggle from the car and then stand leaning on the open door as if waiting for someone to appear.
He could have called out from where he stood but he did not.
McQuaid slammed the car door and walked towards the house.
Not until he was several minutes within the house did Moran leave the plantation.
He came slowly and deliberately across the fields to the back door.
Though he had lived for weeks for this hour he now felt a wild surge of resentment towards McQuaid as he came into his own house. [/p] [p]
McQuaid was seated in the armchair by the fire.
His powerful trunk and huge belly filled the <head>chair</head> and the yellow cattleman's boots were laced halfway up the stout legs.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40143" docsrc="bnc_CDM_1501">
<answer instance="chair.40143" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
I turned to run but slipped over, and that was too much even for my sister who came to my rescue and dared them to throw any more.
They did not. [/p] [p]
&bquo;What's wrong with 'em?&equo;
I cried.
&bquo;What 'ave I done?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I told 'em about you an' the money lender but I didn't know they were gooin' to snowball yer,&equo; she said, pulling me to my feet. [/p] [p]
I rather liked the name &bquo;Louise&equo; but not the snowballs, and from that day on until I left school the girls who didn't like me called after me: &bquo;There goes Miss Louise.&equo;
It was jealousy, I suppose; the fact that I had spotted a chance they had not, although I couldn't get over the suspicion that their reaction to me had something to do with how Liza had told the story. [/p] [p]
When I returned home that afternoon I was surprised to find Dad already sitting in his <head>chair</head> by the fire. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40146" docsrc="bnc_CEF_1894">
<answer instance="chair.40146" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Is there much competition between people at work, or are you united in fighting external competition? [/item] [item]
Does the organisation foster a sense of belonging and membership through organised social events, sports and recreation facilities, and &bquo;perks&equo; to employees? [/item] [item]
What does the environment you work in say about the company and its attitude towards employees? [/item] [/list] [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
THE TRAPPINGS OF OVERT STATUS [/head] [p]
She took the lift to the fifteenth floor.
The managing director's secretary led her to his office through two ante-rooms.
Her feet sank into the thick pile of the carpet.
She walked into a spacious room on [pb] the corner of the building, with large windows on two sides providing panoramic views of the City.
His large walnut desk was at one end, at the other were plush leather <head>chairs</head> with an expensive glass coffee table.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40147" docsrc="bnc_CJF_873">
<answer instance="chair.40147" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
If Father Barnes took it into his head to ring and got no reply he'd probably come round to see [pb] if Berowne was all right.
If he continued to get the engaged sound he'd probably assume that Berowne was having an evening of telephoning and let it go.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;We might get a palm print, sir.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Unlikely, John.
If this is murder, we're not dealing with a fool.&equo; [/p] [p]
He continued his exploration.
With his gloved hands, he pulled open the top drawer and found a stack of white writing paper, of cheap quality, headed with the name of the church, and a box of envelopes.
Apart from these, the desk held nothing of interest.
Against the left-hand wall was an assortment of canvas and metal <head>chairs</head> neatly stacked, presumably for the occasional use of the parochial church council.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40149" docsrc="bnc_CGS_1444">
<answer instance="chair.40149" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
She wore her parents out by nightly refusing to go to bed until they did; whereupon she would sleep normally.
Kim was eventually seen by a psychiatrist and the latter told the parents she was going through a phase of sibling rivalry which she would eventually grow out of.
Unfortunately the nerves of her parents couldn't wait that long! [/p] [p]
The most persistent difficulty occurred whenever her mother fed the baby.
Then Kim strewed the contents of drawers, toy boxes, magazine racks and book shelves over the floor.
Afterwards, as her mother got on hands and knees to pick the objects up, Kim repeatedly climbed on her back and insisted she played &bquo;horsey&equo;.
Her mother gave in to this demand because otherwise Kim had bad tantrums during which she had once broken a glass dividing door and on another occasion a dining <head>chair</head> . [list] [label]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40150" docsrc="bnc_ACB_2568">
<answer instance="chair.40150" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Marie had been waiting for him out in the car-park. [/p] [p]
&bquo;She's all right, then?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I don't know.
All I know is, she's still alive.
She's in the same ward me Grandad was in. &mdash; Come on, I'll show you the way.&equo; [/p] [p]
Marie could not remember ever having been inside a hospital before.
She peered anxiously through the glass doors into the reception area.
&bquo;Isn't it posh!&equo; she breathed to herself.
Immediately, she felt intimidated and uneasy.
It seemed to Marie like those &bquo;executive-style&equo; rooms she had seen in numerous television advertisements and soap operas: bright, spacious and open plan with acres of carpets, a jungle of lush potted plants, low leather <head>chairs</head> with squashy seats and coffee tables, casually strewn with expensive, up-market magazines.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40152" docsrc="bnc_CN3_2422">
<answer instance="chair.40152" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
You rarely agree to see a newspaper man.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Frank, you're an impetuous man.
You'll never occupy this chair until you learn to control that impetuosity.
You really must study my methods more closely.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I know I get it wrong sometimes.&equo;
It cost Galvone a lot to say that but he knew he'd blundered.
&bquo;But I do get it right most of the time.
I think I'll freshen up my drink.&equo; [/p] [p]
He poured himself a double Scotch from the antique drinks cabinet.
Hauser leaned over, opened a drawer in a desk and slid the Grimwood folder inside.
Then, settling himself back in his <head>chair</head> , he lit a cigarette.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40153" docsrc="bnc_ANL_1676">
<answer instance="chair.40153" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;Very well, Bragg.
And, make no mistake, you have my full authority for any action you care to take.&equo; [/p] [p]
Bragg and Morton had barely got back to their office when a young constable Poked his head round the door. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Miss Marsden is here to see you, sir,&equo; he said. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Right, send her up.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I wonder if our friend Aubrey Rivington is proving recalcitrant,&equo; Morton said with a grin. [/p] [p]
&bquo;He'd better bloody not,&equo; Bragg growled.
&bquo;This case is getting complicated enough.&equo;
He stood up as Catherine entered the room. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Nice to see you, miss,&equo; he said. [/p] [p]
Morton set her a <head>chair</head> at Bragg's desk, and perched on the window-sill. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40155" docsrc="bnc_AMB_1999">
<answer instance="chair.40155" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
No-one knew quite what he did in there but there were rumours he drank tea with his furniture and wrote furiously on the walls in a language only he understood. [pb] [/p] [p]
He was often heard muttering to himself, and got into the habit of wiping surfaces with his cloak. [/p] [p]
&bquo;This school's a dirty place,&equo; he would say to no-one in particular.
&bquo;The last thing it needs is pupils walking around mucking it up.&equo; [/p] [p]
He started giving out new punishments.
He made pupils stand in orderly queues to receive nothing.
The worse your crime was, the nearer the back you stood. [/p] [p]
&bquo;You'll thank me one day,&equo; he told them.
&bquo;When you grow up all this practice will come in useful.&equo; [/p] [p]
Matron again helped pupils when the Headmaster wasn't looking.
She kept giving lifts to boys in the corridors and provided <head>chairs</head> for those standing in the queues.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40156" docsrc="bnc_ALH_2648">
<answer instance="chair.40156" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Other people have friends.
I have enemies.
Not that I care.
But there is one empty place.
The face next to it smiles at me, nervously.
I look away fast.
No one wants to be smiled at by Heather. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Hurry up,&equo; says Sir.
&bquo;Just sit by Heather.
She won't bite, you know.&equo; [pb] [/p] [p]
Heather pats the <head>chair</head> and smiles again, a truly horrible sight.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40158" docsrc="bnc_CR6_1623">
<answer instance="chair.40158" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Next time it will be twelve strokes of the ruler and your name read out at mass.&equo; [/p] [p]
Thirty faces looked scandalised at the thought of having their name read out by Father McCormack.
Picking up her chair, the nun turned to her blackboard and began writing on it. [/p] [p]
Seizing her opportunity, Margaret leant forward across her desk and whispered to Maura. [/p] [p]
&bquo;You're dead, Ryan.
Come home time I'm gonna kill you.&equo; [/p] [p]
Maura closed her eyes, a knot of fear already forming in her stomach.
Everyone was frightened of Margaret Lacey, even some of the boys.
Which was surprising really because she was so small.
But small or not, she could fight and that was all that counted.
Maura sat back in her <head>chair</head> and looked out of the window to the side of her.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40159" docsrc="bnc_C8P_1739">
<answer instance="chair.40159" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The easiest way to lay down is to slide out your hands sideways until you are more or less flat.
Take care not to relax your concentration on the way up. [gap] [/p] [p]
2.
[hi]Mind reading [/hi] At one of my first-ever children shows, the father told me of this mind reading trick which we found worked well with the children.
I left the room while the father remained as an article was chosen.
After it had been selected, I re-entered and told the audience to think about the article in question.
My partner [pb] then called out a number of articles and asked if they were the chosen one.
I said &bquo;NO&equo; to them all except the right one. [/p] [p]
The secret we used was to make the correct article immediately follow after one with four legs or corners.
So the correct article would follow a table, <head>chair</head> , the dog or cat or other relevant object in the room such as piano stool.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40161" docsrc="bnc_CHG_1597">
<answer instance="chair.40161" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
At the far end of the street, where the beach curved into an arc &mdash; and where the water was far enough away from the slops of Main Street &mdash; there on my right I could see a grove of coconut palms behind the beach, almost bending over the sand like a canopy as they leaned against the trade winds.
And high above, at the end of the curve, the steep hillsides rose as high as the rim of the dormant volcano on High Island. [/p] [p]
Alec Reid picked me up sharp at six, and gave an approving glance at my clean shirt, spotless white trousers (bought off the peg in Sydney) and the fact that I wore a tie. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Let's go,&equo; he said and led the way to the car. [/p] [p]
The Villa Faalifu was set on the edge of Tala-Tala, and the sight of its opulent exterior almost left me gasping.
It might have been transported from the South of France, one of those lush semi-palaces I had only seen in photos.
It was all white, with stone steps, instead of the usual wooden ones, and on its huge veranda were several basketwork <head>chairs</head> and tables, and yellow sunblinds. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40162" docsrc="bnc_CA7_1137">
<answer instance="chair.40162" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
When planning your excursions in Madeira, let the morning sun be your guide in deciding whether you go east or west because it is quite common for one part of the island to bask in sunshine while another is cloudy.
The weather is one thing we cannot plan for as, although Madeira enjoys a good climate all year round, you must remember it is a small island in the Atlantic Ocean. [/p] [p]
Given the topography of Madeira, it is understandable that the island roads are full of twists and turns, climbing and descending all the time.
If you are hiring a car in the island, you will need three to four days to cover most of the main roads and to savour some of the breathtaking views.
There are various maps to show you the way, and we recommend you take a picnic with you, as most viewpoints also have picnic tables and <head>chairs</head> and space to pull your car off the road.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40165" docsrc="bnc_A0D_383">
<answer instance="chair.40165" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
He turned in his chair a little.
&bquo;I am thinking, Miss Abernethie, she is perhaps wondering, Like myself, why you were sent for to Naples in the middle of the new-engaged couple's holiday.
Is the trouble at home that I am hearing of, perhaps, that someone had been &mdash; what is the expression? &mdash; boiling the books?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;No.
No.
It's a lie.
I haven't&hellip;
Why should&hellip;
Oh, you are all so beastly.
Beastly.&equo; [/p] [p]
Miss Abernethie jumped from her <head>chair</head> , scuttled in the direction of the broad flight of steps leading to the road outside, tripped clumsily over Jilly Jonathan's big crocodile-skin handbag, fell to her feet, scrambled up again, pushed the heavy bag aside with a cry of rage that came oddly from her dumpily [pb] respectable self and ran off out of sight. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40166" docsrc="bnc_AMD_413">
<answer instance="chair.40166" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Other hotel facilities include a snack bar and small shop, indoor swimming pool and roof top sun terrace, hairdressing salon, TV and reading rooms, fitness room and solarium. [/p] [p]
2 lifts; 45 bedrooms; singles on request. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
CHALET HOTEL ALTE POST (3) [/head] [p]
Built in the charming traditional chalet style, the Alte Post is quietly located yet close to all the village facilities.
Accommodation is in twin rooms in the new chalet annexe directly behind the main building.
All the room are furnished in a comfortable, rustic style and have a private bathroom, telephone and radio.
The extensive buffet breakfast is taken in the chalet, whilst nearby evening meals can be purchased in the wood panelled restaurant &bquo;Alte Post&equo;.
The cuisine is traditional and excellent.
The reception area of this relaxing hotel is extremely welcoming with an open fire and comfortable <head>chairs</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40169" docsrc="bnc_BMW_137">
<answer instance="chair.40169" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
In the late sixties he had declared &bquo;Couture is dead!&equo; and concentrated instead on off-the-peg designer wear, but twenty years later his revival had been both stunning and nostalgic and the long-term wealthy and the nouveau riche had come flocking, craving the glamour and excitement, and seeking the prestige that comes from owning a couture gown, specially, individually theirs after hours of masochistic fittings. [/p] [p]
Now they sat eagerly on the rows of brittle gilt <head>chairs</head> with red velvet seats, their exquisitely made-up faces carefully devoid of expression as they made brief notes on their programmes, pretending not to notice that sometimes the clicking cameras were directed not at the catwalk models, all of whom had already done a photo-call session for the photographers the previous day, but at them &mdash; the society women of America and the international circuit, the bored charity conscious wives of big businessmen, the famed actresses of stage and screen, even the occasional European princess.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40171" docsrc="bnc_APP_1043">
<answer instance="chair.40171" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
He shouted to the protesters: &bquo;I ask you citizens of Derry, do you approve of a crash programme of 2,000 houses?&equo;
There were cries of &bquo;yes&equo;.
They also approved his call for an extension of the boundary and he commented, &bquo;This is democracy.&equo;
He then vacated the chair saying, &bquo;on second thoughts, it is not a decent chair for a man to be seen in&equo;.
When the Unionists returned they approved a motion for the council to go into committee, which would require the gallery to be cleared.
At this point a protester shouted to Alderman Hegarty, &bquo;I do not agree with your personal politics, but take the chair.&equo;
There were cries of &bquo;take the chair&equo; and Hegarty walked up to the mayor's chair.
There was a minor scuffle between Hegarty and a Unionist councillor and before desisting, Hegarty shouted to the gallery: &bquo;Whom do you want to see in the <head>chair</head> ?&equo;
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40174" docsrc="bnc_AD1_1440">
<answer instance="chair.40174" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
There was a silence, the Matron, who was a Miss Cress, tapping her fountain pen lightly on the blotter.
Beyond the window, Alida could see Tantamount Hill, poplars at the foot, banks thick with daffodils, climbing out of sight, [/p] [p]
&bquo;She would enjoy this View.
We have nothing like it, only a view across the green.
When The Gantry was a private house, many years ago now, she came here, to balls and parties, it was quite the social centre of the county.
Oh, she talks about it so much, just as though it were yesterday.
The house is in her bones.
She was so fond of it.
It would please her to come back here.&equo; [/p] [p]
Miss Cress had periwinkle-blue eyes, small and clear as stars.
They were on Alida's face and Alida felt a chill and shifted in her <head>chair</head> , as though Miss Cress, in her navy uniform and bib, were one of the old headmistresses. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40175" docsrc="bnc_ALL_2607">
<answer instance="chair.40175" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;We used to do that sort of thing in Paris.
Climbed over the railings when the place was shut and did all sorts of things to the statues and the balconies.
So.
Set fire to the place!
Nobody will notice.
If there was a helluva crash along the road and 19 buses fell off the bridge into Queen Street Station nobody would notice.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I know,&equo; said the visitor, nodding agreement. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Ah.&equo;
The eyebrows shot up again.
&bquo;Know, do you?
If I said to you, &bquo;I saw a <head>chair</head> going down the road yesterday and&hellip;&equo; you would interrupt and say, &bquo;That belongs to Mr So-and-So, 316 Carphalute Quadrant North, Lesmahagow, AND his dog has the croup, and last year he lost his&hellip; &bquo;&equo; [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40178" docsrc="bnc_AEA_390">
<answer instance="chair.40178" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Mitzi tried to rise quickly but her sixteen stones were against all precipitous action.
She intended to slap Elisabeth on the back, but she was too late; Elisabeth had made a dash for fresh air and Mitzi's arm met that of Elisabeth's chair.
Mitzi was immediately conscious of pain and seconds later of the table upturning and its entire contents spreading themselves across the parquet.
By the time Elisabeth was out of the Hall and on to the terrace, the guests at The Tamarisks were all frozen in shocked suspension, their forks lifted half-way to their mouths, their faces pale, their palms clammy. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Oh dear!
Is Miss Danziger dying, Boo-Boo?&equo;
The Colonel did not stop to reassure his wife, but rose neatly, pushed his <head>chair</head> under his table and with swift, disciplined steps reached the terrace no more than a couple of yards behind Miss Danziger. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40179" docsrc="bnc_CKT_192">
<answer instance="chair.40179" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
Nearly half a century ago, J.M.W. Turner &mdash; he of the prize &mdash; was subject to the same patronising disparagement as Mr Davey today&equo;. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [p]
Giuliano Briganti, art historian and critic, died suddenly 17 December in Rome, aged seventy-four.
He was, with Giulio Argan who predeceased him by a month, and Federico Zeri, perhaps the leading opinion-former in the Italian art world, known to the general public from his articles in L'Espresso and then, from 1977, La Repubblica.
Trained by Roberto Longhi, he took part in the 1950s, together with Longhi and Argan, in the legation for the restitution of works of art removed to Germany during the war.
His academic career included the <head>Chair</head> in Contemporary art history at the University of Siena and his bibliography ranges from Mannerism to the Metaphysical painters and Guttuso.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40182" docsrc="bnc_AE0_447">
<answer instance="chair.40182" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
But with you and Bellow and Finn on the programme, it's a sell-out already.
We could have sold twice as many.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;How are the sales going for Wednesday?&equo;
I asked. [/p] [p]
His face clouded.
&bquo;They're coming along nicely.&equo; [/p] [p]
As Sergei went off to call his old friends, I turned into the lounge area where tea was being served, and found Surkov and Masha there.
They had accompanied Mar&iacute;a Sanchez to a mass at Westminster Cathedral; the long and, compared with an Orthodox mass, rather colourless service had drained them.
In contrast the elderly Bolivian lady had seemed energised by Christ's body.
&bquo;She needs her fix every day,&equo; said Surkov. [/p] [p]
Relaxing in the comfortable <head>chairs</head> , we surveyed the plushness of the chandeliered hotel and its sleek well-dressed patrons.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40184" docsrc="bnc_ACW_473">
<answer instance="chair.40184" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
She might even return to the house after suffering a miserable day because of him.
Her mood could escalate into a screaming rage almost without warning, and for that, too, he was responsible.
There were times when his grandma or his aunties made trouble for him behind his back, or when someone would comment on his lack of height and Sweetheart would punish him for the embarrassment he caused her. [/p] [p]
At other times he would come running in answer to her call to find her seated before the stove with her legs stretched out to the fire and her face softened by smiles.
Then he would pick up the silver hair-brush and groom her hair in slow strokes from its dark roots to its glowing auburn ends.
Or he might be handed a file and a tiny silver tool with which to clean her toenails while she dozed in a <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40186" docsrc="bnc_APP_510">
<answer instance="chair.40186" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
The 1966 congress of the CPNI adopted a &bquo;Democratic Programme for Unity&equo;, which included demands for the electoral law in Northern Ireland to be brought into line with that in Britain, except for the reintroduction of proportional representation and the abolition of cash deposits by candidates. [/p] [p]
The CPNI was not instrumental in creating NICRA but it was well represented on its first executive committee: Noel Harris of AUEW TASS, a CPNI member, was the first chairman; Derek Peters of the CPNI was secretary; and Betty Sinclair of the Belfast trades council was elected to the committee.
At the meeting which adopted the constitution, Ken Banks of AUEW TASS was added to the executive committee; he was close to the CPNI, although not actually a member.
However, at the first annual general meeting in February 1968, Banks and Harris were not returned to the executive committee and although Sinclair replaced Harris in the <head>chair</head> , Peters was replaced as secretary by John McAnerney of the CSJ.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40187" docsrc="bnc_BMN_1640">
<answer instance="chair.40187" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;Fine,&equo; he muttered.
&bquo;It makes no difference.
Come.&equo;
He led Corbett into the kitchens, a cook brought him ale and a dish of meat and vegetables.
When he had eaten, Selkirk returned and tossed his possessions at him; Corbett gathered them up and followed Selkirk up rows of steps and into a small, darkened chamber. [/p] [p]
At the far end, in a pool of light thrown by sconce-torches and a cluster of candles, sat a small, balding figure swathed in robes whom Corbett recognised as Wishart, Bishop of Glasgow.
He looked up as Corbett entered.
&bquo;Come in, Master Clerk,&equo; he called, throwing down the manuscript he had been studying.
&bquo;Come, Sir James, a stool for our guest!&equo;
Corbett sat while the Bishop poured him a cup of mulled, spiced wine; Selkirk sat alongside him, lounging in a <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40189" docsrc="bnc_CA9_151">
<answer instance="chair.40189" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
He never really accepted my Mother, who had the temerity to marry his son, but was nonetheless as overjoyed as my parents when, after four years, I was conceived. [/p] [p]
When my Mother went into labour, it was he and not my Grandmother who performed the midwifery until the ambulance arrived, then ran behind it shouting, &bquo;Make it a girl, Betty, make it a girl.&equo; [/p] [p]
He dedicated himself to me.
He secured a council house for my parents, with a garden that butted up to his own, and I enjoyed a sublime if insular childhood, basking in the adoration of my shy parents and doting grandparents. [/p] [p]
Every evening at 6.30, my &bquo;Pop&equo;, as I called him, would come across the garden to take me to bed and read me a story.
He didn't approve of smoking or drinking and my Dad was so dominated by him that he would hide his pipe behind a cushion &mdash; once setting fire to the <head>chair</head> &mdash; for fear of incurring his wrath. [pb] [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40190" docsrc="bnc_B0P_1200">
<answer instance="chair.40190" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Nothing looks worse, and does a poorer job, than a worm which has been stuck on the hook several times and looks as though it has been tied in a knot.
Fish do not find worms that look like that and hooks lose so much of their penetrating power. [/p] [p]
I cast and make sure the worm lands three or four yards further than the baited area, which allows me to pull it back to the swim and sink the line at the same time.
I repeat the action with the other rod, only this time there is a large piece of flake pulled from a new loaf on the size 2 hook. [/p] [p]
A tube of silver foil folded over a loop of line pulled down about eighteen inches between bite alarm and reel.
I sit back in my <head>chair</head> , full of anticipation and confidence, and barely even notice the chewings and scurryings of rats in the rushes. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40192" docsrc="bnc_CN3_2453">
<answer instance="chair.40192" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;I'm forgetting my manners&hellip;&equo;
Hauser introduced Carver and Galvone.
&bquo;Both senior vice presidents.
&equo; He smiled.
&bquo;One day one of them will take over from me.
The question is, which one?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Well, I think that's your decision.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Frank, get Mr Newman a drink.
What's your poison?
Then you can tell me what you want.&equo; [/p] [p]
Newman thanked him, shook his head, sat in the <head>chair</head> Hauser ushered him to with a wave of his large hand.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40193" docsrc="bnc_CHT_1183">
<answer instance="chair.40193" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
The UKCC's radical review of education and training, entitled [hi]Project 2000 &mdash; a new preparation for practice [/hi], usually known as Project 2000, was presented to Council in the Spring of 1986, and a period of consultation with the professions followed. [/p] [p]
A detailed analysis of the 2000 responses to the document was later published, as well as a financial consultancy analysis of manpower, finance and implementation issues.
In the main, the UKCC's proposals had two principal elements: a package of education and training reforms, and a package aimed at improving manpower supply and retention. [/p] [p]
Members of the original project team took as their starting point the anticipated health care needs of the society in the 1990s.
Heralding Project 2000 as a landmark in nursing history, UKCC <head>chair</head> , Audrey Emerton, described the proposed reforms as designed to produce more appropriately prepared nurses equipped to meet the perceived health care needs of future generations [corr].  [/corr]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40195" docsrc="bnc_B2S_203">
<answer instance="chair.40195" senseid="easy_chair-0"/>
<context>
Second only to the Royal Saloons of this time were the 57ft saloons de luxe, built for the accommodation of the Royal suite, when the King and Queen were travelling; when they were not required for this purpose they could be hired.
The compartments, or rooms, were decorated in white enamel, the corridor in fumed mahogany.
The body was divided into two small and one large compartments, which could be divided in the centre by folding doors.
For night travelling, brass bedsteads with handsome eiderdown quilts were provided.
The floors were covered with green figured Wilton pile carpet laid on grey felt throughout the saloon, except in the attendant's compartment and balconies. [/p] [p]
When used for day service, the furnishing comprised three easy chairs, upholstered in green and gold tapestry, one oval centre table in mahogany with inlay of tulip wood and satin wood and two folding side tables.
In the smaller compartments only two easy <head>chairs</head> were used.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40196" docsrc="bnc_ATE_1316">
<answer instance="chair.40196" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Unfortunately, that was finished now and she had to make do with what was to hand, &bquo;Johnnie Walker&equo;, which was very nice indeed thank you. [/p] [p]
After the lunch, they all sat on the verandah and looked at the grass and listened to the wood pigeons and warblers.
There was not much else to do.
The ladies had removed their hats but were still constricted by their fashionable jackets and long skirts.
The men had taken off their stiff collars, but were still uncomfortable in waistcoats and tight trousers and big boots.
The thing to do was move as little as possible. [/p] [p]
&bquo;So that was Christmas,&equo; said Bruce sleepily. [/p] [p]
&bquo;It's not over yet.
There's still Boxing Day,&equo; said Tina, dangling baby Sandy on her knee.
Jean had Roberta up at her shoulder and was patting her back and Billy was lying beside his dad in the long <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40198" docsrc="bnc_ALH_2650">
<answer instance="chair.40198" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Not that I care.
But there is one empty place.
The face next to it smiles at me, nervously.
I look away fast.
No one wants to be smiled at by Heather. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Hurry up,&equo; says Sir.
&bquo;Just sit by Heather.
She won't bite, you know.&equo; [pb] [/p] [p]
Heather pats the chair and smiles again, a truly horrible sight.
She must have forgotten a few things in the holidays, like the time I pushed her in the school goldfish pond.
I lower myself into the <head>chair</head> , keeping as far away as possible.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40199" docsrc="bnc_BM0_1126">
<answer instance="chair.40199" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Mr Gorman recently trained to become a chiropractor. [/p] [p]
The basic principle of his chair is that the knees should be below the pelvis, a quite different principle to the design of most chairs.
The usual type of chair puts an enormous strain on the spine, back muscles and many of the internal organs.
Anyone sitting down for extensive periods (as we all had to do in our school days) would have to tense many of the body's muscles in order to sit up straight.
This, in turn, causes the organs, the bones and, ultimately, the entire system to be under stress. [pb] [/p] [p]
The forward-tilting chair allows the spine and the postural muscles to support and balance the body naturally.
You can easily see the effect by placing a telephone book under each of the rear legs of a ordinary kitchen <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40201" docsrc="bnc_A70_1815">
<answer instance="chair.40201" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
It is shown here in antique brown but it is also available in white. [pb] [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
Lounging around [/head] [p]
This comfy willow chaise longue gives you the perfect excuse for relaxing and putting your feet up. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
Woven wicker [/head] [p]
Diamond patterned cane with cotton covered cushions makes for comfort on the patio. [/p] [/div3] [/div2] [div2] [head]
SUMMER COLOURS [/head] [head]
Look out for the wide range of painted wicker that's around.
Take your pick from pure classic white or go for bolder shades [/head] [div3] [head]
Sea view [/head] [p]
Inspired by the grand ocean liners of the 1930s, where similar pieces were a familiar sight in the saloons and lounges, these items are available in both country blue and antique almond.
The <head>chair</head> comes with a loose seat pad, the table has a 6mm glass top.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40202" docsrc="bnc_CK0_165">
<answer instance="chair.40202" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Obviously related to Margaret Dungarvan?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Her niece.&equo;
(God bless Margaret!)
&bquo;You knew her?&equo; [/p] [p]
He said he remembered her well, hoped she was flourishing, and had I not better get off to my supper? [/p] [p]
&bquo;Yes, Mr Leland.&equo;
I smiled.
&bquo;Thank you.&equo; [pb] [/p] [p]
Nine struck as I reached the dining-room.
A junior Night Sister frowned, but by some miracle the Night Super.
's <head>chair</head> was still empty.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40204" docsrc="bnc_CJA_3902">
<answer instance="chair.40204" senseid="sedan_chair-0"/>
<context>
Tabitha swooped along after the bird, over rubble, through coulisses, under gantries of black bone where vast unknown machinery slept, covered in fawn dust.
In a scaly hollow a crowd of naked Perks fled squealing from the echo of their bounding feet.
By the light of their abandoned bonfire Tabitha checked her watch.
Of her twenty-four hours, rather less than two remained. [/p] [p]
At last they emerged and stood breathing hard in a vast open space, the roof dim and distant above their heads.
Some hundred metres ahead, the floor dropped away into an awesome chasm, spanned, way off on their left, by an ugly concrete bridge.
Across it taxis and scooters droned to and from the cluster of carbuncular hotels on the far side.
Facing the hotels, bulging out over the very brink of the abyss, someone had built a huge green dome.
Its forecourt was paved with hexagonal blocks.
Cars and sedan <head>chairs</head> were parked in tidy ranks. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40205" docsrc="bnc_B0U_948">
<answer instance="chair.40205" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;Frankfurt is my home,&equo; he said.
&bquo;I bring some presents: food,&equo; &mdash; his eyes twinkled &mdash; &bquo;and whisky.
English whisky.
Left behind with the washing on the Siegfried Line.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;But you said&hellip;&equo;
I understood completely.
&bquo;My God, you bloody swine and you made me carry&hellip;&equo; [/p] [p]
The Feldwebel waved impatiently to the man with the keys. [pb] [/p] [p]
&bquo;Komm,&equo; said the man roughly and pushed me out of the door. [/p] [p]
He led me into a corridor.
I was beginning to feel suspicious about my room, but when he opened a door with a key and turned on the light I saw a small clean room with a bed, a table and a <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40207" docsrc="bnc_BP8_1772">
<answer instance="chair.40207" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
The group had had numerous discussions about whether or not they should have a rotating chairperson, some people arguing fiercely that we shouldn't imitate male structures, that we were developing genuinely new ways of relating, conducting political discussions; we must all learn to be more sensitive, not interrupt each other, not talk for too long.
Everyone would nod.
Others in the group argued that up to a point all those things were right, but that often a subject was complex, often it could be constructive for everyone to have a chairperson who would guide discussion, not control it, who would be able to be supportive when someone talked too much or too little.
We should [pb] develop or modify existing structures as well as work out new ones.
Everyone would nod. [/p] [p]
The result was an uneasy compromise, in which for some meetings there would be a chairperson, in others not.
It depended on whether one of the pro-chairperson people suggested it.
Tonight, surprisingly, Annie thought, it was Rachel who said &bquo;Let's have a <head>chair</head> , eh? [/p] [sp] [spkr]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40208" docsrc="bnc_A61_922">
<answer instance="chair.40208" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
They looked at me apprehensively when I asked for a drink of cider or wine.
The woman was getting quite agitated, looking along the banks of the canal and exclaiming, &bquo;Ferm&eacute;, ferm&eacute;.&equo; [/p] [p]
The man standing behind her spoke as I was turning to walk away.
&bquo;You are Scottish?&equo; he said, &bquo;You were playing the [hi]cornemuse [/hi] on the approach to the bridge six days ago.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Yes,&equo; I replied, &bquo;You speak good English.&equo; [/p] [p]
He shrugged his shoulders, &bquo;At times I like to speak English, but not for a long time.
Come in and have a drink.&equo; [/p] [p]
They stood to the side as I entered then the woman showed me to a <head>chair</head> as the man brought two glasses and placed them on the table in front of me, then said very seriously, &bquo;This is my wife.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40210" docsrc="bnc_CA9_832">
<answer instance="chair.40210" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
He was working for his cousin in Sheffield market as an apprentice butcher, but had bought a trumpet and intended, one day, to become Louis Armstrong. [/p] [p]
His cousin knew of our predicament and had informed [pb] Malc's parents before we had a chance to break the news ourselves.
They were terrific &mdash; upset, but very sympathetic and his Mother said not to worry, if Pop threw me out she'd look after me.
We all took the short bus-ride to my Pop's house. [/p] [p]
I ran ahead.
I had to tell him the news myself [/p] [p]
&bquo;Hello Pop, Mr and Mrs Stringer are here to see you.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Oh?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Yes, I'm pregnant.&equo;
[hi](What sweet revenge.) [/hi] [/p] [p]
He fell into the <head>chair</head> as though he'd been hit with a medicine ball and said very little while Malc's parents discussed what we should do.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40211" docsrc="bnc_CEY_1222">
<answer instance="chair.40211" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
It seemed no time at all until the last model, wearing a mauve duchesse evening dress called &bquo;Tour d'Eiffel&equo;, had swished back through the gold curtain and Paul de Levanti&eacute;re was standing to acknowledge the enthusiastic applause. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Did you enjoy it, darling?&equo; asked Louise. [/p] [p]
&bquo;It was [hi]wonderful [/hi]!&equo;
Constance replied, her eyes shining with excitement. [/p] [p]
As she looked at her niece's radiant face, Louise felt sure that she had been right to approach Monsieur de Levanti&eacute;re. [/p] [p]
Three days later Constance was back in the salon with Louise, gazing in amazement at the transformation.
The elegant <head>chairs</head> and sofas had gone; there was not a flower to be seen and, where the gold curtain had been, there was a very ordinary and rather battered door, through which they were taken to Paul de Levanti&eacute;re's tiny, chaotic office. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40213" docsrc="bnc_CJK_1416">
<answer instance="chair.40213" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
[hi]Local Activities [/hi]: walks, fishing, gliding, hang-gliding, golf, swimming, indoor skiing, sailing, squash, tennis, bowls, horse-riding. [pb] [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Sunray Hotel [/head] [head]  [gap] [gap] [gap] [/head] [p]
In a town with over 200,000 holiday beds, this small unprepossessing semi-detached house lying in a quiet residential area has a reputation for being special &mdash; in fact for being one of the best small hotels in the resort.
What makes it so is the extraordinary care and attention given to every guest by its owner, Jean Dodgson.
No one escapes from her warm welcome.
The nine bedrooms have en suite facilities and colour TV.
There is a comfortable lounge.
Jean provides a very good five-course evening meal and will cater for special diets on request.
There is a small front garden with a swing <head>chair</head> , deck chairs and parasols. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40214" docsrc="bnc_CKX_1647">
<answer instance="chair.40214" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
One of the most important works by Motherwell to appear since his death, &bquo;Elegy to the Spanish Republic&equo; is estimated at &dollar;600,000&ndash;800,000 (&pound;400,000&ndash;533,000). [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Chippendale? [/head] [p]
London, Sotheby's, 7 May.
A lacquer-mounted serpentine commode chest dated around 1775 and attributed to Thomas Chippendale will provide the focus of this sale of English furniture.
The top is decorated with a mountainous landscape and the panelled doors in Chinoiserie designs.
The incorporation of Chinese lacquer pieces into the best English craftsmanship of the period clearly shows the continued interest in the Orient during these decades (est. &pound;150,000&ndash;200,000; &dollar;225,000&ndash;300,000).
A set of fourteen late George II mahogany <head>chairs</head> for Hinton House may realise &pound;250,000&ndash;300,000 (&dollar;375,000&ndash;450,000). [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40216" docsrc="bnc_CGT_462">
<answer instance="chair.40216" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Where are her pants?
I wonder if they're in the basket?
Oh, there they are.&equo;
This could be the observation of a mother about her daughter's play which does not demand any interaction from the child but is verbalizing what perhaps the child is thinking.
Another example could be: &bquo;That's a big car.
It goes brmm, brmm all over the room.
It's going very fast, over the carpet, on to the chair, and now on to the table.
Oh, dear it's fallen over.
Let's pick it up.
I wonder where it is going now?
Under the <head>chair</head> , [pb] ooh, that's a bit low, you can't get under there.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40217" docsrc="bnc_CRR_63">
<answer instance="chair.40217" senseid="chair-1"/>
<context>
In an age in which almost every worthwhile appointment likely to attract a gentleman could be obtained only through political interest, true independence was a luxury for a few wealthy bachelors without close kin, and politicians were expected to satisfy their constituents' needs.
Two bribe-hungry burgesses of North Berwick explained matters quite plainly in a letter which they wrote to Henry Erskine when the latter became Lord Advocate of Scotland in 1806.
They advised [gap] [pb] [/p] [p]
Henry Erskine's correspondents could have added to their list several other varieties of revenue officer, judicial appointments, university <head>chairs</head> , first appointments in the army or the navy, and where these could be obtained without purchase, advancement in rank in these services, Indian and colonial patronage, and much more.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40220" docsrc="bnc_AN8_1930">
<answer instance="chair.40220" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;No, of course it isn't.
But you've got to convince everybody, not [pb] just me and people like Bridges, people who've had a scientific training.
You're preaching to the converted in us, but you've got to get at everyone else.
So Mr. Kegan is right.
You'll [hi]have [/hi] to cooperate and answer their questions and explain.
Even if it wastes your time.
It won't really be wasting it, you know.
And I can hold things here, really I can.
The work will get done, even if you miss the doing of it.
And I know that's miserable for you, but what else can you do?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I seem to have been here so often before,&equo; Briant said heavily and moved wearily back to his <head>chair</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40221" docsrc="bnc_APP_1039">
<answer instance="chair.40221" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The DHAC had proved that new and imaginative methods of protest could make an impact on the Unionist administration at the Guildhall, but for most opponents of the Unionist Party in Derry this was a reason for achieving a greater degree of anti-Unionist unity in order to press home their advantage, not to become equally [pb] hostile to the Nationalist Party.
This was shown by the first major DHAC protest following the 5 October 1968 demonstration, when the committee supported an NILP delegation to the council on the housing issue.
There was uproar when the council refused to hear the delegation and the meeting was adjourned, the Unionists withdrawing but the Nationalists remaining in their seats.
Eamonn Melaugh went over to the mayor's chair and sat down.
He shouted to the protesters: &bquo;I ask you citizens of Derry, do you approve of a crash programme of 2,000 houses?&equo;
There were cries of &bquo;yes&equo;.
They also approved his call for an extension of the boundary and he commented, &bquo;This is democracy.&equo;
He then vacated the <head>chair</head> saying, &bquo;on second thoughts, it is not a decent chair for a man to be seen in&equo;.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40223" docsrc="bnc_CDM_206">
<answer instance="chair.40223" senseid="rocking_chair-0"/>
<context>
I literally jumped for joy when I heard that key turn in the lock and saw Mum and Mrs Taylor enter with another woman.
As they banged the door shut, the vibration set Granny's chair rocking and I put my hands over my eyes.
But Mum wouldn't have that. [pb] [/p] [p]
&bquo;Yer don't 'ave ter look if yer don't wanta,&equo; she said sharply, pulling them away. [/p] [p]
&bquo;We're gooin' ter tek 'er upstairs an' lay 'er out,&equo; she said. [/p] [p]
I felt safer now that they'd arrived and I was curious to see what she meant by &bquo;laying out&equo;.
So, avoiding Granny's staring eyes, I watched Mum, Mrs Taylor and the big-bosomed woman they called Aggie lift Granny with some effort out of her chair and up the creaky stairs.
I stood engrossed by this until I heard the rocking <head>chair</head> creak behind me, and at that I scampered up after them.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40224" docsrc="bnc_A0X_1192">
<answer instance="chair.40224" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
My own taste for formal furniture tends to fall between the &bquo;Arts and Crafts&equo; and &bquo;Modern&equo;, rather than &bquo;Repro&equo;, and yet looking at modern designs you see in exhibitions, I doubt their &bquo;long-sit&equo; comfort and, personally, I feel that the limits of acceptable elegance are frequently passed by many, in the cause of being different.
The demand for elegance carries with it the requirement to fit in with existing furniture and although talking points can be useful, a table surrounded by a set of such chairs could be a positive eyesore.
Talking to professional designer-producers confirms this point: people will stop to admire such designs, but many more &bquo;traditional&equo; products are purchased. [/p] [p]
So we can put some limits on the project: the <head>chairs</head> must be upholstered; modern in the simplicity of their lines but not &bquo;Cubist&equo; for want of a better term; easy on the eye and bottom; they should fit in with other existing furniture; and naturally should be of strong construction so that they will be heirloom quality. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40226" docsrc="bnc_CJG_1192">
<answer instance="chair.40226" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
This needs to be placed at the angle which gives the best support for the material being used in relation to the pupil's vision, and some initial experimenting with different angles of work may be needed in order to settle on this.
A desk with an adjustable sloping top is useful as it provides storage space too, but probably the most practical aid, especially as the pupil progresses into secondary school, is a light, portable reading stand that can be easily taken from room to room as required.
It will need to have a ledge to support the reading material and strong clamps to hold pages in place are useful.
The earlier a pupil is able to find and keep to a comfortable and efficient working position, the better. [/p] [p]
Another factor in the pupil's near environment that can affect the comfortable use of vision for work is the &bquo;fit&equo; of the furniture (<head>chair</head> , desk, table) in terms of individual requirements.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.40227" docsrc="bnc_C9X_83">
<answer instance="chair.40227" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Soon they plan to revamp the kitchen and perhaps invest in some unusual modern furniture, which is a particular passion of Bill's.
But the traditional family feeling will never change.
It's very likely that the Petites and their children's children could be living here for another 100 years. [ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][pb] [gap] [pb] [gap] [pb] [gap] [pb] [ptr][pb] [/p] [caption]
Main picture: Decorations in shades of orange and gold bring the living room to life for Christmas. [/caption] [caption]
Above: The family open their presents by the magnificent marble fireplace in the living room [/caption] [caption]
Far left: Build in 1850, the house had changed very little in 130 years [/caption] [caption]
Main Picture: The grand piano lends a dramatic air to the dining room which has quite a modern look with its black <head>chairs</head> and stark glass table.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.30001" docsrc="wsj_2428.mrg_17">
<answer instance="chair.30001" senseid="U"/>
<answer instance="chair.30001" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
The shaky market received its biggest jolt last month from Campeau Corp.,
which created its U.S. retailing empire with junk financing.  Campeau
developed a cash squeeze that caused it to be tardy on some interest
payments and to put its prestigious Bloomingdales department-store chain up
for sale.  Now, dozens of corporations, including Ethan Allen, TW Services
and York International, that are counting on at least $7 billion of
scheduled new junk financings to keep their highly leveraged takeovers and
buy-outs afloat, may never get the money.  ``The music has stopped playing,''
says Michael Harkins, a principal in the investment firm of Levy Harkins.
``You 've either got a <head>chair</head> or you do n't.''
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.30002" docsrc="wsj_0569.mrg_38">
<answer instance="chair.30002" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Is that the forecast?'' Mr. O'Brien asks, trying to pin down the economist.
He does n't fully succeed, although Mr. Straszheim lists an array of
interest-rate scenarios.  In a chilly conference room at Alliance Capital
Management in Minneapolis, in contrast, the firm's money managers seem
ready to pin Mr. Straszheim to the wall.  Alfred Harrison, the manager,
shoves Mr. Straszheim's handout back at him: ``Do we want to go through this?
Or can we ask you why you changed your forecast just when it's about to be
right?'' Swiveling in his <head>chair</head>, Mr. Straszheim replies
that the new outlook, though still weak, does n't justify calling a
recession right now.  ``
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.30004" docsrc="wsj_0413.mrg_40">
<answer instance="chair.30004" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Mrs. Stinnett says she never believed in ghosts before, but lately her
vacuum cleaner turned itself on, a telephone flew off its stand, doors
slammed inexplicably, and she heard footsteps in her empty kitchen.  ``I
was doing the laundry and nearly broke my neck running upstairs to see who
was there, and it was nobody,'' she says, eyes wide at the recollection.
Mr. Baker hears her out, pokes around a bit, asks a few questions and
proposes some explanations.  Of the self-starting vacuum cleaner, he says:
``Could be Cuddles, -LCB- Mrs. Stinnett's dog -RCB-.'' The flying telephone:
``You tangle the base cord around a <head>chair</head> leg, and the
receiver does seem to fly off.''
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.30005" docsrc="wsj_2161.mrg_51">
<answer instance="chair.30005" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Elisa Byler, a St. Louis masseuse, won over officials at Emerson Electric
Co., a maker of electrical and electronic equipment, by providing documents
and other articles trumpeting the therapeutic benefits of massage.  She
notes that she also stresses professionalism during her weekly visits.  ``I
pull my hair back, wear a little makeup and look corporate,'' says Ms. Byler,
who has been visiting Emerson since January.  ``If I go in there as I
normally dress, they 'd ask, ` Who is this hippie?  ''' The self-proclaimed
father of on-site massage is David Palmer, a 41-year-old San Francisco
masseur whose mission is to save the touch-starved masses.  To help do this,
Mr. Palmer developed a portable massage <head>chair</head> three
years ago that he hopes will bring ``structured touching'' into mainstream
America.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.30008" docsrc="wsj_2161.mrg_56">
<answer instance="chair.30008" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
To help do this, Mr. Palmer developed a portable massage chair three years
ago that he hopes will bring ``structured touching'' into mainstream America.
``The culture is not ready to take off its clothes, lie down and be touched
for an hour for $45,'' he says.  ``The idea is to keep the clothes on and
to keep people seated.  The chair is a way to package massage.'' Sitting in
one of Mr. Palmer's chairs, which cost $425 and have since been copied by
others, is a bit like straddling a recliner.  Customers lean forward, rest
their knees on side supports and bury their face in padding on the back of
the <head>chair</head>.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.30009" docsrc="wsj_2161.mrg_1">
<answer instance="chair.30009" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Officials at Options Clearing Corp., which processes all options trades for
U.S. exchanges, said that the $50 million guarantee was unprecedented, but
was necessary to help insure the integrity of the options markets.  ``It
was an extraordinary situation that needed extraordinary steps,'' said Paul
Stevens, OCC president and chief operating officer.  Mr. Stevens declined
to give the specific contributions to the $50 million guarantee from each
participant.  But CBOE and Amex officials said that Options Clearing Corp.
contributed $20 million to the guarantee, the CBOE put up $8 million, the
Amex added $4 million and $18 million came from Mr. Fossett's own assets.
Mr. Fossett could n't be reached to comment.  Debora Foster takes off her
necklace, settles herself on a padded <head>chair</head> and gently
leans forward.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.30011" docsrc="wsj_0267.mrg_63">
<answer instance="chair.30011" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
And no one with a complaint about the judge would allow his name to be
printed.  ``I do n't have anything much to say, and I think that's what you
're going to find from everyone else you talk to up here,'' says local
attorney Edward F. Peduzzi.  Says another lawyer: ``The practice of law is
a matter of biting one's lip when you live in a small community.  One had
best not dance on top of a coffin until the lid is sealed tightly shut.''
The judge was considered imperious, abrasive and ambitious, those who
practiced before him say.  He sipped tea sweetened with honey from his
high-backed leather <head>chair</head> at his bench, while scribbling
notes ordering spectators to stop whispering or to take off their hats in
his courtroom.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="chair.30012" docsrc="wsj_2161.mrg_40">
<answer instance="chair.30012" senseid="chair-0"/>
<context>
Mr. Soule says his only beef was that the massages were being given in a
company conference room; the department's supervised health facility would
have been fine.  ``In my view, -LCB- massages -RCB- should be managed with
an appropriate mixture of males and females around,'' he says.  Given such
attitudes, some corporate masseurs prefer to go about their business quietly.
Russell Borner of Park Ridge, N.J., says he has been working for the past
year at a huge chemical and manufacturing concern in New York --
unbeknownst to the company's executives.  He visits the same department
every two or three weeks.  His massage <head>chair</head> is kept in
a closet, and a secretary escorts him past security.
</context>
</instance>

</lexelt>



</corpus>