<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1" ?>
<!DOCTYPE corpus SYSTEM
  "lexical-sample.dtd">
  <corpus lang='english'>
    <lexelt item="xD" >
       <instance id="day.40002" docsrc="bnc_CGJ_861">
<answer instance="day.40002" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Rounding-off an incredible period in the Museum's history, Pat Twite presented Roger Bryan on behalf of all at NAM with the 1990 Twite Award on September 11.
By chance, the Museum was also acting as host to a large delegation of Mayors and Councillors from the surrounding area and it is hoped that the significance of the presentation rubbed-off on them.
Through the display hangar, NAM has become not just a local attraction and amenity, but has developed into a regional, if not national, venue. [/p] [p]
While the hangar has clearly attracted much of the limelight during the last couple of years, NAM have been undertaking a programme of conservation on their larger airframes.
One project that was underway on the <head>day</head> of the trophy presentation was the awesome task of repainting Vulcan B.2 XM594.
</context>
</instance>
        <instance id="day.40002" docsrc="bnc_CGJ_861">
<answer instance="day.40002" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Rounding-off an incredible period in the Museum's history, Pat Twite presented Roger Bryan on behalf of all at NAM with the 1990 Twite Award on September 11.
By chance, the Museum was also acting as host to a large delegation of Mayors and Councillors from the surrounding area and it is hoped that the significance of the presentation rubbed-off on them.
Through the display hangar, NAM has become not just a local attraction and amenity, but has developed into a regional, if not national, venue. [/p] [p]
While the hangar has clearly attracted much of the limelight during the last couple of years, NAM have been undertaking a programme of conservation on their larger airframes.
One project that was underway on the <head>day</head> of the trophy presentation was the awesome task of repainting Vulcan B.2 XM594.
</context>
</instance>
    </lexelt>

  <lexelt item="day.n">

<instance id="day.40002" docsrc="bnc_CGJ_861">
<answer instance="day.40002" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Rounding-off an incredible period in the Museum's history, Pat Twite presented Roger Bryan on behalf of all at NAM with the 1990 Twite Award on September 11.
By chance, the Museum was also acting as host to a large delegation of Mayors and Councillors from the surrounding area and it is hoped that the significance of the presentation rubbed-off on them.
Through the display hangar, NAM has become not just a local attraction and amenity, but has developed into a regional, if not national, venue. [/p] [p]
While the hangar has clearly attracted much of the limelight during the last couple of years, NAM have been undertaking a programme of conservation on their larger airframes.
One project that was underway on the <head>day</head> of the trophy presentation was the awesome task of repainting Vulcan B.2 XM594.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40003" docsrc="bnc_CH5_4313">
<answer instance="day.40003" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
AT first he failed to notice we had stopped.
Then he came roaring back down the road in a cold fury. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I will kill you if you don't behave,&equo; he said flatly. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I could kill you all.
It means nothing.&equo; [/p] [p]
Life is cheap here and people want to escape.
But Britain refuses to take them. [ptr][ptr][ptr][ptr][/p] [caption]
TOGETHER AGAIN Sead Hukanovic, weakened by the hell at Omarska, desperately clings on to his brother Nijaz at the camp yesterday [/caption] [caption]
TRAGIC Outcast mum Sabira Radic hugs daughter Elma on the road to the camp [/caption] [caption]
MISERY Refugees queue for the meagre rations at the camp in Trnopolje yesterday [/caption] [caption]
SCRAPS: Paltry bowl of rations dished out by Serbs to feed two men for a <head>day</head> [/caption] [/div1] [div1] [head]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40006" docsrc="bnc_C92_1185">
<answer instance="day.40006" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
A stock of &bquo;standard&equo; components will not help when an unusual item is &bquo;out of stock&equo;, and with these you just have to accept that you are at the mercy of the suppliers. [/p] [p]
On the other hand, a stock of components can avoid the frustration of being held up on a project because a mundane integrated circuit is temporarily unavailable, or because you have managed to break one lead away from a 100m capacitor.
You need to be sensible about buying components for stock though, or you will probably just waste a lot of money. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
JUNK BOX [/head] [p]
The old approach to the problem was to raid discarded or inexpensive pieces of surplus equipment for any components that could be removed intact.
These went into what was known as the &bquo;junk box&equo;.
The &bquo;junk box&equo; approach is a less practical proposition these <head>days</head> , although there are plenty of surplus printed circuit boards etc. available.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40007" docsrc="bnc_CKA_1359">
<answer instance="day.40007" senseid="U"/>
<answer instance="day.40007" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Transvaal, who had beaten [hi]Western Province [/hi] the week before, bounced back from the Baa-Baas defeat with a win against [hi]Free State [/hi] the week after.
Pieter Hendriks scored a marvellous kick and chase try and one of the Free State stars was Hendrik Truter who last season played for Transvaal.
He felt, with some justification, that he had received from Transvaal a raw deal for his loyalty, and he moved to Bloemfontein.
A senior Transvaal player, who wished to remain anonymous, indicated that the burly 6ft 5ins fullback will be sorely missed. [/p] [p]
The Free State front row was also impressive and it you can imagine three Mighty Mouse McLauchlans, well then you have them.
The two Bester brothers, Piet and Andr&eacute; along with Johan Styger, prove week in week out that technique and timing can match size and bulk any <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40010" docsrc="bnc_CE9_155">
<answer instance="day.40010" senseid="time_of_day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40010" senseid="U"/>
<context>
D. K. McKenzie remembers a chilling story told by his uncle, Tom Ackroyd, who, from the time he left school in 1925, worked for the railway. [/p] [p]
In 1935 Ackroyd was put in charge of Entwhistle Halt on the Darwen-Bolton line.
There was nothing special about the halt: it had a signal cabin, about a dozen levers, and a pair of gates to allow carts to cross to the farms scattered across the moors.
Apart from the occasional passenger, the main traffic was milk chums en route to the dairy and dye wagons from Preston.
The sidings were situated about half a mile away and there was a water-tower nearby.
Ackroyd enjoyed a quiet bachelor life and lived in a small house by the crossing. [/p] [p]
Ackroyd's strange experience began one day as he looked out from his lonely signal box.
He knew most of the men who used the line and passed the time of <head>day</head> with them.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40011" docsrc="bnc_AS3_939">
<answer instance="day.40011" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
The first part of the walk kicks off up a private road gliding beneath a fabulous railway viaduct, the very one from which I had gazed in my bike-less train down the length of Loch Shiel for the first time some ten years earlier.
There is a package holiday that runs steam trains up and down the line during the summer, carrying rich tourists dressed in dinner-jackets and gowns, who scowl sternly from their carriage windows when the train is stranded at obscure little Scottish stations.
Dozens of people with rucksacks glare back at them from the platform as they wait for their substandard &bquo;Sprinter&equo; to turn up; wet, cold and miserable perhaps, but at least secure in the knowledge that they will eventually travel through the same scenery without parting with their life savings.
As we passed under the viaduct that <head>day</head> , one of these steam trains passed overhead, in a cloud of champagne and Chanel fumes.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40013" docsrc="bnc_CEV_307">
<answer instance="day.40013" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40013" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Lest we're parted by the crowd, [/l] [l]
That sweeps up on to the deck, [/l] [l]
To glimpse sea and low slung cloud. [/l] [l]
Come, stand by me my darling, [/l] [l]
That I ever keep you near, [/l] [l]
I'm moved to see your loveliness, [/l] [l]
Your voice I need to hear. [/l] [l]
Come, lean on me my darling, [/l] [l]
As the ship slides smooth away, [/l] [l]
So that we may be together, [/l] [l]
And think over this perfect <head>day</head> . [/l] [l]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40014" docsrc="bnc_AC2_1046">
<answer instance="day.40014" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
When asked by an interviewer if he was pleased with the performance of the British plants, the President had replied that although past performance had been bad by traditional British standards, he was now happy to say that in recent months a marked improvement had taken place.
This enabled him to look forward with confidence to continued improvements which would put the British plants back at the top of the performance league, where they used to be, and where they belonged. [/p] [p]
Clasper had other ideas, however.
On the <head>day</head> that Don Peters was on his feet at the EPC meeting, fighting for the survival of the British Vehicle Division and the jobs of the fifty thousand people it employed, Fred Clasper was setting in motion the third and final stage of his scheme to sabotage any possible chance of the company's recovery. [pb] [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40016" docsrc="bnc_CL2_1584">
<answer instance="day.40016" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Her background was a few rungs up from the Jenkinses and that elementary social fact helped to give her a poise in the face of his ever-increasing sureness.
Many found her consistent equilibrium the most surprising of her many qualities.
She came to England to stay with a sister, went to acting school in London and through a teacher who knew how to persuade Emlyn Williams, was all but smuggled into [hi]The Last Days of Dolwyn [/hi] as the sixth girl extra &bquo;when only five had been budgeted for.
But then I thought &mdash; Alexander Korda can afford six,&equo; said Emlyn, doing a favour for the female line of the Tafia. [/p] [p]
She was petite, going silver-haired, vivacious, bright, and willing to take Richard on trust.
After the first date he said he would phone her: she waited by the telephone until after midnight.
No call.
Next <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40017" docsrc="bnc_A7H_413">
<answer instance="day.40017" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
She may have been just twenty years old, and secretly terrified, but she would only have one wedding in her life, and she was determined to make it her own.
And for all the pomp and ceremony, for all the formality and precision, the security and the months of planning, for all the cameras and lights, it was still a touching and surprisingly intimate affair. [/p] [p]
The couple were determined their honeymoon should be too, despite equal determination on behalf of the world's press to keep them company.
After a few days at Broadlands, they flew to Gibraltar to join the Royal Yacht [hi]Britannia [/hi] for a two-week cruise in and around the Mediterranean.
For two weeks the press flew from one Greek island to another, like migrating birds, at the slightest rumour.
They set to sea in boats and cruisers; one newspaper even hired a Lear jet, which flew over the area <head>day</head> after day.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40020" docsrc="bnc_CCC_805">
<answer instance="day.40020" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
It then continued: [hi]Mr. Callaghan's statement is not the end of the story.  [/hi]
[hi]Material now with [/hi] The Observer &mdash; [hi]which we are still checking &mdash; suggests that there may well have been a group hostile to Sir Harold Wilson (and hostile to leaders of the Liberal party) extending far beyond a &bquo;faction of MI5' [/hi]. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Whether Sir Harold himself appreciated the full ramifications of the matter is doubtful. [/p] [p]
four days before [hi]The Observer [/hi] published this statement by Wilson, Chapman Pincher wrote in the [hi]Daily Express [/hi] that he had a copy of a DI6 report, detailing the heavy surveillance of Harold Wilson prior to the general election of February 1974.
It was several pages long and marked &bquo;Top Secret for Addressee Only&equo;.
Next <head>day</head> , he gave more information.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40023" docsrc="bnc_A6R_1640">
<answer instance="day.40023" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Others: Andy Harvey (Legionaires) 4&ndash;0&ndash;8; Tim Harrison (Leeds Anglers World) 3&ndash;1&ndash;8.
Teams: Leeds Anglers World 10&ndash;7&ndash;0; Legionaires 10&ndash;6&ndash;0; South Bank 9&ndash;14&ndash;0.
League: Mitre Pets 55; Legionaires 53; South Bank 52. [/p] [p]
LONDON AA.
The final round on the Grand Union Canal at Broadmead Bridge was fished by 26 competiors who had to smash through ice up to six inches thick.
Peter Vasey (Trev's Browning) had three roach on pole and bread punch for victory with 0&ndash;4&ndash;0.
Others: Steve Davis (A1 Shimano) 0&ndash;3&ndash;0; Derek Seymour (Trev's Browning) 0&ndash;2&ndash;12.
A1 Shimano's Bill Bullock won the league with 0&ndash;2&ndash;8, enough for fourth on the <head>day</head> to bring his earnings from the series to almost &pound;500. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40027" docsrc="bnc_BP7_2183">
<answer instance="day.40027" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
He had a son, running the family business for him. [/p] [p]
He sucked greedily on the cigar, like a heart patient needing oxygen.
Ah, that Jack.
What a problem he was.
A chip off the old block he was not.
Bright, yes.
Motivated, yes.
But tough?
Dream on.
Young Jack thought he was hard, thought that having a few blondes and getting a few legs broken made you a man, but underneath it all he was soft, a little boy.
If Jack had had to protect his pitch at Dagenham and White City in the <head>days</head> when men were men, he wouldn't have survived until the third race. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40028" docsrc="bnc_B2U_816">
<answer instance="day.40028" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
2 Take the old till roll out carefully (make sure it is not damaged, thereby losing valuable information).
3 Sign and date the end of the till roll.
4 Place the new roll on the reel/spindle, feed the end through into the receipt-holder section and make sure that it will run smoothly.
5 Sign and date the start of the roll.
6 Close and lock the till [pb] [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
Cashing up [/head] [p]
At the end of a day's trading, the retailer needs to know exactly how much money he has taken.
Each assistant/checkout operator has to cash up the contents of the till. [/p] [p]
In large stores and supermarkets, &bquo;pick-ups&equo; are made throughout the day, so that the tills do not become overloaded with money &mdash; and possibly a security hazard.
This means that the final cashing up will not include all the <head>day</head> 's takings. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40030" docsrc="bnc_BM5_1353">
<answer instance="day.40030" senseid="day-4"/>
<context>
No one with cash and no part-exchange should consider buying used Sierras from franchised dealers, who invariably ask unrealistic prices.
The private columns are thick with them, but buyers should look out for complete service histories as many are clocked. [/p] [p]
Darren's car was reasonably priced when bought in July 1991 and evidently in clean and original condition.
Although he has added 40,000 to its mileage, this will not deter potential buyers if the condition has remained good and &pound;1750 should be easy to get. [pb] [pb] [pb] [/p] [/div2] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Where the ghosts of racing roam [/head] [caption]
Cars no longer race at Brooklands, but memories of its glory days in the '20s and '30s live on, says Mike McCarthy [/caption] [caption]
Restored Brooklands clubhouse today; before World War II, race <head>days</head> pulled big crowds (inset) [/caption] [pb] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40032" docsrc="bnc_AAK_108">
<answer instance="day.40032" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Many Romanians are subsidised by Western currencies brought into the country by relatives on holiday from jobs abroad.
On a back street, just off Bucharest's Bulevardul General Magheru, a spiral stone staircase winds up to the cramped first floor offices of Comturist. [/p] [p]
Here, in an aquarium light, men and women crouch in rows of wooden tip-up seats, peering at half a dozen shuttered doorways.
One of these is labelled &bquo;Iran (Irak)&equo;. [/p] [p]
Every ten minutes an austere blouse steps into the gloom and calls a croucher forward to the cashier's hatch.
Credit notes bought with francs, marks and dollars win relatives access to government caches of whisky, butter, chocolate and ground coffee.
Otherwise, rationing restricts Romanians to one kilo of meat a month and half a loaf of bread a <head>day</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40034" docsrc="bnc_CBY_505">
<answer instance="day.40034" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Although the merger gave them the chance to start Andy claims they could &bquo;never&equo; have done it without it &mdash; the recession has taken clients and exposure has been &bquo;painful&equo; on occasions.
But he argues, they have survived.
&bquo;After two and a half years, we are still here.
We wouldn't still be doing it if we didn't feel that it was creating enough profit in the meantime, and looked like it could create more as it went along.&equo; [ptr][ptr][ptr][pb] [ptr][ptr][/p] [caption]
Pollock: Surviving [/caption] [caption]
No free wheeling.
Richard Parkyn, a chartered accountant from Tiverton in Devon who has suffered from diabetes since childhood, has successfully completed a 750-mile bike ride from John O'Groats to the Royal Devon and Exeter Hospital in just 10 <head>days</head> despite having his bike stolen in Kidderminster and suffering from increasingly sore knees.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40035" docsrc="bnc_C9S_114">
<answer instance="day.40035" senseid="early_days-0"/>
<context>
It is arguable that the increased visibility of gay men in television drama was a reflection of their dramatic potential as &bquo;dangerous&equo; characters, and their function in raising discussion of AIDS. [/p] [p]
Television's response to the struggle around Clause 28 reflected the status the campaign achieved in the political arena.
The involvement of influential people, including many heterosexuals, in all areas of public life; the high visibility of figures such as Ian McKellen and Michael Cashman; the size and nature of the demonstrations and direct actions made it great television material.
For probably the first time since 1967, homosexuality was at the forefront of public debate, resulting in moments of real visibility and intervention.
I recall one evening, during the early <head>days</head> of the campaign, when on three occasions on different channels (an arts programme and two awards ceremonies) public statements were made against the Clause.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40037" docsrc="bnc_BPC_852">
<answer instance="day.40037" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Further exhibits depict the opening of the West, Whaling (with a Captain's Cabin reproduced from the last of the great Yankee whalers), Textiles (with a fine collection of quilts and hooked rugs), Pewter, Glass and Silver.
The gardens include an American Arboretum, and a semi-circular gallery presenting the vigorous forms and primitive designs of American Folk Art.
There is also an 1830 Conestoga wagon, an observation platform of a railroad car, and a replica of a Tepee. [ptr][gap] [/p] [caption]
A new gallery contains a reference library covering American history and the decorative arts, a map relating to the discovery of the New World, and a hall showing special exhibitions. [/caption] [p]
1992 General Information [/p] [p]
The Museum is open daily from 2&mdash;5 p.m. (except Mondays) from the 28th March to 1st November, Sunday and Monday of Bank Holiday weekends 11 a.m. &mdash; 5 p.m.
Gardens open 1&mdash;6 p.m. every <head>day</head> (except Monday).
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40038" docsrc="bnc_ABU_476">
<answer instance="day.40038" senseid="early_days-0"/>
<context>
My Minister of State, Hugh Rossi, had announced the change during discussion of a social security bill in standing committee on Tuesday morning change is still unjustly called &bquo;the Rossi Index&equo; &mdash; and the Opposition had protested strongly.
At Prime Minister's Questions in the afternoon Margaret Thatcher was challenged by a Labour MP, Jeff Rooker, on the change and although she managed to deflect the question it was clear she had not been briefed.
It was entirely our responsibility and that evening to well past midnight Leon and I took her through the changes until she was satisfied that she knew the policy thoroughly.
We only broke for the night [pb] on the promise of a further meeting next day together with social security officials.
By the next Prime Minister's Questions on Thursday she knew the policy rather better than we did. [/p] [p]
The feature that came through most clearly, however, even in those early <head>days</head> of government, was Margaret Thatcher's stamina.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40040" docsrc="bnc_CEK_7619">
<answer instance="day.40040" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
MANCHESTER: Today, Britannia Hotel, Portland St BIRMINGHAM: Wednesday, Nov 18, Hyatt Regency, Bridge Street SOUTHAMPTON: Thursday, Nov 19, Southampton Moat House, Highfield Lane BRISTOL: Friday, Nov 20, Bristol Moat House, Victoria St LONDON: Saturday, Nov 21, Drury Lane Moat House, 10 Drury Lane, London WC2 [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Secrets of a beauty scout [/head] [head]
Tim Ewbank [/head] [p]
HUNDREDS of people were checking in at New York's JFK airport, but one face stood out from the crowd.
It belonged to a 14-year-old schoolgirl with the looks of an angel. [/p] [p]
By chance, one of the world's top fashion talent-spotters happened to be booking in for that same flight.
Once they were airborne, the girl was approached. [/p] [p]
The next <head>day</head> she was signed up to the top model agency Storm &mdash; and the day after that she started her modelling career. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40041" docsrc="bnc_CRK_1431">
<answer instance="day.40041" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Catholic biblical scholars, theologians and many active lay groups had good reasons to be grateful.
Among the &bquo;observers&equo;, the Orthodox now had something more like their own teaching on Tradition than from any previous Western Council.
Anglicans and Protestants now not only heard the first systematic teaching on the word of God in the Church ever formulated by a Catholic Council (for Trent had only dealt with particular points at issue with the Reformers), but also admired it.
Most remarkable of all, Karl, Barth, having been unable to serve as an observer, later published his reflections (1967, 1969), asking himself such questions as &bquo;How would things look if Rome (without ceasing to be Rome) were one <head>day</head> simply to overtake us and place us in the shadows, so far as the renewing of the church through the Word and Spirit of the gospel is concerned?&equo;
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40044" docsrc="bnc_AT7_1212">
<answer instance="day.40044" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
But if it had meant working for two months she would have said immediately, as she did now, &bquo;I'll have it.&equo; [/p] [p]
The sisters were laughing quite gaily.
&bquo;I knew you would.
I knew you would.&equo;
Florence was moving from one foot to the other as she helped her off with the coat.
But it was Belle who said, &bquo;What about the hats?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Yes, what about them?&equo;
Her voice was full of laughter.
&bquo;I'll take them both, but I want discount for buying two at once, mind.&equo; [/p] [p]
The laughter filled the room, it filled the shop, it even penetrated the wall into the tobacconist's shop and made Arthur Conway wonder if the three old girls next door had gone barmy or taken to the bottle early in the <head>day</head> , for it was said that they took wine with their dinner.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40046" docsrc="bnc_ALX_675">
<answer instance="day.40046" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
[pb] Howard later reported that the Nez Perce had &bquo;jammed their ponies through, up the rocks&hellip; and among the fallen trees, without attempting to cut a limb, leaving blood to mark their path; and abandoned animals with broken legs&hellip; or stretched dead by the wayside.&equo; [/p] [p]
The Nez Perce then descended the eastern Bitterroots into Montana on 25th July to find their path blocked by a crude stockade, subsequently dubbed &bquo;Fort Fizzle&equo;.
It was manned by thirty-five regulars under Captain C.C. Rawn summoned from Fort Missoula by Howard, plus 200 Montana volunteers and, to the Nez Perce's disgust, twenty Flathead Indians.
Joseph, Looking Glass and White Bird calmly approached the defenders under a white flag.
For three <head>days</head> they parleyed; Rawn demanding their surrender and the Nez Perce asking to be allowed into Montana in peace.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40049" docsrc="bnc_BPA_2480">
<answer instance="day.40049" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Under the duress of the moment, the act of crossing the threshold into this place had passed unnoticed. [/p] [p]
She raised her head and looked around.
The feet were by the door, small, ill-formed, like wax models of a child's that had passed through flame and were partially melted.
They would possess none of the inherent tactile and balancing powers of hers, or that creature outside. [/p] [p]
Nell raised her eyes and looked at the rest of the body; and caught her breath.
Her guess as to what it fundamentally was had been correct. [/p] [p]
As a doctor she'd seen others like it before.
So many times.
But never in the normal world [pb] &mdash; one nearly five feet tall. [/p] [p]
It was a human embryo of some forty <head>days</head> that had been somehow arrested, then grown to its own obscene maturity. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40050" docsrc="bnc_CHB_2476">
<answer instance="day.40050" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Could you find out what has become of SHELLEYAN ORPHAN?
Do they still exist or are &bquo;Helleborine&equo; and &bquo;Century Flower&equo; to be the only albums to mark their existence? [gap] [gap] [/p] [p]
&bull; The message is brief &mdash; Shelleyan Orphan are alive and well and still signed to Rough Trade, who, in mid-October, will be releasing an album that answers to the name of &bquo;Humroot&equo;.
Happy endings &mdash; you can't beat &bquo;em! [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
LIFE IS SWEET [/head] [p]
What's happened to RACHEL SWEET, once pride of Akron and a Stiff princess? [gap] [gap] [/p] [p]
&bull; These <head>days</head> she's pretty much engaged in an acting career, although she did turn up in John Waters' Hairspray in 1988 to render Barbara Lynn Ozen's title song, which duly appeared on the soundtrack album.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40053" docsrc="bnc_CRJ_1343">
<answer instance="day.40053" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Unfortunately it kept to the tops of the trees and didn't give me any chance of pictures. [/p] [p]
Much easier to photograph were the giant tortoises which were lumbering around like tanks in the undergrowth.
Some of them were said to be at least a hundred years old. [/p] [p]
Indian mynahs were common and we saw several strange-looking mutants with bald yellow heads.
Many sunbirds were flitting around, but I found them almost impossible to.
photograph with the equipment I had with me.
I also realised that forest photography was fraught with problems I hadn't even considered, and was not at all well-equipped to deal with. [/p] [p]
We flew back to Mahe and straight on to Praslin for a stay of a few <head>days</head> with the intention of taking day-trips to the smaller islands of Cousin and La Digue. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40055" docsrc="bnc_ASF_1433">
<answer instance="day.40055" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Associated with the four seasons, the weeks concerned begin, respectively, on St Lucy's Day (13 December), the First Sunday in Lent, Whitsunday, and Holy Cross Day (14 September).
Wednesdays, Fridays, and Saturdays in these weeks are the Ember Days.
Traditionally, these days were set apart for special prayer and fasting.
The following Sundays, for example Trinity Sunday, are the days specially fixed for the ordination of the clergy.
This ancient custom was finally established as a law of the Church, c.1085, by Pope Gregory VII. [/p] [p]
In England, belief in the uniformity of time was greatly influenced by [pb] the Puritans in their strong opposition to the practices of the Roman Church, in particular to the idea of special days in the ecclesiastical calendar.
Instead, the puritans advocated a regular routine of six <head>days</head> of work followed by a day of rest on the Sabbath, the famous Nonconformist ethic.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40058" docsrc="bnc_AMD_288">
<answer instance="day.40058" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
During the afternoon, our tour includes the Belvedere Palace, the Spanish Riding School within the grounds of the Hofburg Palace, the magnificent Opera House and St. Stephen's Cathedral.
As evening falls, there is an optional &bquo;Vienna by Night&equo; excursion.
This includes a traditional waltz dance show at the Cafe Hubner, followed by dinner in the famous wine village of Grinzing. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
DAY 4: Vienna [/head] [p]
Our morning tour of the city includes the Schonbrunn Palace.
Here, Marie Antoinette spent her childhood.
The afternoon is free for you to explore the delights of classical Vienna.
Alternatively, join us for an optional excursion to Vienna Woods, including a trip to the hunting lodge at Mayerling.
Our &bquo;Romantic Vienna&equo; evening excursion includes dinner in a typical restaurant, followed by a visit to the Prater Funfair with its big wheel. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
<head>DAY</head> 5: Vienna &mdash; Klagenfurt [/head] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40059" docsrc="bnc_A7W_113">
<answer instance="day.40059" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
In further pressure on East German leaders, academics at the influential Potsdam Academy sent an open letter to the central committee. [/p] [p]
It said that &bquo;the party's ignorant and arrogant behaviour over the years towards reserved and moderate criticism provoked the crisis.&equo; [/p] [p]
Meanwhile, there were signs last night that the Interior Ministry is about to recognise the country's biggest opposition group, New Forum.
For the first time last night, the official ADN news agency published a statement by the group, and a regional newspaper printed a &bquo;catalogue&equo; of New Forum demands yesterday. [/p] [p]
An East German parliamentary committee yesterday dismissed a draft travel law, saying that the 30 <head>days</head> ' travel to be granted a year in no way met people's expectations. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40062" docsrc="bnc_B2U_3209">
<answer instance="day.40062" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Anything that doesn't fit under another heading may be entered here, eg tea, biscuits, soap. [/p] [p]
Each analysis column is totalled separately.
All the analysis columns totalled together should agree with the figure in the TOTAL PAID column. [/p] [p]
The balance of petty cash is the difference between the total paid and the amount originally in the cash box (either the amount in the float, or the amount left after previous purchases).
The sum of money needed to restore the balance to the original amount is known as the imprest.
So, for example, [/p] [p]
You began the day with &pound;20 in the cash box. [/p] [p]
You spent &pound;2.06 on batteries, and &pound;1.71 on nine 19p stamps, so the TOTAL PAID was &pound;3.77. [/p] [p]
The imprest would also be &pound;3.77, so that the petty cash box contains &pound;20 for the next <head>day</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40065" docsrc="bnc_CBE_2411">
<answer instance="day.40065" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Mrs Clarke's brother, Norman Wilce, of Blyth, Northumberland, said yesterday: &bquo;We are all devastated.
They had gone out to Jamaica to start a new life.&equo; [/p] [p]
Police are questioning two men about the deaths. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Brit shot and left in swamp [/head] [p]
THE body of missing British businessman Howard Bates has been found in a Florida swamp. [/p] [p]
The killers shot Mr Bates in the back of the head and then dumped his body. [/p] [p]
Mr Bates, 43, of Hawkhurst, Kent, had flown to Miami in February last year to recover &pound;500,000 he had lost in a crooked business deal. [/p] [p]
After phoning his wife Sheila to tell her he had arrived safely, the computer boss was never seen again. [/p] [p]
The former RAF Hercules pilot and director of Hastings-based South East Computers, which has since folded, had planned to spend just two <head>days</head> in America. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40068" docsrc="bnc_CKL_143">
<answer instance="day.40068" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The crowd's response to his resilient 6&ndash;4, 7&ndash;5, 6&ndash;4 defeat of a totally overawed Sampras, in his David Cup debut, plus their even greater support as he and [corr] Forget [/corr] beat Ken Flach and the hapless Robert Seguso 6&ndash;1, 6&ndash;4, 4&ndash;6, 6&ndash;2, with flurries of brilliant winners in the doubles, must have gone a long way to at least dimming the memory of the cruel booing he received in 1988 when he struggled against Mats Wilander at Roland Garros in the final of the French Open and then again at Bercy the following [corr] November [/corr]. [/p] [p]
For Noah, it was a glorious culmination of dedication, endeavour and skill by what he called &bquo;&hellip; our whole tennis family&equo;. [/p] [p]
On choosing Leconte, which clearly caught the Americans by surprise, he said, &bquo;I decided ten <head>days</head> beforehand that he would play.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40069" docsrc="bnc_CD2_1285">
<answer instance="day.40069" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
My regard for your daughter has in no way diminished; I still want her for my wife.
You may not know, that I have had a book on philosophy published, and am working on another; my superiors at London University College are pleased with me, and promotion seems probable.
Will you not reconsider your former decision against us?
I will not interfere with Dinah's career on the stage; I have watched with great pleasure her performances as Lady Teazle and the other young lady in The Rivals; and I know, that [/p] [/quote] [pb] [quote] [p]
she owes a great deal, not only to her natural gifts, but to your tuition. [/p] [p]
I venture to ask, again, for your permission to pay her my addresses, and for marriage between us at an early date.
Yours devotedly, Paul Arkwright [/p] [/quote] [/p] [p]
He waited; the <head>days</head> lengthened into weeks; but no answer came.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40072" docsrc="bnc_CK0_2217">
<answer instance="day.40072" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Just a very nice man.&equo; [pb] [/p] [p]
&bquo;Well, then!
Oh, this is fab!
Bill'll be so thrilled!&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Hey, Jo!
This is a strict professional confidence!
No raising of false hopes.
This is just for the trade, still all very much in the air,&equo; she warned, &bquo;and not the trade at large.
You're not to say one word of any of this to your pals when you get back to Benedict's&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I won't, I promise.&equo; [/p] [p]
Before I left for London next <head>day</head> Margaret had the official confirmation of Dickie's examination results.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40074" docsrc="bnc_CA8_822">
<answer instance="day.40074" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Tillard and Royal Marine Lt. R.C. Hay, spotted another Z.506B as they were heading back towards the carrier, and attacked.
This too made a number of very steep turns and made for nearby cloud, though its port engine was believed damaged, and possibly the rear gunner killed.
The Fulmars continued searching for it and came across it (or the aircraft forced down by Taylor) floating on the sea; there were no signs of life.
At least one Z.506B from the 287 [hi]a [/hi] Squadriglia was reported lost. [pb] [gap] [ptr][/p] [caption]
Hurricane IIAs ranged on &bquo;Ark Royal&equo; ready for take-off on 3 April 1941. [/caption] [/div2] [div2] [head]
6&ndash;9/4/41 [/head] [p]
7/JG 26 had left Sicily for Taranto during this period, operating over southern Yugoslavia on 6th., the <head>day</head> of the invasion of that country.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40076" docsrc="bnc_CB2_778">
<answer instance="day.40076" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Here is the prop's definitive advice: &bquo;If you concentrate on the scrum and get your own put-in right without being shoved back and disrupted, everyone from the back row through to the threequarters can work off that.
But if the scrum is retreating no one can do anything.
It's not attractive or exciting but you have to do a basic job&equo;. [/p] [p]
Which might just be Alan Davies' test for 1992. [ptr][/p] [caption]
The steam and sweat of the scrum &mdash; the source of all endeavour!
The Welsh pack hold the French in Cardiff. [/caption] [div2] [head]
&bquo;PANTHER&equo; MARTIN'S PSYCHOLOGY SEMINAR [/head] [p]
Allan Martin's analysis of Wales' gradually improving forward play has a poignancy born of happy memories of the halcyon Seventies.
In those <head>days</head> the towering Aberavon lock was surrounded by quality and experience &mdash; a luxury successor generations have not had. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40077" docsrc="bnc_CH1_6594">
<answer instance="day.40077" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
But he can afford to joke because his pub has won the Egon Ronay Family Pub of the Year award. [/p] [p]
And it's not hard to see why. [/p] [p]
The hotel features special family rooms with fabulous views of Freshwater Bay, high chairs and kids' menus and there's full access to a wonderful garden. [/p] [p]
It even supplies baby listening devices. [/p] [p]
Perhaps the most impressive thing about the hotel is [corr] its [/corr] price. [/p] [p]
A room with en-suite bathroom, breakfast and dinner for a family of four &mdash; two adults and two children under five &mdash; will pay &pound;540 per week. [/p] [p]
Be sure to book in advance.
For full details, phone: (0983 730431). [/p] [div3] [head]
FACT BOX [/head] [p]
RED Funnel Ferries offer a <head>day</head> trip from Southampton to Cowes at &pound;28 for a car and four adults and a weekend special deal (after 6pm Fridays) of &pound;35.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40079" docsrc="bnc_CLD_2290">
<answer instance="day.40079" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
&bquo;Charming,&equo; the Trade Attach&eacute; sighed. [/p] [p]
&bquo;The Ambassador's daughter&hellip;&equo; the Charg&eacute; warned. [/p] [p]
&bquo;To see her is to start the day well,&equo; the Trade Attach&eacute; whispered. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Actually, my own day started pretty well,&equo; Pink said. [/p] [p]
Their eyes were on him, enquiring.
Yes, it was his day.
His day to talk, their day to listen. [/p] [p]
&bquo;You know what?
I walk into my dining room at 9.26 this morning, just to say my goodbyes to the little lady.
There's a woman sat there, in front of the fire, and she's stark naked.
That started my <head>day</head> well, I can tell you.&equo; [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40080" docsrc="bnc_CKD_236">
<answer instance="day.40080" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
&bquo;I'll come and do some measuring in the morning if that suits,&equo; she said.
Edward Morris smiled and nodded but it was the stranger who spoke. [/p] [p]
&bquo; [hi]I'll [/hi] definitely keep you in mind,&equo; he said and as his dark eyes met hers he seemed again to be laughing at her. [/p] [p]
Hari hurried back along the street anxious to get home, it was turning colder and the night was closing in.
She ran through the last few streets and saw with relief the familiar tall building rising against the night sky. [/p] [p]
She let herself into the kitchen and sank into a chair before the fire that urgently needed mending.
Hari rubbed her hand over her eyes, it had been a strange <head>day</head> , an eventful one in which she had quite clearly made an enemy [pb] but perhaps she had also made a friend of Edward Morris. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40083" docsrc="bnc_CBG_3927">
<answer instance="day.40083" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;That's rubbish,&equo; said the Danish defender.
&bquo;I think it's just an excuse.
I don't want other prospective buyers to think I'm not fit, because I am.
There is nothing wrong with my knee.&equo; [/p] [p]
City directors are understood to have pulled out for financial reasons. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Grim Graham [/head] [head]
Mike Walters [/head] [p]
GEORGE GRAHAM last night reluctantly accepted the role of Public Enemy No 1 as Arsenal turned to cup competitions as the salvation for their crumbling season. [/p] [p]
The Gunners' Premier League challenge is virtually a write-off after the Bank Holiday Monday defeat at Aston Villa made it seven games without a win. [/p] [p]
Now they face non-League Yeovil in Saturday's FA Cup third-round tie and a Coca-Cola Cup trip to Scarborough four <head>days</head> later. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40084" docsrc="bnc_CRC_1070">
<answer instance="day.40084" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
There, cars file in an endless stream into the Fort McDowell Recreation Centre, pride of the Fort McDowell tribe and salvation of its economy.
Those same elderly men and women, in pastel slacks and tennis shoes, who play the machines on the Fort McDowell reservation could also be losing their money at Turf Paradise, or at the greyhounds down the street. [/p] [p]
The Arizona legislature has just opened a special session to hear what the racetrack owners want.
In brief, they want slot machines of their own: 500 each for Turf Paradise and the Phoenix Greyhound Park, 250 each for the smaller tracks.
They reckon that if each machine brought in &dollar;192 a <head>day</head> (a claim the Las Vegas experts call unrealistic), and if the owners let the state pocket 90% of it, the state could earn more than &dollar;196m a year; and it could put the money towards education. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40086" docsrc="bnc_A52_554">
<answer instance="day.40086" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The German show, which offers substantial prize money, has attracted all four members of Britain's European Championship-winning team &mdash; Skelton, Joe Turi and the Whitaker brothers &mdash; as well as the reserve, David Broome. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Racing: Muddle concept gains ground: JOHN KARTER reports on plans for an all-weather race track coming to fruition [/head] [head]
By JOHN KARTER [/head] [p]
INSPIRATION may not spring readily from the prosaic-sounding north Midlands town of Southwell but it is the black stuff that dreams are made of in the eyes of Ron and Richard Muddle, the father and son team of racing entrepreneurs extraordinary. [/p] [p]
Southwell, as well as Lingfield, has been chosen as a first venue for all-weather racing in this country.
The opening meeting on the new surface at the Nottinghamshire track is on 1 November, two <head>days</head> after Lingfield stage their historic fixture. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40087" docsrc="bnc_CEU_2082">
<answer instance="day.40087" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40087" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
The land around the cloud towers was NASA's special country.
There were more animals there, and fewer humans.
It was a pretty good place for nomes.
Some of them believed that NASA had arranged it all for precisely that reason. [pb] [/p] [p]
Shrub sat back. [/p] [p]
&bquo;And does [hi]she [/hi] believe that?&equo; said Masklin.
He looked across the clearing to where Gurder and Topknot were arguing.
They couldn't understand what one another was saying, but they were still arguing. [/p] [p]
The Thing translated. [/p] [p]
Shrub laughed. [/p] [p]
&bquo;She says, <head>days</head> come, days go, who needs to believe anything?
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40089" docsrc="bnc_A6J_1078">
<answer instance="day.40089" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40089" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Just somehow, somewhere between the sweet shop and her house, between home and school, between tea-time and bath-time, she would lose concentration.
Something would attract her &mdash; a cloud, a flower, a fat lady on the street- and she would drift away from the track unthinkingly.
She knew that her grown-ups were frightened and she did not want them to be frightened, but she also knew that Fenna was a mightier protection than all their loving care could ever be.
She could walk safely in the forest of city streets and that no harm could touch her. [/p] [p]
She would just wander off; and then later she would come to, wondering where she was and remembering that they would be angry with her again.
That <head>day</head> she had wandered off between leaving her mother's kitchen and arriving in her grandmother's sitting-room.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40090" docsrc="bnc_BP0_352">
<answer instance="day.40090" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Primaflora, now he will blame you.&equo; [/p] [p]
She lifted her wet face, smiling at last.
She said, &bquo;What is this?
You want me to urge you to submit to him?
No.
All I am saying, my dear, is that you have another reason to end this war quickly.
When he is truly King, he will find other favourites, and no reason to keep you or me at his side.
But quickly!
Quickly!&equo; [/p] [p]
And he didn't tease her, or court her, or divert her, because what she had done was risk death, which was a thing better honoured by abstinence.
Only, next <head>day</head> , he rode to Famagusta with less than a light heart, to lead his men to the end of the game. [pb] [/p] [/div1] [div1] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40096" docsrc="bnc_CBF_6853">
<answer instance="day.40096" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The mothers did not suspect anything until Mrs Bursey noticed a name tag on her baby showed the mother as Marie Coyle. [/p] [p]
Mrs Bursey, a supermarket supervisor, added: &bquo;I feel sick all the time.
I've been so frightened of giving her all my love. [/p] [p]
&bquo;That Friday night we just sat there rocking her backwards and forwards and crying. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I keep looking at her face and saying &bquo;Are you mine?&equo;&equo;
The couple, who live in a village in the New Forest, took the baby back to the hospital because they feared they would become too fond of her, but have now taken her back. [/p] [p]
Twenty miles away on the outskirts of Southampton, former hospital worker Marie, 27, is suffering the same anguish. [/p] [p]
Sitting next to Peter, 24, she said she was unaware of the mix-up until there was a knock at the door after their first full <head>day</head> at home with Gemma. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40098" docsrc="bnc_A18_265">
<answer instance="day.40098" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
To stay with yellow for a moment: we noted a paring-down to the bare bones of yellow water in a yellow glass when Raskolnikov comes to after fainting on his first visit to the police station.
An opposite movement occurs with the elements of oppressive heat and smell on that same momentous fourth floor.
In the first draft of the scene neither are mentioned.
Then, as an afterthought, Dostoevsky wrote &bquo;the air was [pb] terribly stifling&equo; and &bquo;in addition, a smell of wet paint assailed the nostrils&equo;.
Our final text elaborates this to &bquo;the nauseating smell of fresh paint which had been mixed with rancid oil&equo;. [/p] [p]
Rancid oil is simply right.
Hundreds of such details mark Dostoevsky's year-long burst of composition, hour upon hour, &bquo;Without straightening my neck&equo;, he said.
Thus he caught the police station and the whole city during those few fictional july <head>days</head> when everything except the Epilogue happens.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40100" docsrc="bnc_BN7_876">
<answer instance="day.40100" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
GPs and family planning clinics can also provide advice to those who wish to use natural methods of seeking to avoid pregnancy. [pb] [/p] [p]
Contact your local Family Health Services Authority or District Health Authority for information on the availability of local services (the address will be in the phone book).
Information can also be obtained from: [/p] [p]
For advice on natural family planning methods: [pb] [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
In case of emergency [/head] [p]
Emergency contraception (sometimes called &bquo;the morning after pill&equo;) may protect you against pregnancy if you have had sexual intercourse without contraception or if you think that the method you have used may not have worked &mdash; but it should never be used up to 72 hours after intercourse and an IUD method that may be fitted within five <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40101" docsrc="bnc_CAD_1941">
<answer instance="day.40101" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
Boys being boys, (What, you mean sexist tossers? &mdash; Female Ed) the interview crashes to a halt as Galliano grapple for a peep of her pins.
They don't know her name and the chances are that she ain't that familiar with them.
If she's got half an ounce of cool in her beautiful bones then she'll get wise. [ptr][ptr][pb] [/p] [caption]
St Etienne: Heavenly-sent [/caption] [caption]
Galliano: WARNING &mdash; this band features Mick Talbot [/caption] [/div2] [div2] [head]
HI, ENERGISE [/head] [p]
Round and round, and back again, everything spins around, passing by if you missed it the first time.
David Lee from ENERGIZE thinks Electro is on its way back, and could speak for many hours about the halcyon <head>days</head> before Electro meant toddlers break-dancing in the streets, title-dropping classics like Man Parrish's &bquo;Hip Hop Be Bop&equo;, early Mantronix, and Shannon. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40106" docsrc="bnc_ABW_1496">
<answer instance="day.40106" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40106" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
And she enjoyed the humour: the comic dignity of goats, with their vacant, pale, wide-angle eyes (reminiscent of a well-known soap star), the retriever who collapsed in an untidy heap (dogs were becoming outcasts, like smokers) &mdash; in contrast to the neat pool of sleeping cat. [/p] [p]
Exact Nature! which designs and makes both plants and animals so carefully &mdash; each animal with precisely the amount and type of intelligence it needs to survive &mdash; and then squanders them so carelessly.
Life, not lives. [/p] [p]
It had been a gloomy <head>day</head> which suddenly burst into splendour in the evening, the clouds rising behind the fields in the setting sun like mountains (if only they had been!) and above, a darkening amethyst sky with &mdash; the finishing touch &mdash; a rose pink filigree disc of a moon foreshadowing the peace and perfection of a moonlit night. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40107" docsrc="bnc_CK5_3177">
<answer instance="day.40107" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
And then, right in the middle of a well-executed display of crushing mediocrity, these four grinning long-hairs launch into &bquo;Soup&equo;, which succeeds in being every bit as stunning as the recorded version.
It's followed by &bquo;Gibbet&equo;, a lush, textured tune that scrapes the impressive heights reached by its predecessor, only to give way to more featherweight tat. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Confused&equo; isn't the half of it. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
IT'S ONLY ROCK 'N' STROLL [/head] [head]
STROLLERCOASTER [/head] [p]
BREATHE IN &mdash; Jon &bquo;Fat Beast&equo; 's &bquo;Indie Variety Spectacular&equo; is coming to a college near you.
Forget your Rollercoasters and Lollapaloozas, this is burgeoning Indiedom in a shrink-wrapped package. [/p] [p]
The idea took shape some five years ago in the back room of London's Bull &amp; Gate, and it's taken until now to get it on the road &mdash; for 32 <head>days</head> only.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40109" docsrc="bnc_B29_595">
<answer instance="day.40109" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The facade survived intact and was incorporated in the rebuilding, which was completed in 1932. [/p] [p]
However, the fires of the Rising and exposure to the weather in the years immediately after contributed to the decay of the stonework of the facade in a way that has made it hazardous in recent years.
To remedy this, a major restoration project is now under way, financed by an allocation of funds from the National Lottery. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Where you can find out more about 1916 [/head] [p]
This exhibition is intended to provide a brief survey of the political events and historical forces that shaped the 1916 Rising.
The Video-wall presentation attempts to give an impression of what actually happened over those 18 tumultuous <head>days</head> between the reading of the Proclamation and the execution of James Connolly. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40111" docsrc="bnc_CKV_1029">
<answer instance="day.40111" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
In recent years Winters has interested himself in making objects of glass and ceramics.
Perhaps it is true that everything points back to one's youth: as a teenager Winters began a bottle collection after discovering a drugstore basement full of abandoned glass containers.
&bquo;Vitro Vivo: Paintings, Glass and Ceramics&equo; is how Winters styles his newest exhibition, on until 20 March at Brooke Alexander. [/p] [p]
During his European peregrinations in the 1970s, Winters at one point met up with Marcel Broodthaers in Paris.
There he assisted him in the preparation of an installation called &bquo;La Salle Blanche&equo;.
Broodthaers, who was an installationist in the <head>days</head> when such work was still rather uncommon, became a guru to a select handful of French and later American artists &mdash; but his work remains, oddly, little known in New York.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40113" docsrc="bnc_B22_263">
<answer instance="day.40113" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
On the west side of Culver Street at the Milford Street junction was Jenkins' Shop, having a window in each street with the door across the corner.
It was not large but did a fairish trade.
Noted for its cleanliness, it was owned by Mrs. Jenkins, although the work was done by her daughter and son-in-law, Mr. &amp; Mrs. Cecil Bevis.
On entering the shop, facing you was a glass showcase with a marble top for the counter.
Shelving covered the back two walls, whilst to the right was a biscuit stand containing some dozen tins, stacked at an angle so that by just taking off the lid, biscuits could be removed.
Jenkins did quite a delivery trade, the goods being taken out by Mr. Bevis on a very old &bquo;errand boy's&equo; bike with a wicker basket at the front.
They used to sell cut-corned beef at 2d a quarter pound, broken biscuits for 6d a pound, [gap] [pb] there were many of these in the <head>days</head> before packaging.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40114" docsrc="bnc_AT3_2169">
<answer instance="day.40114" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
I picked up reasonable speed and had just about regained my composure when a hand appeared on my left shoulder from behind!
The wraith had caught me up.
I gathered my courage, and turned, prepared to look myself in the face.
Instead, I saw a smiling, though breathless, New Zealander. [/p] [p]
&bquo;You walk at some speed,&equo; he said.
&bquo;What a job I've had catching you.
We read about your trip in the paper before we came on holiday and now we're on our way back through Reggane.
Your friends told us to follow the [hi]piste [/hi] and we'd be sure to meet you head on.
We'd gone miles, then saw your tracks going in the opposite direction, so we doubled back.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Yeah, the [hi]piste [/hi] was too churned up.
I've been south of it all <head>day</head> .&equo; [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40116" docsrc="bnc_ARB_264">
<answer instance="day.40116" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;I could have sworn you were American.
What are you doing here?&equo;
Looking and listening.
I ask what he does.
&bquo;I'm a businessman from Indiana.&equo;
Here on business?
&bquo;On vacation.&equo;
You must be the first tourist in years.
&bquo;Right.&equo;
Been here long?
&bquo;A couple of <head>days</head> .&equo; [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40117" docsrc="bnc_A90_397">
<answer instance="day.40117" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Richard Lee, who trains Market Leader, expressed himself happy with Greene's riding and said he felt Market Leader was a moderate animal. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Pakistan v India, third Test Shoaib cashes in. [/head] [p]
SHOAIB MOHAMMAD completed a double century, his first in Tests, before the third Test at Lahore was allowed to subside into the inevitable draw yesterday. [/p] [p]
Pakistan were 699 for five in reply to India's first innings score of 509 when the game was called off 10 overs into the final hour with Shoaib 203 not out. [/p] [p]
Pakistan's score was the highest by any side in a Test in Pakistan, surpassing the 561 they made against New Zealand in 1955-56, and the highest in matches between the two countries. [/p] [p]
Only two wickets fell yesterday, slightly below the game's average of three a <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40122" docsrc="bnc_A4F_540">
<answer instance="day.40122" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The fall was not helped by remarks made in Moscow by Alan Greenspan, chairman of the US Federal Reserve, who said it might be counterproductive to give great importance to short-term stabilisation of domestic financial or foreign exchange markets. [/p] [p]
Though there was some selling yesterday, volume was not heavy.
Some large investors stood on the sidelines, happy to have moved money out of UK companies earlier in the year to overseas markets. [/p] [p]
Most fund managers believed it was too early to say when they would consider buying London shares again. [/p] [p]
Wall Street, however, experienced an unusually quiet day, with stock markets drifting slightly lower despite the strong dollar and firm credit markets.
Investment strategists said the decline was attributable to profit-taking after six <head>days</head> of climbing prices, which brought the Dow Jones Industrial average up by more than 100 points. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40125" docsrc="bnc_CBE_477">
<answer instance="day.40125" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
PUNK violinist Nigel Kennedy has escaped having a good behaviour pledge slapped on him after smashing up a hotel room. [/p] [p]
&bquo;You may as well ask us to guarantee world peace,&equo; said record company EMI's Louise Bagshawe. [/p] [p]
&bquo;He hardly has a reputation to protect.&equo; [/p] [p]
Kennedy, 36, caused &pound;3,000 worth of damage to his &pound;350-a-night penthouse suite in Berlin, ruining sofas, carpets and china. [/p] [p]
He is currently No 1 in the classical charts with Beethoven's Violin Concerto. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Deadly jinx of Lockerbie [/head] [head]
Adrian Lee [/head] [p]
A JET crashed yesterday killing all 157 people on board &mdash; bringing chilling echoes of the Lockerbie disaster. [/p] [p]
The Libyan Arab Airlines Boeing 727 came down the <head>day</head> after the fourth anniversary of the Lockerbie bomb &mdash; allegedly planted by two Libyans &mdash; which killed 270.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40128" docsrc="bnc_C93_1272">
<answer instance="day.40128" senseid="day-2"/>
<answer instance="day.40128" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Until the 1950s the village had a chapel, a school, two shops and a public house.
At the present time there is only the public house left. [/p] [p]
The children travel by school bus to Howden, and social events are held in the old school.
It is no longer a farming community.
People travel outside the village to work, so turning it into a dormitory village. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Skerne [/head] [p]
Skerne is mentioned in the Domesday Book as a small village and seems to have changed little ever since!
It was a fairly important village, the church having possible connections with Meaux Abbey.
Certainly the Abbey were known to be large landowners in the area. [/p] [p]
The Norman church was much larger than its present <head>day</head> form, having a north transept of which the arches leading to it can still be seen.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40129" docsrc="bnc_CHK_893">
<answer instance="day.40129" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Along the side of Roaring Springs Canyon the path hugs a ledge of pink sandstone, giving airy views into the rocky chasm below. [/p] [p]
Roaring Springs at the junction of Bright Angel Canyon, is like a last oasis before entering the desert.
There's a waterfall and a stream which looks fantastic.
Below Roaring Springs the real desert starts. [ptr][/p] [caption]
Junction of Roaring Springs and Bright Angel Canyons, where the real desert starts [/caption] [p]
In Bright Angel the heat is intense and cacti with red and yellow flowers grow along the sides of the trail among great sheared-off blocks of stone.
Rattlesnakes are supposed to be common, though they are generally shy and silent and we didn't see any trace of them. [/p] [p]
At the end of Bright Angel Canyon &mdash; and a long <head>day</head> 's walking &mdash; is the central canyon and finally the Colorado river &mdash; wide, green, fast flowing, and icy cold.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40131" docsrc="bnc_ARW_171">
<answer instance="day.40131" senseid="day-4"/>
<context>
Delia Cope believes that although we have suffered from slavery, imperialism, capitalism, and exploitation, we should dismiss our feelings, keep smiling and put up with this shit.
We have a right to be represented in a women's magazine that's fighting for equal representation.
I'm sure the Delia Copes of this world can make their own boring magazine. [/p] [p]
Yes, middle class women have done a lot for the &bquo;Women's Movement&equo; but does she really think that us [hi]working class women [/hi] have been sitting on our arses doing nothing all this time. [/p] [p]
Anyway, I hope that Spare Rib always continues to be there for all women, and some of us do appreciate the entertaining, interesting and informative magazine Spare Rib is. [/p] [p]
YOURS, SURINDER LANDA [/p] [/div2] [div2] [p]
* indicates that this letter has been cut [/p] [p]
INTERNATIONAL WOMEN'S <head>DAY</head> IS MARCH 8 &mdash; IF YOU HAVE ANY LISTINGS PLEASE SEND THEM IN! [ptr][/p] [caption]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40132" docsrc="bnc_C87_2215">
<answer instance="day.40132" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The ten runners-up will receive their own personal choice of cassette from the list provided in that issue. [/p] [p]
And the big winner is&hellip;
Terence Honeyford, Buxton, Derbyshire. [/p] [p]
The following ten receive the Hi-Tec game of their choice: [gap] [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
WAGGLE THAT STICK MADAM (Issue 86) [/head] [p]
Originally we were planning to reward the first ten correct answers drawn out of the bag with a wonderful Sigma-Ray joystick, but unfortunately Markie (feeble minded fool that he is) mistook them for his laundry and took them home to be washed by his Mum.
However Steve decided it would be unfair for the winners to go without some kind of reward, and so he intends to pop round to show you his collection of &bquo;Bunty&equo; comics &mdash; expect him within the next 28 <head>days</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40135" docsrc="bnc_AND_1736">
<answer instance="day.40135" senseid="day-4"/>
<context>
The NUT isn't the only union to be alarmed by the fact that some schools are attempting to influence parental choice through &bquo;free gifts&equo; on enrolment.
The National Association of Head Teachers [hi]Code of Conduct [/hi] instructs members to: [quote] [p]
avoid the practice of giving gifts or commercial incentives to prospective pupils or their parents with the intention of inducing them to enrol and to take account of the possible damage to pupils in other educational establishments as a result of marketing activities. [/p] [/quote] [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Keeping track of competition [/head] [p]
Not only are primary schools in the neighbourhood competing for children but prep schools may also be attracting pupils out of the area too. [/p] [p]
Popping along to open <head>days</head> and public events to see what's on offer and collecting a few prospectuses will give some data to think about.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40136" docsrc="bnc_B1N_1707">
<answer instance="day.40136" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
We'll be up in five minutes.&equo; [/p] [p]
A whole lighthouse to myself.
An eery echoing spiralling climb of 168 steps took me up to the light itself and 180 degree views stretching to hazy nothingness to the west and north; Harris hills to the south-west; the Cuillins of Skye to the south and the mainland mountains to the east. [/p] [p]
The lighthouse was fourteen years old when JTR sketched it and by 1876 fish oil had been replaced by paraffin fuel.
It was a hundred years later that electricity was first used.
Erosion of the cliffs below have changed the profile of his view.
The [pb] previous year to my visit a sizeable chunk had cracked off in a storm. [/p] [p]
The <head>day</head> I was there was the still, silent kind of a winter day when the light clings to the skyline slowly moving round from east to south to west.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40138" docsrc="bnc_CB5_31">
<answer instance="day.40138" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40138" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
&bquo;Hark at you!
You have come back in a funny mood.
What's got into you?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Oh nothing much,&equo; Ruth retorted.
&bquo;Only that my father's dead, my stepmother's ill, and I'm worried sick about my grandfather!
Nothing at all, really!&equo; [/p] [p]
She could hardly tell Florrie that, most of all, her mind was on Dick.
He had already gone to his new job in Wensleydale, with a promise to return on his first free Sunday. [/p] [p]
Ruth's conscience was troubled over Dick: not because of what they had done together &mdash; that had been wonderful and whenever she thought about it her body ached, her breasts tingled with longing to experience it again &mdash; but because she now knew, had known it from the <head>day</head> after he had brought her home, that he was not the man she wanted to marry.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40139" docsrc="bnc_C98_2586">
<answer instance="day.40139" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
I realise what a fool I was, throwing myself at you the way I did.&equo;
George made a deprecating sound, but she held up her hand to silence him and then continued, &bquo;I'm happy enough at Uncle Nathan's, although coming back has brought it home to me how much I miss country life.
What I said when I left still holds good, George.
I do love you &mdash; I shall always do so and no matter how many eligible young men my Uncle parades before me, I shall never marry.&equo; [/p] [p]
George felt uncomfortable at this declaration, especially as it was made in a steady and unemotional voice, far removed from the previous frantic outburst on the day she had left the farm. [/p] [p]
, I just want you to know that I shall never change, but I also want you to allow me to come home now and again for a few <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40144" docsrc="bnc_CG0_1440">
<answer instance="day.40144" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
They put up [hi]dazibao [/hi] which at first mostly mourned Chai, but the contents of the posters soon became more politically oriented.
The situation at Beida became tense as demonstrations were called to protest not just at the student's death but the poor conditions of intellectuals in China, the lack of free speech and human rights, excessive bureaucracy in the party's structure and rampant corruption within party echelons.
These issues were all becoming &bquo;hot topics&equo; of discussion and were later to form an integral part of the 1989 student movement.
The tragic death of Chai Qing Feng gave rise to small-scale protest which signalled clear warnings to the leadership of the serious problems they would have to face.
A brief &bquo;diary&equo; of the tense <head>days</head> in June 1988, when a full-fledged &bquo;xuechao&equo; was narrowly avoided, is given below. [pb] [list] [item]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40146" docsrc="bnc_AA3_407">
<answer instance="day.40146" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
But he added: &bquo;It didn't require a great deal of insight in 1985 to appreciate that the business of Barlow Clowes was not at that time being run in a fashion which made it an obvious candidate for a licence.&equo; [/p] [p]
Mr Alf Morris (Lab.
Wythenshawe) welcomed a step forward for the victims of a &bquo;huge and vile swindle&equo;.
Two of his elderly constituents had lost not only their life savings, but their homes. [/p] [p]
But they had received a further &bquo;hammer blow&equo; with a demand yesterday &bquo;for thousands of pounds from the Inland Revenue for taxation which they had been told by Barlow Clowes had been deducted at source. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Shares tumble after Wall Street slump. [/head] [head]
By Mark Milner [/head] [p]
SHARE prices in London shrugged off Monday's sharp fall on Wall Street but then succumbed to fresh falls in New York late in the <head>day</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40148" docsrc="bnc_A74_249">
<answer instance="day.40148" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
I sort of sit by her bed till she falls asleep.
It's weird, but when she's asleep she looks real young, even though her face is all puffy.
I'm not tired no more so I just sit and watch her.
I still don't understand why she was all bashed up.
She's my friend. [/p] [p]
I been to hospital once to visit someone.
I can't remember who, but they were pretty poorly like and all round the bed was flowers and fruit and that.
I remember cos it looked so nice.
Sitting there, I think about that for a while, then I decide to bring all my plants in and stick them round the bed.
I don't have no fruit, but I reckon just plants are OK without the fruit.
So that's what I do &mdash; I bring all my plants and the flowers Mr Frost gave me a couple of <head>days</head> ago.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40149" docsrc="bnc_CNA_447">
<answer instance="day.40149" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
The household timetable revolves around restaurant work, with children often being late for school, and visitors being least welcome (and this is a very hospitable culture) early in the morning.
The notion of a routine, of a particular time for meals, baths, bed for young children &mdash; to fit in with the other interests and commitments of parents working outside the home &mdash; is not especially important.
If Bangladeshi mothers' idea of time emphasises fluidity and flexibility, then Welsh mothers' notions emphasise regularity and routine. [/p] [/div4] [div4] [head]
sleeping patterns [/head] [p]
Bangladeshi babies are thought to be vulnerable, and they sleep close to other people both <head>day</head> and night; [pb] at night they are either in the mother's bed or in a cot next to it, a practice also reported by Farooqi [hi]et al [/hi].
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40151" docsrc="bnc_B7J_1444">
<answer instance="day.40151" senseid="time_of_day-0"/>
<context>
And yet, so mechanical is this learning routine that if we interrupt such a bee while she is feeding she must take off and land again of her own accord, that landing permits her to choose the correct feeder colour on her next visit.
Similarly, bees learn landmarks after taking off: a recruit who arrived and fed at the feeder, but was transported back to the hive while feeding, returned without the slightest memory of the landmarks she must certainly have seen on her arrival. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Desirable imperfection [/head] [p]
Other aspects of the associative component of flower learning seem equally curious.
Although a bee learns a flower's odour almost perfectly in one visit, she must make several trips to learn its colour with precision; and even then a bee never chooses the correct colour 100 per cent of the time.
It learns shape less quickly, and time of <head>day</head> more slowly still.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40152" docsrc="bnc_A0L_140">
<answer instance="day.40152" senseid="day-4"/>
<context>
&bquo;Are you coming, Francis?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I think it's girls&equo; talk,&equo; said he, archly. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Oh, piss off, you silly old queen.
R's more like Claire Rayner!&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;But you love it, darling!&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;It's all right,&equo; said Jay, grinning absurdly.
It was pleasant to feel needed by an attractive older woman, it amused her when Lucy pecked her goodbye.
Always brisk, always on the cheek.
Food for fantasy. [/p] [p]
It was springtime when she fell in love with Lucy.
On St Patrick's <head>Day</head> , at 7.48 in the evening, just like that.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40156" docsrc="bnc_CBG_9175">
<answer instance="day.40156" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
&bquo;There were loads of players who were just as good as Ian, but they didn't have his determination. [/p] [p]
Some dropped out and got into drugs, others just fancied drinking with their mates in the pub. [/p] [p]
&bquo;But he stuck at it, even though clubs didn't give him his chance until he went to Palace. [/p] [p]
Now, the same people who discarded him as a kid are the ones who want to shake his hand. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I must admit, when he came to the club we didn't hit it off.
I felt threatened by him because I used to play up front, so I decided to show him who was boss.
But that all changed after an incident in training. [/p] [p]
&bquo;All the older pros used to take the mickey out of us, but then one <head>day</head> in a practice match Ian went past Jim Cannon, who had been at the club for ages, and he didn't like it. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40157" docsrc="bnc_B1J_592">
<answer instance="day.40157" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
But shouting murder at those who are trying their best to maintain quality of life from another standpoint is neither appropriate, nor likely to produce a healthy outcome for society. [/p] [p]
The Roman Catholic Church must take a great deal of credit for consistently arguing the &bquo;pro-life&equo; case.
That is why it is sad to see so much bitter polemic springing out of sincere concern.
But to argue that an embryo is sacred is different from saying that a sperm is sacred.
That is what the illogical anti-contraception stance of the Roman Catholic Church is in effect saying &mdash; and as that film so vividly illustrated that would mean a mini-genocide going on inside every male every minute. [/p] [p]
The Irish Government may some <head>day</head> allow non-Catholics, and Catholics [pb] too, to buy contraceptives in Eire.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40160" docsrc="bnc_CDK_1261">
<answer instance="day.40160" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Hurry up &mdash; this one is often learnt from our parents.
How many times were you told to hurry up, and how many times have you said &bquo;hurry up&equo; to your children?
This can turn into a driver where people then feel they have to achieve everything in the fastest possible time.
Never mind the quality &mdash; watch the speed! [/item] [item]
I want to please you &mdash; most of us like to be popular and enjoy pleasing other people.
However, when this becomes a driver we are often looking for attention when we are doing something.
We over-emphasize our [hi]needs [/hi] for other people's approval of what we do.
This makes it very difficult for us to be angry with other people or to give criticism. [pb] [/item] [item]
Be strong-I will achieve all these things in a <head>day</head> even if I am exhausted by the end of it.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40161" docsrc="bnc_A46_304">
<answer instance="day.40161" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Egon Krenz, 48, a hard-drinking hard-liner and nominally number two, responsible for youths, is now written off, having no friends in the Soviet Union or anywhere else.
But no one knows, and perhaps there is nothing to know. [/p] [p]
President Gorbachev claimed on Soviet television to have found many supporters of perestroika in SED.
That could be true.
The disgruntlement among its two million members is almost palpable. [/p] [p]
The 22-man Politburo jealously guards power.
It is entirely dominated by old comrades of 77-year-old Erich Honecker from the days when, after 1945, he built his powerbase.
All in Mr Honecker's image, tough and second rate, they are not inclined to give up the hunting lodges and chauffeurs they feel are their due.
With luck, an &bquo;easeful death&equo; will intervene before that <head>day</head> comes.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40163" docsrc="bnc_ASB_658">
<answer instance="day.40163" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
A search of his house revealed evidence that was, to put it mildly, incriminating: two face masks, a building society pass book hidden under the carpet, lots of property from some other burglaries, and photographs of Samuel kissing bundles of banknotes.
Samuel admitted to the burglaries but not to the robbery.
The police were anxious to charge him with this as well.
He had said that he did not want a solicitor when he first arrived at the police station, at 2 p.m.
At 8.30 p.m. he asked for his lawyer.
The superintendent refused access, recording that it was a serious arrestable offence and that there was a &bquo;likelihood of other suspects to be arrested being inadvertently warned&equo;.
He was kept in overnight and questioned in more detail.
At 11 a.m. the following <head>day</head> his mother was told of his detention.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40165" docsrc="bnc_A61_1864">
<answer instance="day.40165" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
&bquo;Very well played, Piper,&equo; remarked Mills Roberts as he and his Officers left the saluting base and made their way across the village green in the direction of Brigade H.Q I remained at attention until they disappeared through the gates of the big house.
I felt it was prudent to remain silent and then keep out of the Brigadier's way until he had forgotten the incident of the bodyguards.
The parade dispersed, the Commandos returning to their respective units, and soon the village green was quiet, except for the murmur of French voices as the civilians read the newsheet pinned to a tree.
Whatever the newsheet was telling them they all seemed excited about it; there was waving of arms and pointing in the direction of Caen.
The newsheet had started to appear over the past few <head>days</head> as the villagers began to return to their homes.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40168" docsrc="bnc_A75_844">
<answer instance="day.40168" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Accepting that meals are a very important part of a person's life-style means that their timing might have an important role in adjusting the body clock.
The effect can be direct, through the influence of food intake on gut activity (see below), or indirect, through the social factors that are associated with meals. [/p] [p]
Indigestion and constipation [/p] [p]
After eating the meal, the food must now be digested.
This requires the co-ordinated release into our gut of a series of digestive enzymes and fluids which are then mixed with the food.
The digested material is slowly passed through the gut by muscle action, and foodstuffs, water and salts are absorbed into our blood stream.
What remains is converted into solid material for elimination as faeces. [/p] [p]
There is no good evidence to indicate that these processes cannot be achieved by the body equally well at any time of the <head>day</head> or night.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40169" docsrc="bnc_CEB_2827">
<answer instance="day.40169" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Rather messily, incidentally.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;That sounds similar to Tom's.
Well, we'll see if any more turn up.&equo; [/p] [p]
Stanley sighed.
&bquo;I'll be frank with you.
I'd rather it were kept quiet if any more do.
The hunt can do without a report like that in the local press.
It would inspire the cranks and a shoal of other letters.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I promise you we'll be discreet.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Discretion,&equo; said the Master slowly.
&bquo;Not much of that about these <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40172" docsrc="bnc_B01_612">
<answer instance="day.40172" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Advocacy projects are beginning to emerge, with young-old people often acting as advocates for people with illnesses like dementia or stroke who [pb] cannot articulate their needs.
Self-advocacy requires training and support for inarticulate people to learn how to voice their needs and wishes.
I once attended a talk at which a group of people with learning difficulties described how they hated being called &bquo;mentally handicapped&equo;.
It made a lasting impression on me.
There may be all kinds of professional practices which frail and inarticulate older people hate, but which, without support, they would be unable to articulate. [/p] [p]
One of the fundamental ways of changing attitudes is through information.
Often, negative attitudes are based on misinformation.
A commonly held view is that &bquo;we're all of us&hellip; moving&hellip; into the category of those who don't know what <head>day</head> it is.&equo;
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40174" docsrc="bnc_APK_189">
<answer instance="day.40174" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40174" senseid="U"/>
<context>
Thomson died in 1921 aged 84.
His real interest had always been in the scientific aspects of his work.
Although now remembered solely for his pictures, he would probably have preferred to be recognised as a man of science, and the man who taught Sir Henry Stanley the rudiments of expedition photography. [/p] [p]
Visual documents such as Thomson's are an exciting link with our own history, and that of the developing world.
The photographic pioneers who travelled our own rural lanes, and cobbled back alleys have left us a visual legacy that portrays the changing face of our society.
This legacy has been added to down the years, and continues to develop.
It's an interesting thought that the images of every <head>day</head> life that we all make today, will sooner or later become a part of this heritage. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40177" docsrc="bnc_AS0_676">
<answer instance="day.40177" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
If the situation lasts for a long time with no sign of improvement, you should discuss the future very carefully with the doctor or hospital specialist, rather than trying to cope in a hopeless situation which cannot resolve itself. [/p] [p]
Even if you are coping well enough overall, you may sometimes be provoked into anger against the patient, either because of his behaviour, or because of your mutual frustration at the situation his illness has created.
You may even feel like hitting him.
If you reach this stage, you will probably feel guilty about it, which adds to your own discomfort.
What you should recognize is that it is a warning sign that you have been doing too much, and that you need to get away from the patient, at least for short periods in the <head>day</head> , if not for some days or weeks.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40178" docsrc="bnc_CK4_1685">
<answer instance="day.40178" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The band's guitar tech, Mole &mdash; so named because of the way he squints through his rounded spectacles &mdash; punches a continuous barrage of Ramones hits into the jukebox, and drummer Fyfe Ewins models a beret he's liberated from Lord knows where. [/p] [p]
Therapy? 's latest game is &bquo;Whose Round Is It Anyway?&equo; in which contestants from the band and crew have to go to the bar and order a drink in the manner of a named personality.
Picture guitarist Michael McKeegan jerking his way back to the table in the style of Gary Numan! [/p] [p]
Little do we know that this drink will shape the course of the rest of the tour.
But that comes tomorrow.
For now, Therapy? are at the start of their first proper American jaunt, glad to take a break from the pressures of Britain and their debut major label release, and swap them for the promotional chores of the States. [/p] [p]
My key word for the next three <head>days</head> is born here out of a conversation with the increasingly vocal and 45-degree angled Fyfe.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40181" docsrc="bnc_BN6_1025">
<answer instance="day.40181" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
The kind words you have to say about me, [/l] [l]
Say them now for I want to hear them. [/l] [/poem] [/p] [p]
I decided to have a farm sale after Uncle went, and put up all the livestock for auction.
There were about fifteen cattle, around a dozen sheep and a few lambs left over from the spring lambing.
But I chose the wrong time when prices were depressed and there wasn't a great deal to come after all the expenses were paid.
Apparently, if I had waited a bit longer prices would have been much higher.
But then I was never much of a businesswoman and I had no close relatives left to turn to for help and advice. [/p] [p]
I was all alone. [pb] [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
My Friends, the Beasts of the Field [/head] [p]
Life for Hannah Hauxwell then settled into a pattern which basically continues to this <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40182" docsrc="bnc_ALW_733">
<answer instance="day.40182" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The new booklets complement those already available on assessments (regulation 6), health surveillance (regulation 11), setting in-house occupational exposure limits (regulation 7), and information, instruction and training (regulation 12) and will be joined by booklets on COSHH and product distribution, contractors and occupational exposure limits for mixtures, during the first quarter of this year.
The booklets will be of use to any industry sector that uses chemicals. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
Industry safety profile [/head] [p]
The Health and Safety Executive (HSE) has produced a statistical safety profile of the chemical industry.
It provides key statistics on safety matters and concentrates on details of the fatal, major and over three day injuries to employees in the chemical industry between 1981 and 1988&ndash;89. [/p] [p]
During 1988&ndash;89, 4051 injuries were reported &mdash; 8 were fatalities, 490 major injuries and 3553 resulted in absence from work for more than three <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40185" docsrc="bnc_B7E_443">
<answer instance="day.40185" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
At the end of this period, in a month when the natural, or &bquo;wild&equo;, population of these mosquitoes should have peaked, not a single [hi]A. albimanus [/hi] could be found. [/p] [p]
This technique is more efficient when only sterile males are released, but we must be able to sort out the sexes.
At first entomologists depended on a slight difference in the size of the male and female pupae, but the technique was far from efficient.
Jack Seawright, a USDA colleague of Weidhaas, used a technique of genetic sexing.
This involved the translocation of the gene responsible for resistance to the carbamate insecticide propoxur on to the male-Y-chromosome so that only the males were resistant.
The exposure of immature insects to a dosage of the insecticide sufficient to kill the susceptible females, enabled Seawright to &bquo;mass produce&equo; more than one million sterile males a <head>day</head> with only two females per thousand.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40186" docsrc="bnc_CH1_9648">
<answer instance="day.40186" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
On orders from the new Earl, my visits to the house were to be permitted only if I agreed to be supervised. [/p] [p]
The following day, when I arrived to collect her ladyship's papers, a similar reception was waiting.
This time it was Simon Thorpe, the new estate manager. [/p] [p]
Nothing was to be removed, and I was to go home and keep my head [corr] down [/corr]. [/p] [p]
A few days later, I was made redundant.
On the directions of the new heir to a &pound;50 million fortune, I was to receive the state minimum of one week's redundancy pay for each year's service. [/p] [p]
Only 11 years were acknowledged, and plans to throw the wedding reception at Althorp for my second marriage were cancelled. [/p] [p]
Two <head>days</head> after her husband's death, Lady Spencer came to Althorp with a roll of red stickers to identify her possessions, the pieces she would be removing to her London home. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40188" docsrc="bnc_CBG_349">
<answer instance="day.40188" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40188" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
I believe he'll get them, and &mdash; Hirst take note &mdash; it's a question of when, not if, Francis wins his first trophy. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Giant step [/head] [head]
Graham Fisher [/head] [p]
MANCHESTER UNITED manager Alex Ferguson staunchly backed his temperamental superstar Eric Cantona last night and claimed: &bquo;This man can become a giant at Old Trafford.&equo; [/p] [p]
Ferguson brushed aside what he called &bquo;innuendo and criticism&equo; and made it clear he regarded the acquisition of the French striker as a huge stepping stone towards winning the title. [/p] [p]
Within minutes of Cantona signing for United last week, sources at Leeds revealed that he had twice asked for a move, and stormed out of Elland Road only <head>days</head> before his &pound;1.2 million transfer. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40189" docsrc="bnc_AHB_10">
<answer instance="day.40189" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The Treasury says the decision to change the basis of treatment, announced by Peter Lilley, Trade and Industry Secretary, on February 13, came too late to affect the current year's figures but have been included in the 1993&ndash;94 estimates. [/p] [p]
Pressure from Bruce Millan, EC regional commissioner, has resulted in the Treasury reluctantly accepting that the funds provided by Brussels are additional to government spending rather than part of it and should be steered to specific projects rather than forming part of the spending pool.
Treasury insistence that EC contributions are &bquo;taxpayers' money&equo; and should be counted as part of the public spending programme caused friction with the EC and Mr Millan froze money due to coal and steel areas. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
City: Nervous sterling mauled by the mark [/head] [head]
By Anne Segall [/head] [p]
THE pound had another tense <head>day</head> , struggling to hold its own on the exchanges as investors waited nervously for weekend opinion polls before deciding their next move. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40192" docsrc="bnc_CHE_1921">
<answer instance="day.40192" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
I tried rearing owlets in my bedroom under heat lamps several times, usually without much success.
Come to think of it, I always seem to have baby owls in my bedroom.
Perhaps that's why it smells so terrible in there. [/p] [p]
One particular owl that sticks in my mind was one I kept alive for six weeks, in the early days.
He seemed to be doing fine and then one night I found him cold and dying.
I cuddled him for four hours until he died in my hands.
I was very upset, even though I had seen a lot of birds die before; I had really thought this one was going to make it.
I'm afraid this is just something you have to get used to, like a nurse in a hospital &mdash; it goes with the job.
Still, more make it these days, I'm glad to say.
I hope to rear another barn owl like Dawn some <head>day</head> , from the egg to the jesses.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40193" docsrc="bnc_ADK_568">
<answer instance="day.40193" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40193" senseid="U"/>
<context>
PET &bquo;HOTEL HATES&equo; (THE FREQUENT ONES) * narrow stairs and no lifts * low shower pressure * telephone kiosks built for left-handed midgets * only one plug, down on the floor under the bed and 5AMP * hairdryers on 1m fixed lead from the floor socket 3m away from wall mirror facing opposite direction * just two 40 watt lamps to read and work by * toilet rolls positioned for contortionists only * room service that brings each course separately throughout [hi]Dallas [/hi] * radiators that haven't been on for years * radiators that won't go off * basins that take half an hour to empty after you've cleaned your teeth and you want to shave * stoppers that hang under the cold water tap but don't reach the drain * stoppers that have no chain so you wallow in the dirty water to find them * toilets where you can sit down or close the door but not both [/caption] [p]
The venue staff should be able to demonstrate all their equipment and facilities, and understand your technical requests.
Watch out for the &bquo;Oh the electrician will be here on the <head>day</head> &mdash; I'm sure&equo; syndrome.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40195" docsrc="bnc_A9F_316">
<answer instance="day.40195" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The doctors, who deny the charge, are Dr Crockett, a Harley Street physician specialising in kidney disease, Mr Michael Joyce, a urologist at Guy's hospital in London, and Mr Michael Bewick, a leading kidney transplant surgeon. [/p] [p]
Mr Koc told Mr Roger HendersonQC, counsel for the GMC, that the &bquo;broker&equo; brothers Mr Ata Nur and Mr Riza Kuntar had promised him he would be getting a job when he was brought to England.
He was examined several times by Dr Crockett in his surgery, but was never told a kidney would be removed. [/p] [p]
Mr Henderson asked him three times if he had any idea what a kidney was for.
Mr Koc replied: &bquo;No.
I didn't know what a kidney was, that it would be worth money.
They stole one of my kidneys.&equo;
Mr Koc said on a visit to Dr Crockett's surgery he saw him hand a cheque to Mr Ata Nur Kuntar. [/p] [p]
Mr Koc remained in hospital for six <head>days</head> , and was then taken back to the small hotel where he had been staying since his arrival in London. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40196" docsrc="bnc_B1N_65">
<answer instance="day.40196" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
The factor, who was with us, asked him, in Gaelic, if he knew what he had taken.
He told him it was turpentine.
The shepherd grew pale and left us at once, and tried to rid his stomach of the dread stuff, and thereafter went home to his bed, expecting to die.
We called at the cottage at night, and found he was very ill, and it was not till the factor assured him he was joking, and that he had swallowed none other than the best of whiskey, that he rose from bed, and Donald was himself again. [/p] [/quote] [/p] [p]
John, your present temperance is admirable but, selfishly, I am comforted by your inclusion of that awful tale.
It somehow excuses my necessary but mild intemperance after one of your punishing walks. [pb] [/p] [p]
Housing conditions in Greenock in JTR's <head>day</head> were some of the worst in Britain.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40198" docsrc="bnc_CBV_3975">
<answer instance="day.40198" senseid="early_days-0"/>
<context>
It is easier to reconcile with the profit and loss account [/item] [/list] [/p] [p]
From the open-ended question asked, we can make some comments on the extent to which analysts actively use the information given in the cash flow statement for investment decisions.
Eleven analysts had stated that they were keeping a spreadsheet model of the company.
But only four specifically stated that they would extract information from the cash flow statement to build into their model.
Some appear to use the cash flow statement in an impressionistic way, in the words of one interviewee, &bquo;to get a feel for investments and for management action&equo;.
But we would add a word of caution: these are early <head>days</head> in the life of the cash flow statement and experience is needed to discover the most appropriate method of analysis. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40199" docsrc="bnc_B3J_625">
<answer instance="day.40199" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The seaman returned the nod and jerked his head towards the rear of the bridge. [/p] [p]
Picking up his now empty haversack, Yanto climbed up the ladder on to the deck.
A quick glance up and down the wharf showed no sign of Cliff Barrett.
He went up the companionway ladder to the bridge two rungs at a time.
&bquo;Don't forget you know who,&equo; Billy shouted from the top [pb] of the hatch ladder as Yanto and the seaman disappeared through a door at the rear of the bridge. [/p] [p]
Yanto stood alone in the oily smelling cabin, allowing his eyes to grow accustomed to the gloom after the bright sunshine outside.
He listened to the throb of the ship's generators, a noise he associated with every ship he had travelled on.
The Campbells steamer his mother had once taken him on for a <head>day</head> trip to Ilfracombe.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40201" docsrc="bnc_CMU_516">
<answer instance="day.40201" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40201" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
We now know too much about child development to allow this kind of testing to be inflicted on our schools, so we must co-operate in developing and using appropriate tests while, at the same time, resisting inappropriate proposals. [/p] [p]
Having established my personal feelings about the current political situation and the changes resulting from the GERBIL, it is now necessary to pay attention to present practice with regard to special needs in the primary school.
Perhaps the starting point for this discussion should be a historical one. [/p] [p]
When I started teaching a junior class in 1947 in a London County Council [pb] school there was no provision at all.
The school was a JMI school with over 400 pupils in ten classes, ten teachers plus a head teacher, a part-time secretary and a milk lady who came into school for one and a half hours a <head>day</head> to distribute milk.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40202" docsrc="bnc_CGE_1287">
<answer instance="day.40202" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
It may be full of happiness for those who are fortunate to have the right conditions at play in their lives, but there is no doubt how stretching it can be to live in close proximity to your relations. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
Mother and daughter [/head] [p]
A family doctor often finds himself a father confessor as much as a physician.
On Tuesdays, Dr Jacks takes both a [pb] morning and an afternoon surgery.
There'll be a whole range of needs, many uncomplicated, others requiring the most careful attention. [/p] [p]
This particular Tuesday Georgina Taylor came in looking tired and drawn.
At fifty-three she has had some minor medical problems, but is usually fit and healthy.
&bquo;Will you check my blood pressure please, doctor?
I've been feeling headachy and dizzy for a few <head>days</head> now.&equo; [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40204" docsrc="bnc_CHG_499">
<answer instance="day.40204" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Koraloona is 130 miles west of Sanders Island and is dangerous to shipping because it is encircled by a coral reef at times fifty miles long, marked on all Admiralty charts.
Two passages through the reef, both navigable for vessels up to 5,000 tons.
Main town of Koraloona is Anani.
Smaller town to east is Tala-Tala.
Several small villages, unnamed.
Regular vessels bring supplies from either Sanders Island or Apia, Pago Pago or Rarotonga.
Abundant water supplies, fruit, vegetables, staples, fish plentiful.
[hi]Note [/hi]: The Lords Commissioners of the Admiralty feel that pilots should advise would-be visitors that Koraloona has only one small hospital and one doctor. [/p] [p]
In that respect their Lordships were wrong; by the time the [hi]Mantela [/hi] docked Koraloona would have gained, at the ripe old age of twenty-four years, four months and seven <head>days</head> , their first assistant medical officer. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40206" docsrc="bnc_CHJ_533">
<answer instance="day.40206" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
WINTER WARMER [/head] [p]
A windproof layer can be used over the base layer in warm conditions, and when it gets chillier, over your fleece.
The modern microfibre fabrics which work so well in windproof garments are also quite often pretty goo din the wet.
They're not totally waterproof, but they'll see off pretty stiff showers.
They also scrunch down to virtually nothing in your pack. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
WEATHER SHIELD [/head] [p]
The outer layer is the totally waterproof one, and if you're going to follow the performance fabric ideology through to its logical conclusion, then a breathable waterproof is essential.
Many manufacturers have their own breathable fabrics these <head>days</head> , others use Sympatex or the best known top-of-the-range breathable, Gore-Tex, which is available in a variety of configurations.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40208" docsrc="bnc_B35_346">
<answer instance="day.40208" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The position will be a little clearer after the first of the two individual time trials around Luxembourg on Monday 13 July.
Team work now has no part in the outcome.
Alone on the road, forbidden to take shelter from any other rider, each man will be assessed for what he is.
This race against the clock is of an intriguing length, 68 kilometres, perhaps a little too short for the top men in the discipline.
Noone can win the Tour without being able to ride a very good time trial.
But only a supreme effort over this distance will produce more than two or three minutes' advantage.
That's a lot of time on the flat stages, not so much on the fierce and extended mountain climbs that are to come. [/p] [p]
The greatest pressure in Monday's time trial will be on the yellow jersey.
He will be the last man off, since riders begin in reverse order of positions on general classification.
Tension mounts throughout the <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40209" docsrc="bnc_AL6_661">
<answer instance="day.40209" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
Although the country may have lost its strategic significance with the collapse of the Soviet Union, Washington is nevertheless concerned at the possibility of an unstable radical Islamic state growing up on the borders of the former Soviet Central Asia. [/p] [p]
The signal for the collapse of the regime was Mr Najibullah's announcement last month that he was ready to step down in favour of a United Nations-appointed interim committee. [/p] [p]
It destroyed morale throughout the regime, forcing commanders and party chiefs to activate their tribal links with the Mujahideen and save their skins before the time of reckoning. [/p] [p]
The effect has been to accentuate divisions between the majority Pushtuns (known in the <head>days</head> of the Raj as Pathans) and the ethnic minorities of the north such as the Tajiks, who are kin to the people of the former Soviet republic of Tajikistan across the Amu Darya river. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40211" docsrc="bnc_B1G_904">
<answer instance="day.40211" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The absolute difference between the two figures seems to be due to two different factors: absorption by the oceans and other reductions in carbon stocks in living biota, the latter being strongly affected by human activities since the Industrial Revolution. [/p] [/div4] [div4] [head]
Does God play dice? [/head] [p]
Much environmental prediction is predicated upon a logical positivist or Newtonian deterministic basis.
The environmental systems are effectively regarded as machines whose workings can all be discovered, described in differential equation form and whose future activities can thus be predicted in detail if their initial states are known.
An argument by many atmospheric physicists, for example, is that shortcomings in the accuracy of weather prediction over periods of more than a few <head>days</head> largely results from the unsophisticated nature of existing models, the lack of suitable data and inadequate computer power (see Fig. 9.3, derived from Tyler 1989).
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40212" docsrc="bnc_CH5_2159">
<answer instance="day.40212" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
How do we look after it? [/p] [p]
A GINGER (Zingiber officinale) grows into a very handsome, three-foot-high conservatory or house plant, with yellow-green flowers with a purple, yellow-striped lip, but it is quite a shy flowerer. [/p] [p]
Gingers are natives of Malaysia, Eastern Asia and Northern Australia. [/p] [p]
They do best in a rich, limy potting mixture which should be kept moist while they are growing. [/p] [p]
The humidity should be supplied by regularly spraying the leaves with fresh water. [/p] [p]
Also stand the pot in a tray of damp pebbles, too. [/p] [/div2] [/div1] [div1] [head]
SAVE UP TO &pound;8.95 [/head] [head]
On a fun day out at Thorpe Park [/head] [p]
ENJOY a great <head>day</head> out at Thorpe Park, Britain's favourite leisure park, with mountains of fun for all the family. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40215" docsrc="bnc_C9E_1530">
<answer instance="day.40215" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The 23-year-old Brussels ace closed with a 67 to leave US money leader Dottie Mochrie trailing two shots in her wake. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
HOLING OUT [/head] [p]
&hellip;
Darren Clarke's dreams of a place in Ireland's side for the Alfred Dunhill Cup were dashed when a recurring tendinitis problem forced his withdrawal from the Volvo German Open.
The lucky trio were: Ronan Rafferty, Christy O'Connor Jnr and Philip Walton&hellip; [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
CADDIE'S WEDDING DAY BLUES [/head] [p]
Jamie Spence's caddie could be forgiven for taking a week off, especially since he was getting married.
But he didn't exactly pick the right week for doing it. [/p] [p]
Mark Steers, who has been carrying Jamie's bag for the past 15 months, got married [pb] in Liverpool on Saturday, September 5 1992.
On that <head>day</head> , his boss was playing in the Canon European Masters, returning a score of 73. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40216" docsrc="bnc_AT3_474">
<answer instance="day.40216" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Insurance, ferries, food and kit took a large slice, the rest went on fuel for the Land Rover's seven thousand mile round trip.
Petrol consumption was high, with the price often twice what it was at home. [/p] [p]
We were short of batteries, too.
The lads had brought four dozen for their torches and Mick's radio.
I had six dozen smaller ones for the tape recorder and my torch.
The tape recorder was used to send reports to churches and schools who were using the expedition to raise money for famine relief.
The torch was even more essential.
I made camp at sunset, and then cooked, wrote letters, and did my chores after dark.
In the morning, I broke camp in the dark.
At present usage I would run out of batteries before the half-way point and Mick and Paddy would run out just after. [/p] [p]
I [hi]had [/hi] to cover more than fifteen miles a <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40218" docsrc="bnc_CKH_114">
<answer instance="day.40218" senseid="day-4"/>
<context>
&bquo;CADBURY NUMBER 1&equo; an old 0-4-0 tank locomotive liveried in maroon and lined-out in yellow and black and locally known as &bquo;Lolloper&equo; due to its riding qualities, or &bquo;The Fruit and Nut Case&equo; from its original long association with the chocolate factory at Bourneville in Birmingham, hauled a short freight train on another adjacent road to the &bquo;Main Line&equo;. [/p] [p]
This was yet another most unusual event, as not too many preserved railways in Britain can actually operate a demonstration freight using industrial steam power.
The sight of this train-set was greeted with much pleasure amongst the huge audience. [/p] [p]
Based around the museum site was No. 7027 &bquo;Thornbury Castle&equo; awaiting restoration, plus modern preserved diesel/electric motive power in the shape of No. 40118 and No. 50043 =Eagle&equo;, the latter externally turned out for the extravaganza in Network South East colours. [/p] [p]
This was repainted earlier in the year for the BR Bescot Open <head>Day</head> at Walsall while 0-6-0- shunter 13029 was also used for various duties around the Museum site during the course of the weekend. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40220" docsrc="bnc_AN1_396">
<answer instance="day.40220" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Sulph. 0/2, 0/3, 0/4, and currently 0/5.
There has been no aggravation, the blood pressure is normal, the spells are infrequent now, and she is losing weight with improved energy.
Nat. sulph. will be continued in gradually ascending potencies until there is aggravation, or the symptoms change to another remedy. [/p] [p]
Case No. 3: A Lachesis patient, whose main complaint was fatigue, called for further treatment after his improvement stopped 4 months after a dose of Lachesis 1M which created a short initial aggravation.
He was given Lach. 0/1 with marked improvement after four doses, one dose daily.
Six weeks later he felt somewhat better but had an immediate flare-up of painful, bleeding [sic] hemorrhoids [/sic] on the left side, an old symptom.
This cleared on sac.lac. after five <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40222" docsrc="bnc_BNB_1029">
<answer instance="day.40222" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The war, seemingly interminable, was by now unpopular, and in October 1761, having failed to persuade his colleagues to declare war on Spain before she entered into an open alliance with France, Pitt the Elder resigned.
He was rapidly proved right; Spain pledged herself in December to a Family Compact with France, forcing England, on 2 January 1762, to declare war on her and reviving the old nightmare of a joint Franco-Spanish fleet sweeping up the Channel to land a papist army on English soil. [gap] [/p] [p]
The French invasion plan of 1762 was very different from all those that had preceded it.
The Duc de Choiseul did not expect to occupy England, much less incorporate it in Louis XV's empire, but merely to distract his enemy from further conquests overseas and encourage an early peace.
A copy of his plan was sent to Spain on the very <head>day</head> , 14 April 1762, that he replied encouragingly to a British approach about opening negotiations to end the war.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40223" docsrc="bnc_C94_237">
<answer instance="day.40223" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Even on the same diet, this will vary from person to person depending on many individual factors, including the amount of excess weight (the heavier you are the faster you tend to shed weight) and the degree of energy expended in physical activity.
Nevertheless, there was a simple weight-loss equation on which it was possible to estimate the maximum amount of weight likely to be lost each week on any specific calorie allowance.
This was based on subtracting the calories consumed in food from the calories required to keep the body going. [/p] [p]
Let us assume that you are a woman of medium height, doing a job like housework, which requires a moderate amount of physical activity, and that you are about one stone overweight and just about to embark on trying to lose it.
In these circumstances, it should be roughly assumed that you would be burning up around 2,000 calories a <head>day</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40225" docsrc="bnc_ADS_267">
<answer instance="day.40225" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
She had always told him how proud she was of him, that he should work so hard to support his son in a far-off country and how one day she would tell Oreste it was due to his father's efforts that he had been so well looked after.
Now, if he left service, it was true they would no longer be able to afford to remit the regular payments.
What was she asking him to do?
To throw over that stability she had insisted they must have.
It was too soon to do so.
In September, another year's rent must be paid and the money for that would not this time come from the Brownings.
Writing to Ellen, she could not help be bitter, remarking: &mdash; all life seems a trap again Ellen and I expect it has too often seemed so to you and will yet.
However hard I work and struggle for the future there are ever snares to catch me and sometimes I see no end to it and think myself doomed to pass my <head>days</head> in toil and nothing else.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40226" docsrc="bnc_ABW_861">
<answer instance="day.40226" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40226" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
In the interim, she had become a bit &bquo;bolshie&equo;.
After all, she told herself in extenuation, this was the first thing she had [hi]ever [/hi] done to please herself&hellip; [hi]but [/hi], said a small voice &mdash; &bquo;but&equo; is surely the most miserable little word in the English language &mdash; [hi]but [/hi]&hellip; they hadn't asked to come into this vale of tears&hellip;. [/p] [p]
Her family she could stand, and even regarded some of them as having qualities superior to her own, arrogant as she knew she was.
A few things nettled her: she did not relish being a clearing house for family complaints, for instance, and was carefully reticent on such occasions.
But [pb] their &bquo;friends!&equo;. [/p] [p]
As luck would have it, a furious wind was blowing on the <head>day</head> of their arrival, by hired minibus.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40228" docsrc="bnc_AHU_366">
<answer instance="day.40228" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Yet I would be insensitive indeed if I did not recognise the smell of battle and the weapons with which such wars are fought.
Barely over the age of 30, I used some of them in 1961 against the Establishment.
The most powerful, I found, was public opinion. [/p] [p]
Retrospectively, the last of the mill-owners, as I then described them, had no chance in the argument over the abolition of the maximum wage and easing players' contracts.
With hindsight, the two points of principle were indisputable.
First, that a player should be free to earn whatever his employer wished to pay him; secondly, that having fulfilled a contract, a player had the right to leave his employer and go elswhere, at the same time accepting the club's right to a transfer fee. [/p] [p]
On January 18, 1961, those two principles were agreed at a meeting at the Ministry of Labour four <head>days</head> before an all-out strike was to take place.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40229" docsrc="bnc_CS4_1977">
<answer instance="day.40229" senseid="day_off-0"/>
<context>
So there were large numbers of spectators who simply had no idea that you should be quiet when a golfer is about to hit a shot.
In fact the professional golfers almost took a back seat, and it always afforded me some wry amusement when Ryder Cup golfers of repute were ignored by the [pb] spectators who were intent on getting the autograph of some star from a television soap opera. [/p] [p]
Jack Mason was certainly far from his best in such a situation, and I was surprised that he had decided to enter.
But, since he was lying twelfth on the Ryder Cup points list and the first prize was &pound;40,000, he could hardly afford to miss out. [/p] [p]
The whole tournament was in effect a pro-am so the usual pro-am which precedes conventional tournaments was not required.
That gave me an extra <head>day</head> off, since Jack had decided that one practice round was enough for him.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40231" docsrc="bnc_AK6_137">
<answer instance="day.40231" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
I never wilted and was proud of my fighting qualities when I was looking for survival and happy for any form of success. [/p] [p]
&bquo;This season has been far better.
Now I am looking to win.
The world championship is the ultimate; any top player to lose at the Crucible can consider it a failure.&equo; [/p] [p]
Prowess at the game is not enough.
An iron constitution is required for 19 to 34-frame matches.
He will need to keep his eye on the ball during an opening match against rookie Peter Ebdon.
Davis is not taking it for granted. [/p] [p]
&bquo;The Crucible is awesome.
I still get butterflies coming down the steps to the tournament table. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I have a dress rehearsal the <head>day</head> before my match, walking into an empty arena.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40232" docsrc="bnc_ACP_664">
<answer instance="day.40232" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
In her future, a big fundamentalist upsurge has stuck women back in the kitchen and the bedroom, turned their money into plastic and then taken that plastic away.
It's not a particularly convincing rationale, but it's not meant to be &mdash; any more than George Orwell was literally predicting the future in [hi]1984 [/hi].
In any case, it's tucked away in the second half of the book, after Offred's prison-like existence has been thoroughly, horribly established.
Offred doesn't tell her story from beginning to end.
She keeps circling between past and present, memory and oblivion, like someone trying to wake up from a nightmare.
You think, &bquo;Why don't these women [hi]do [/hi] something?&equo;
And at the same time you understand &mdash; because they can't.
It's not rational.
It's just total. [/p] [p]
More and more these <head>days</head> &mdash; and often the bigger the production, the more it's true &mdash; film adaptions tend to be [hi]literal [/hi].
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40234" docsrc="bnc_CS4_740">
<answer instance="day.40234" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
He, too, had become part of her vicarious family, and she sent him regular messages of encouragement. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Now then, Chris, you take it easy and have an early night.
You look very tired and I'm not surprised,&equo; she said. [/p] [p]
A few reassurances later and she was on her way to do battle at the bridge table. [/p] [p]
I glanced at the answering machine in the corner and saw that the red light was glowing.
I rewound the tape and prepared to note down any urgent messages.
A couple of clients had called me, and I would have time to talk to them in the morning; and I had an invitation to a golf society day in a couple of weeks' time. [pb] [/p] [p]
The final message was from Andrew Buccleuth, who told me that the shares in one of the leisure companies which I followed closely had dropped a further 20p during the <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40235" docsrc="bnc_BMV_1181">
<answer instance="day.40235" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
The staff listed consists only of the chancellor, one of the greatest of the royal officers, whose wages were five shillings a day, the master of the writing-office, who originally had tenpence a day, but Robert de Sigillo had made himself so indispensable that he had risen into the two shilling class, and the chaplain in charge of the chapel and relics.
It is clear that Robert de Sigillo did not write all the royal writs himself, although there is no reason to believe that a twelfth-century English king needed a permanent staff of more than half a dozen clerks, sometimes perhaps even less.
The departments which fed the king and organized his armies, and above all his hunting staff, were far larger.
The household of Henry I of England, the most literate of its <head>day</head> north of the Alps and the Pyrenees, the centre of an administrative and judicial system which was rapidly growing, was still a mobile headquarters for a chieftain whose principal business was to hunt and to fight. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40237" docsrc="bnc_AK4_470">
<answer instance="day.40237" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
She differs from Proust, however, in dwelling on the reality and hence irredeemable transience of the past. [/p] [p]
Yourcenar (an anagram on the family name of Crayencour) was not an academic, but as one of France's most highly-regarded novelists, she was the first woman to be elected to the French Academy.
Her best known novel, Memoirs of the Emperor Hadrian, is a work of scholarship and fiction, but, unlike the narratologists, she believed in the truth of history and the often melancholy tone of her writing lies in her regret that the dead have no more truthful memorial than that which the living can provide.
She would have especially wanted to know more of her own mother, whose story is told in the final chapters and who died in 1903 of peritonitis when the author was 10 <head>days</head> old. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40240" docsrc="bnc_CCL_1523">
<answer instance="day.40240" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
The authentic Church is part of a Kingdom which is not on the way out, but on the way in.
The people of God, therefore, have a stake in today and an inheritance for tomorrow.
No matter how unpromising the immediate situation may seem, they have an unshakable hope that the best is yet to come.
Nostalgia needs to be replaced by expectancy. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Remnant theology&equo; exercises a powerful influence in the Protestant churches of Western Europe.
When the future seems to be filled with storm clouds, it may appear that the Church has no other recourse but to batten down the hatches and attempt to ride the storm.
Our Lord did indeed warn of persecutions, heresy and growing violence in the last days.
These &bquo;last <head>days</head> &equo; have in measure been with us since his crucifixion two thousand years ago.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40242" docsrc="bnc_A1N_626">
<answer instance="day.40242" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
&bquo;Earners&equo; like these keep Charles Clairmonte's body and soul together &mdash; no small task when the body in question is 17 stones of unadulterated muscle. [/p] [p]
The 31-year-old ex-paratrooper's prize for retaining his title at Wembley on Saturday night was &pound;10,000, which does not go far for a full-time body builder who downs half a dozen eggs after his breakfast cereal and eight to 10 chicken breasts a day when &bquo;bulking up&equo;.
Charlie's weekly food bill comes to rather more than &pound;100. [/p] [p]
In his amateur <head>days</head> he was an &bquo;eviction technician&equo; (a fashionable euphemism for bouncer) but such work is regarded as unseemly for the standard bearer of a sport which prides itself in its healthy clean-living image, and he now supplements his income from the few competitions which pay more than a pittance by personal appearances. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40244" docsrc="bnc_B06_1468">
<answer instance="day.40244" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
However, if you are unable to seek professional help, do read one of the following really excellent books which will tell you everything you will ever need to know about healing through diet: Leslie Kenton's [hi]Biogenic Diet [/hi] and Celia Wright's [hi]The Wright Diet [/hi]. [/p] [p]
Briefly, the diet consists of an initial one or two day fruit &bquo;fast&equo;, followed by two weeks on raw fruits and vegetables, nuts, seeds, springwater, juices and herb teas.
Thereafter, you adopt a wholefood diet with a little or no dairy products and no more than one cup of coffee or two cups of tea a day.
I am afraid it is tough (at least at the beginning), as are all restricted diets, but I promise you, it does work!
Incidentally, you will be very pleased to hear that (according to British nutritionist Celia Wright) for [hi]one [/hi] <head>day</head> a week you can and [hi]should [/hi] feast.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40246" docsrc="bnc_CB8_2072">
<answer instance="day.40246" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
According to Allen Pease, in [hi]Body Language &mdash; How to Read Others' Thoughts by Their Gestures [/hi] (Sheldon Press, &pound;4.99).
&bquo;Whenever we call someone &bquo;perceptive&equo; or &bquo;intuitive&equo;, we are referring to his or her ability to read another person's non-verbal cues and to compare these with verbal signals.&equo;
When we have a hunch that somebody is telling lies, for instance, &bquo;what we really mean is that their body language and their spoken words do not agree.&equo;
Women are generally more perceptive in this way than men, he says, but it is something anybody can develop.
He advises setting aside 15 minutes a <head>day</head> to study and consciously interpret her own and other people's gestures and he promises that we will be amazed to find how much our &bquo;intuitions&equo; about people can improve. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40247" docsrc="bnc_AAT_286">
<answer instance="day.40247" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40247" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
However, there appears little support at this stage for the former king's return from his Swiss exile. [/p] [p]
For the moment there are more immediate concerns.
The returning emigres hope for a clean sweep but this has not happened anywhere in Eastern Europe where the price of reconciliation has always been a measure of compromise. [/p] [p]
What worries many here is the claim that in the initial stages the surge for the Securitate men has not been pursued with real vigour.
One guest at the Hotel Bucharest, which saw fierce fighting in the initial stages and now stands deserted, has complained that nobody believed him when he pointed out the leader of the Securitate fighters.
The man managed to disappear in the cellar beneath the kitchen.
He was captured <head>days</head> later however, in another action. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40249" docsrc="bnc_CFN_126">
<answer instance="day.40249" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
The calls for democracy and capitalisation in the post-revolutionary states, alongside the growing prominence of pressure groups as political forces around such issues as the environment, women's demands, anti-racism and demilitarisation, have irreversibly disturbed the political landscape.
They insist in a new and serious appraisal of such ideas as radical liberalism/radical democracy, the community in the nation-state, the changing role of civil society; in short, the form of the political self. [/p] [p]
This conference intends to explore these and other related issues from a number of incisive and contentious angles. [/p] [p]
The discussion will be held in four panel sessions. [/p] [p]
In Association with Marxism Today [gap] [ptr][/p] [note]
adverts from New Scientist 16 February 1991 [/note] [/div1] [div1] [head]
BAYSDAY [/head] [head]
The Carnival of Science AT THE SOUTH KENSINGTON MUSEUMS, LONDON ON SATURDAY 16 MARCH [gap] am &mdash;4pm [/head] [p]
COME ALONG AND JOIN IN A FUN-PACKED <head>DAY</head> OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY FOR ALL AGES [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40250" docsrc="bnc_CH7_763">
<answer instance="day.40250" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Final: Brazil bt Holland 15-12, 15-8, 15-5. [/p] [p]
MEDAL TABLE GldSlvBze Ttl CIS 45 38 29 112 United States 37 34 37 108 Germany 33 21 28 82 China 16 22 16 54 Cuba 14 6 11 31 Spain 13 7 2 22 South Korea 12 5 12 29 Hungary 11 2 7 30 France 8 6 15 29 Australia 7 9 11 27 Italy 6 5 8 19 Canada 6 5 7 18 GT BRITAIN 5 3 12 20 Romania 4 6 8 18 Czech'kia 4 2 1 7 North Korea 4 0 5 9 Japan 3 8 11 22 Bulgaria 3 7 6 16 Poland 3 6 10 19 Holland 2 6 7 15 Kenya 2 4 2 8 Norway 2 4 1 7 Turkey 2 2 2 6 Indonesia 2 2 1 5 Brazil 2 1 0 3 Greece 2 0 0 2 Sweden 1 7 4 12 New Zealand 1 4 5 10 [/p] [/div2] [/div1] [div1] [head]
OUT OF THE FRYING PAN [/head] [head]
MIKE LANGLEY [/head] [p]
ADIOS, Barcelona &mdash; you old frying pan!
Goodbye to your sweaty nights, broiling <head>days</head> , gassy ale and loudspeakers never turned down. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40252" docsrc="bnc_BP1_1436">
<answer instance="day.40252" senseid="time_of_day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40252" senseid="U"/>
<context>
&bquo;From tomorrow, Sarah, I should like you to wear your hair in the style in which it was dressed when you attended the service at the Foundling Hospital,&equo; he said, forcing the smile which gave him a jovial reputation.
&bquo;The severity will be more in keeping with your new responsibilities.&equo; [/p] [p]
He meant it would make her look older and plainer. [/p] [p]
Sarah came through the first week of marriage with few hopes of real happiness, though she was pleased enough with her elevated circumstances.
It was gratifying to have people shake her hand who once wouldn't have given her the time of <head>day</head> , and when she walked through the dreary rooms where evidence of the late Adelaide Morey still abounded she had trouble convincing herself that she was now the mistress here. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40253" docsrc="bnc_AT4_778">
<answer instance="day.40253" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40253" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Jazz did not reply.
His father went out, leaving the small light on.
Jazz reached out for the photograph and held it, examining it closely.
It showed an old Sikh warrior on a pony, glaring at the camera fiercely, a huge spear in his hand.
Behind him in the dust lay a dead tiger.
Jazz looked at it for a long time, then he propped it back against the lamp, and turned the light out. [/p] [p]
He didn't know whether to laugh or cry. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [p]
The next day Mr Foggerty told the four boys to meet him at the Town baths after school. [/p] [p]
&bquo;But we've got to go and help with the horses.
They're coming tonight, Mr Bean said.&equo;
Hoomey's tone of voice indicated that his strength would not be equal to two extra-curricular excursions in one <head>day</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40255" docsrc="bnc_CH6_8219">
<answer instance="day.40255" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Bosses revealed July's High Street sales showed their biggest fall since records began in 1983. [/p] [p]
Credit giant Barclaycard said fear of unemployment is forcing one in three card holders to slash spending. [/p] [p]
And car loan experts HPI announced no end to the slump in new car sales. [/p] [p]
Mr Lamont, who is on holiday in Italy, is banking on a spending boom to boost the economy. [/p] [p]
But despite extra sales, many shopkeepers are facing ruin. [/p] [p]
Worst-hit are clothing and shoe stores where sales crashed even with up to 70 per cent price cuts. [ptr][/p] [caption]
HOPES: Lamont [/caption] [/div1] [div1] [head]
There are some rolls a film star just has to grab&hellip; [/head] [head]
PATSY TAKES HER QUEUE [/head] [head]
NICOLA BRIGGS [/head] [p]
ONE <head>day</head> you're a movie star, the next your rolls are rather less grand. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40256" docsrc="bnc_A99_132">
<answer instance="day.40256" senseid="day_off-0"/>
<context>
No, he asks you to please stay for supper and we'll go on in the morning.
Did Lee Trevino say &bquo;How much?&equo;
Of course not.
Nor anyone &mdash; not one &mdash; down the years, when I've approached such luminaries of the lore as, well, Ashe, Stewart, Prost, Platini, Charlton, Best (he even cooked me breakfast), Coe, Thompson, Cauthen, Francome&hellip; [/p] [p]
This year alone &mdash; the sad one in which British rugby players are apparently rubbing their hands in greedy but pitful expectation &mdash; I've relished long, doubtless tedious (for them) but totally gratis and generous interviews with the likes of Scudamore (on his most precious mid-season afternoon off), Offiah, Gower, Gooch, Border, Simpson, Jacklin, Robson, the teenage millionaire Chang; and even Mansell took a <head>day</head> off to drive me round and round Silverstone. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40258" docsrc="bnc_C9K_2273">
<answer instance="day.40258" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
Consequently, the world inhabited by these gate-keepers abounds with stories of promises made and broken, dreams fulfilled and shattered. [/p] [p]
As a profession A&amp;R is as precarious as politics, with reputations lost just as quickly as they're won.
As a business it's as circumscribed as any other, with A&amp;R departments answerable to what Jeff Young describes as &bquo;men in grey suits&equo; shouting, &bquo;Bottom line!
Bottom line!&equo;. [/p] [p]
Young is the recently appointed A&amp;R Director of MCA Records.
It's an unmentionably early hour of the morning and we're sitting in his Soho office, feasting on take-away toast and cappuccino.
Dressed in American-style sweatshirt and jeans, Young chomps and chats with great enthusiasm.
His <head>days</head> as a Radio 1 DJ are now firmly behind him, but he still likes to trade in extravagant language.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40259" docsrc="bnc_AJT_49">
<answer instance="day.40259" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Dr Williams rang the police himself and was clearly worked up.&equo;
Dr Williams, of Foxham, near Chippenham, admitted a charge of assault by beating and was ordered to pay &pound;300 compensation to Dr Henry with &pound;100 court costs. [/p] [p]
Mr John Greenwood, defending, said: &bquo;There was a certain amount of antipathy between the two doctors.
All of a sudden, the other partners carried out an overnight coup and faced Dr Williams with the situation where he was no longer persona grata. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Dr Williams became a victim of a number of dirty tricks with nasty little jibes and bits of paper through letter boxes.
Things were put in his tyres to cause a puncture, which had him under the most extreme tension and pressure. [/p] [p]
&bquo;On this particular <head>day</head> , he saw a poster contrary to the practice rules about use of the notice board.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40261" docsrc="bnc_CAM_854">
<answer instance="day.40261" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
In the Club section was a tall and clean-cut young man who had made the flight after connecting from Houston.
He worked for a major oil corporation there called Pan-Global and felt he was privileged to be entrusted by his employer, the proprietor himself, with such a discreet mission. [/p] [p]
Not that he had the faintest idea of the contents of the envelope he carried within the breast pocket of the jacket he declined to hand over to the stewardess.
Nor did he wish to know.
He only knew it must contain documents of great corporate sensitivity since it could not be mailed or faxed, or sent by commercial courier pouch. [/p] [p]
His instructions were clear; he had repeated them many times.
He was to go to a certain address on a certain <head>day</head> &mdash; the following day &mdash; at a certain hour.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40262" docsrc="bnc_B3G_1460">
<answer instance="day.40262" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The organisation Relaxation for Living offers cassettes and classes, in some areas of the country. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
For smokers only [/head] [p]
What doctors say is unfortunately true: smoking can lead to cancer and to serious heart and lung diseases such as emphysema and bronchitis.
But giving up will immediately reduce the risk of heart disease, and circulation problems can improve within just weeks.
Eventually the chances of developing lung cancer and other diseases will also be lessened, until they are the same as for non-smokers. [/p] [p]
If you are determined to give up smoking, you are already off to a good start.
You may be able give up gradually, or decide one day to remove everything connected with smoking from your house &mdash; and give up from that day on.
Work out the times of <head>day</head> when the desire for a cigarette is most likely to undermine your good intentions, and be prepared.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40265" docsrc="bnc_ADM_115">
<answer instance="day.40265" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
All the youths seemed interested, so I told them stories of Black Magic in Sussex, a county particularly afflicted by Satan because of all the artistic people who live there, running craft shops or theatrical costumiers. [/p] [p]
&bquo;On Midsummer's Eve, I walked up to Highdown Hill at midnight, below a full moon.
When I saw a fire and capering figures, I ran down again.
The grass all around my feet was alive with black toads.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Do Black Magic people in England attack you?&equo; a Roscommon chip shop boy asked me in awe. [/p] [p]
&bquo;No, they just ask you to go with them.
In Brighton, the worst place for magic, my sister went to a theatrical costumier.
He was dressed as a wizard and the whole place was full of drawings of human sacrifices and magic designs.
She was terrified, but he didn't hurt her.&equo; [/p] [p]
Back in 1959, I had been sitting one <head>day</head> in a Brighton coffee bar aptly named the Thieves' Kitchen.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40266" docsrc="bnc_A6T_2317">
<answer instance="day.40266" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Tony and I get up as quickly as we can, brushing the snow free from clothes before putting them on so that it will not melt with the heat from our bodies.
We tell Nat to stay where he is, brushing the snow from his bag to try to minimize how wet it will be.
The advantage of the temperature being so low &mdash; although it has risen several degrees with the cloud over &mdash; is that the snow is like dry flour and brushes off easily. [/p] [p]
It was late when we woke, and by the time we have cleared up the mess it is later still.
Working outside is difficult in the fresh snow and when the wind picks up again we admit defeat and agree that we will stay another night.
We fix the cowl in the twilight and prepare the evening meal.
Nathan goes outside with the kettle, anxious for some activity, having spent most of the <head>day</head> inside.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40268" docsrc="bnc_CK9_1795">
<answer instance="day.40268" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Mother Francis stared at the enormously fat and none too clean woman.
This is what came of dealing with the common herd.
It was hard to remember that God had made them, too, and that He begged for leniency for them.
Inwardly praying that she might be able to show her piety and understanding, she said, &bquo;Yes, I'm sure it must mean a lot to you.
But, you know, real education never comes cheaply.
And then the child has to be fostered, fed, and provided with a school habit and hood, besides night attire.
Did you ever go to school, Mrs Winkowski?&equo;
God hadn't fully maintained His help to keep condescension from her tone or to prepare her for the answer when it came: &bquo;Yes, I went to school, ma'am.
I started at the early age of five, and I was taught until I was ten, and all <head>day</head> at that.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40269" docsrc="bnc_ABA_82">
<answer instance="day.40269" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
British Commonwealth links, though gossamer thin for most of the time, can become emotional ties of steel in times of crisis, drawing us into unexpected military commitments, as occurred in the Falklands Campaign.
They remember also that the Dominions came voluntarily to our aid in the two world wars: we would be in honour bound to do likewise if any of them came under threat.
Nonetheless, the Maritime school accept that our forces should be deployed primarily to support the First and Second Pillars, but argue that they must also be given the strategic mobility, equipment, and training to continue Britain's global role as required by the Third Pillar. [/p] [p]
British Defence policy, unlike her grand strategy, is written, re-written, written about and debated annually in the Defence White Papers, in which the government of the <head>day</head> makes its case for military expenditure for the coming year.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40271" docsrc="bnc_AM4_563">
<answer instance="day.40271" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
By this time the rivers Camel and Allen had been polluted with aluminium, killing 60,000 trout and salmon.
Pilkington talked to Dr Richard Newman, who was out on an early morning call, on the Thursday.
He watched in disbelief as water gushed from the fire hydrants and flowed down the road into the river, where the fish were dying.
The SWWA had opened the hydrants at night to try and clear out the system before the town woke up. [/p] [p]
The attempt failed and no warning was given to the public.
Pilkington recounts how when Winifred Harper turned on her tap, &bquo;out came a yellowy, stinking acerbic fluid which curdled the milk&equo;.
She, like others, telephoned the Water Authority and was reassured that the water was safe to drink.
Still, it tasted so bad she had to make sugary coffee instead of tea.
&bquo;For the first few <head>days</head> ,&equo; wrote Pilkington, &bquo;it was all quite humorous.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40272" docsrc="bnc_B3K_1009">
<answer instance="day.40272" senseid="P"/>
<answer instance="day.40272" senseid="the_good_old_days-0"/>
<context>
January to June What's On Guide [/head] [gap] [div2] [head]
Buy a Seat Scheme [/head] [p]
As part of the major refurbishment to this warm intimate Music Hall we propose to renew the seats giving, extra legroom in extremely comfortable seats. [/p] [p]
For just &pound;30 a year for four years you can buy one of the 550 seats available and have it names after you or someone of your choice. [/p] [p]
Buying a seat means a permanent and privileged association with our world famous Music Hall bringing you a number of attractive benefits: [list] [item]
A theatre seat named after you or someone of your choice. [/item] [item]
Acknowledgement of your seat donation on permanent display in the theatre. [/item] [item]
The opportunity to win a champagne evening for two at the Good Old <head>Days</head> . [/item] [item]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40274" docsrc="bnc_AR5_1209">
<answer instance="day.40274" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
A registered charity, all dogs and prospective owners are vetted and this accounts for the high success rate but it must be kept in mind that people who need to find a new home for their dog usually have a problem, or a problem dog.
Be careful: it may be a problem passed on to you. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
Choosing the Right Puppy [/head] [p]
So often, I have watched people pick over one of our litters, sometimes nervous or apologetic for taking so long.
I tell them to take their time; it is hoped that the dog will be with them for the next ten years or more &mdash; what are a few minutes?
If you need help, just ask.
It is extremely important to go to an experienced breeder with a proven track record; [pb] he will have seen the litter every <head>day</head> and will know each pup's individual character, faults and virtues. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40275" docsrc="bnc_CM4_2438">
<answer instance="day.40275" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Impossible.&equo; [/p] [p]
Was she telling the truth?
[hi]He did not know. [/hi] [/p] [p]
&bquo;In that case,&equo; said Jaq, &bquo;let us drop back into true space.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;And lose the scent of Carnelian?
While we dilly-dally in the ordinary universe, his ship will forge onward through the warp out of my range.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Surely you can transmit from the warp.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I'm sure I wouldn't know how, Inquisitor.
That's quite outside of my experience.
If I was trained in that, I've forgotten long since.
Please recall how I've been penned in a sanctum on a planet for most of my <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40277" docsrc="bnc_A66_1239">
<answer instance="day.40277" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
It was hesitant about its role, and indeed divided within itself over doctrinal issues like the significance of the Resurrection, and over such indicators of change as the ordination of women.
Wags commented on a search for &bquo;closet Christians&equo; among the bishops.
But here again was a major institution in the land in clear conflict with the determined woman who bestrode government &mdash; and actually appointed bishops and archbishops as well (though they often disappointed her).
The doctors, the architects, and, after 1987, the legal profession were all to face the same mood of antagonism. [/p] [p]
No group in society, however, symbolized the alienation of key institutions from the government more clearly than did the university teachers.
The wheel had come full circle since the heady <head>days</head> of expansion after the Robbins Report in 1963.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40278" docsrc="bnc_CBV_2200">
<answer instance="day.40278" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
National Savings announced lower rates on many other products on 5 August; again, this is believed to be a move to prevent a rise in mortgage rates. [ptr][ptr][/p] [caption]
BUILDING SOCIETIES [/caption] [caption]
Less pain from inflation [/caption] [p]
For investors still concerned about the possibility of inflation's remaining a problem, Britannia Building Society's Index Linked Account is well worth considering. [/p] [p]
The account pays interest at 4.5% gross over the headline retail price index.
The interest rate is adjusted on the 23rd of each month after publication of the RPI. [/p] [p]
Minimum investment is &pound;1,000 and the maximum &pound;500,000.
Interest is paid quarterly in January, April, July and October; basic rate tax is deducted. [/p] [p]
Withdrawals can be made penalty free if 90 <head>days</head> ' notice is given; instant access means 90 days' loss of interest.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40280" docsrc="bnc_CCU_1129">
<answer instance="day.40280" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
9.1 [gap] shall initially decide whether or not proceedings shall be brought against third parties, and shall name the conduct of any such proceedings, where these are based upon infringement or the Trade Marks or [gap] 's copyright or other intellectual property rights in the Work or the Converted Text or the Work.
In the prosecution of any such proceedings, [gap] agrees at [gap] 's expense to execute such documents and do such things as may be necessary in the opinion of [gap] 's Counsel to carry out such prosecution, including without limitation, joining as a party.
[gap] shall pay the legal fees and costs of both parties incurred in the prosecution of such proceedings and shall be solely entitled to any monetary recovery by way of settlement or judgement. [/p] [p]
On [gap] 's refusal within thirty (30) <head>days</head> notice from [gap] to bring any such proceedings, [gap] shall have the right to bring any such proceedings at its own expense and with the full cooperation of [gap]. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40281" docsrc="bnc_B11_443">
<answer instance="day.40281" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
In retrospect, perhaps we played on the heart-strings of our listeners too heavily, but it was, in actual fact, a hearty, healthy exercise in a good cause for the &bquo;benefit&equo; of the community, and in defiance of the written and spoken diatribes of a federal political bureaucracy. [/p] [p]
Thus it was that we made use of every method in the book to fan into flame the natural resentment of the public against a big and unfair bully kicking a man when he was down.
People offered to raise whatever sum of money needed to keep the Community Radio Station on the air; even those who never cared or listened much, now felt that 1OAB must be preserved!
As the <head>day</head> of &bquo;our final hour&equo; approached our publicity releases continued to whip up public opinion, and I carefully planned the last programme for broadcast from 9pm on the last evening until the station's license expired with the stroke of midnight.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40283" docsrc="bnc_A6T_1890">
<answer instance="day.40283" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Next backwards comes a waft of dog fart.
In the days that follow we learn about this smell, which varies from [hi]ugh [/hi]! and a turn of the head to really gut-wrenching.
Tonight it is just another sensation. [/p] [caption]
Sledge dog [/caption] [caption]
Taiga [/caption] [caption]
Dawn sledging, Rostadalen [/caption] [p]
When it is my turn on the sledge the experience is incomparable.
Not like learning to drive a car, not even like riding a horse.
There is a sense of isolation from the rest of the world, a sense of the power in the dogs, and a wonderful feeling of being in control, but only just.
It is perhaps like being on top of a big wave in a canoe or on a surfboard, but to try to describe it is to fail. [/p] [p]
The following <head>day</head> we packed Odd-Knut's depressed Volvo.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40284" docsrc="bnc_AR0_850">
<answer instance="day.40284" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40284" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
When John A. Droege came to write his classic work on the American station in 1916, he regarded train-sheds as beyond the pale: [quote] [p]
The day of the great awkward arched train shed is long since gone.
There was a time when in railroad terminal architecture it was considered as the most necessary adjunct (or evil).
It will long remain a problem to the average person that these sheds had such wide popularity and that so little use was made of the cheaper, cleaner, or, in fact, better umbrella sheds.
In view of the widespread use of the old style train sheds it is pleasing to our vanity to be reminded how expensive they were to build and how costly to maintain.
And what is more, the sheds are dark and dirty, the coldest places in town on cold <head>days</head> , the stuffiest on hot. [/p] [/quote] [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40286" docsrc="bnc_CEN_4098">
<answer instance="day.40286" senseid="rainy_day-0"/>
<context>
The 14-year-old boy had heated the forceps on a Bunsen burner in the lab at Beaumont School, St Albans, Herts, an industrial tribunal was told yesterday. [/p] [p]
The teacher claimed that the boy put the forceps in his hand, but the pupil said Mr Harrison had picked them up from a desk. [/p] [p]
Mr Harrison, 59, of Welwyn Garden City, a science master for 30 years, claims unfair dismissal, which Hertfordshire County Council denies.
The Bedford tribunal was told he had been warned previously about slapping pupils. [/p] [p]
The hearing continues. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
&pound;60m paid off as we save for rainy day [/head] [head]
By Paul Wilenius, Political Editor [/head] [p]
JOB loss fears are forcing millions of consumers to save for a rainy <head>day</head> rather than borrow, it was revealed yesterday. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40287" docsrc="bnc_ADY_3206">
<answer instance="day.40287" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
For instance, Perkin thought in wood, like a language.
Any trap he made would be wooden. [/p] [p]
Nolan had knocked Perkin down at Tremayne's dinner.
I'd picked Nolan up and made a fool of him.
Perkin wouldn't have [pb] risked any way to kill me that meant creeping up on me, not after what he'd seen. [/p] [p]
Perkin had had to get over the shock of finding my familiar ski-jacket and boots in the boathouse and then the far worse shock of the cataclysmic reversal of his scheme when Harry and I both lived. [/p] [p]
The best actor of them all, he had contained those shocks within himself with no screaming crises of nerves.
Many a convicted murderer had displayed that sort of control.
Maybe it was something to do with a divorce from reality.
There were books on the subject.
One <head>day</head> I might read them. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40289" docsrc="bnc_CEK_2366">
<answer instance="day.40289" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
HOW much would you expect to pay for a dress modelled by Linda Evangelista? &pound;15,000? &pound;25,000? [/p] [p]
That would be the normal price bracket for a Dior or Chanel creation &mdash; but now the supermodels have gone from catwalk to catalogue.
And that means you can buy an outfit &bquo;as worn by Linda, Naomi or Claudia&equo; for as little as &pound;9.99. [/p] [p]
Six supermodels feature in the new spring/summer Littlewoods home shopping catalogue, and though they all charge up to &pound;10,000 for a single day's work the clothes they model for Littlewoods are all within easy reach of every woman. [/p] [p]
Linda and Co are used to wearing the most luxurious quality fabrics, cut by the world's top couturiers to fit their finely-tuned bodies to perfection.
So what did they make of these budget off-the-peg outfits which the rest of us wear every <head>day</head> ? [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40290" docsrc="bnc_BNU_1009">
<answer instance="day.40290" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Then he lifted the body so that the blood dribbled over the stones and spilt on to the ground in front of him, where it was littered with the remains of other, older offerings &mdash; dead flowers, grains of rice and barley, a few coins. [/p] [p]
Late that night there was a feast of rice and meat. [/p] [p]
Two weeks later Sigarup was still weak.
He couldn't stand or walk alone and the muscle in his leg had withered badly.
But his face was full and there was colour in his cheeks.
He talked and laughed a lot, and practised walking with his crutch.
Every day he rubbed some ointment on his leg.
It was red and smelled of perfume.
He'd bought it in the Bazaar from an Indian trader who told him it would make the muscle grow. [/p] [p]
In the month of S&amacr;un, Kalchu and Sigarup set out together across the mountains on a pilgrimage to R&amacr;n&amacr;m&amacr;che Lake.
On the night of the full moon, people gathered there from as far afield as B&amacr;rakot, twelve <head>days</head> ' walk away.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40292" docsrc="bnc_CGH_1649">
<answer instance="day.40292" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
A few days ago I again removed the brood of one of these [hi]A. aluaudi [/hi] females and counted a record 113 fry. [/p] [p]
The other two species of Victorians also spawned in the Malawi tank. [/p] [p]
The green [hi]N. nigricans [/hi] male and his female spawned with little interference from the Malawis.
The female producing 22 young after only 11 days incubation. [/p] [p]
in this same tank the Flameback male was hurtling around in full breeding colours.
The colour photos I have seen of this fish just do not do him justice. [/p] [p]
His upper body, dorsal and tail are a rich orange, his lower body bright green, and his chin, chest and short triangular pelvic fins a dramatic contrast of jet black. [/p] [p]
He spawned with two females in the next few <head>days</head> and they produced 82 and 64 fry. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40293" docsrc="bnc_CR8_2442">
<answer instance="day.40293" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Given the clarity of your diagnosis, why then do you waffle when offering recommendations for reform?
You suggest continuous realignments, wider bands and &bquo;soft buffers&equo; (which in effect means no bands at all).
Back to floating is hardly what one expects to hear from The Economist, which understands the threat this poses to Europe's single market.
If Hoover's decision to move a couple of hundred jobs from Dijon to Scotland was enough to provoke an uproar, imagine the corrosive effect on political support for the Single European Act of additional competitive devaluations. [/p] [p]
More surprise realignments, the Bundesbank's preference, are not feasible when capital flows are unfettered.
The markets are smart enough to guess when a realignment is coming.
You can fool them once by realigning in the middle of the trading <head>day</head> , as Spain did recently.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40295" docsrc="bnc_C9R_1926">
<answer instance="day.40295" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Cope confidently and calmly with whatever is waiting on the other side of it. [/p] [/item] [/list] [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Planned participation [/head] [p]
A person with impaired hearing has to take a lot more strain than people with normal hearing.
It should be recognized and accepted that coping with hearing loss can be utterly exhausting. [/p] [p]
Do not continue to meet and talk with people non-stop all the time.
Plan periods when there is no need to be with anyone and when there is an opportunity to relax and to recharge energy. [/p] [p]
Any recreation which means continually trying to understand other people (for example, the small group when the conversation rushes about like a squashball) is very far from recreation.
It is likely to be a depressing experience if one is already tired after a <head>day</head> 's work and possibly even more frustrating with background noise and dim lights. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40296" docsrc="bnc_AHU_1118">
<answer instance="day.40296" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
On their forays to Britain they employed ridicule against the snobbery of golf clubs which insisted that the golfing untouchables must change their boots in the pro's shop.
BETWEEN rounds, two a day at that period, Cotton and Toots would stroll to the car park where the chauffeur unpacked the Fortnum and Mason hamper from the back of the hired Rolls and set up folding chairs and table for an al fresco repast of caviar and champagne. [/p] [p]
As they surveyed their steak and kidney pud and overcooked cabbage in the clubhouse the members began to get the message. [/p] [p]
Victory in the Open in 1934 changed everything, as Cotton knew it would.
His win ended 11 years of American domination of the championship.
He was a national hero and now he had the leverage to change golf. [/p] [p]
These <head>days</head> golf managers parcel up their clients rather like those butchers' pictures of carcases with dotted lines showing the different joints.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40298" docsrc="bnc_CFT_4215">
<answer instance="day.40298" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40298" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Beautifully maintained, only one season in salt water.
Located in Great Lakes. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
SWAN 44 &bquo;PICKPOCKET&equo; (1973): [/head] [p]
Tall rig.
New engine '90, epoxy bottom, teak decks in excellent condition.
Harken roller furling, extensive sail wardrobe, B&amp;G 390 system, electronics new in '88.
Interior without blemish, beautifully maintained.
Call Newport office for brochure. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
SWAN 42 &bquo;SWANSONG&equo; (1984): [/head] [p]
There cannot be another 42 with so little use, this boat is in as new condition.
Rarely used for <head>day</head> sailing in New England during the summer months and &bquo;winterized&equo; for most of the year.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40299" docsrc="bnc_CHG_1500">
<answer instance="day.40299" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
&bquo;But what about money?&equo;
I asked.
&bquo;Surely &mdash; &bquo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;If they do want something that costs extra, there's always a way to make a few pennies.
There's about fifty Europeans on the island &mdash; including Americans &mdash; and there's plenty of men anxious to do a bit of gardening, or women ready to earn a day's wages doing the laundry &mdash; you saw them at work &mdash; or sewing.
There are fifty times as many Singer sewing machines as motor cars in Koraloona.
And the ship's chandler is always needing spare hands when a boat comes in.
So is Mick the barman.
But they work when there's fun in it, not to live.
Since most people own a plot of land, they have everything they need to keep alive.
A <head>day</head> 's casual work takes on an extra meaning.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40301" docsrc="bnc_B1X_3112">
<answer instance="day.40301" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40301" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
&bquo;Where is that little&hellip; little&hellip;?&equo;
He was apoplectic with anger. [/p] [p]
&bquo;She's gone away with Con Gallagher,&equo; Peg answered coolly.
&bquo;They're probably married by now,&equo; she added, not bothering to disguise the satisfaction in her voice. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Where to?&equo;
Bull O'Malley choked.
&bquo;Where to?&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;I don't know.
Dublin, England maybe.&equo; [/p] [p]
He wanted to smash everything about him into smithereens, but he managed with iron self-will to control himself. [/p] [p]
&bquo;By Christ, that little bitch will regret this to her dyin' <head>day</head> !&equo;
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40302" docsrc="bnc_AAV_688">
<answer instance="day.40302" senseid="day-4"/>
<context>
Quickly and certainly Remove all Obstructions arising from any Cause Whatever where Steel and Pennyroyal fails.&equo; [/p] [p]
If the anti-abortion campaigners have their way advertisements like these, and for similar dangerous products, will no doubt reappear.
If the choice facing us were legal, clean, decently performed abortion or none at all, no doubt many of us would be hard put to it to vote for the former; but in fact the choice is between the legal, clean sort and backstreet self-induced efforts of the Ottey's Pills variety.
And if the anti-abortionists succeed in 1990, I and others of my ilk will once again be begged, somehow, to help the unwillingly pregnant.
Well that's what Christmas is all about, isn't it?
Keeping up the good old traditions. [/p] [p]
BOXING <head>Day</head> and we launch ourselves on our own family tradition &mdash; a visit to the theatre.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40304" docsrc="bnc_BPH_460">
<answer instance="day.40304" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The Southwark Court of Requests was still functioning, and the process there was initiated by a tradesman or individual lodging a complaint against another for non-payment of money owed, after less formal requests had been ignored.
He went to the court where he found himself dubbed the plaintiff, paid a fee and a deposit for which he received a receipt.
If he was suing for less than 20s in 1830 he left a deposit of 5s; 7s 6d for one between 20s and 40s; 10s between 40s and 60s, and 12s 6d for 60s.
He gave the Clerk of the Court his name and that of the person he was suing whom the clerk called the defendant. [gap] [pb] [/p] [p]
This action by the creditor set in motion the issuing, by the clerk, of a writ or summons which was formally delivered to an officer of the Chief Bailiff who served it on the defendant at his house.
It told him to come to the court on a certain <head>day</head> to defend himself before a Commissioner and the man who said he owed him money.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40305" docsrc="bnc_CRY_1803">
<answer instance="day.40305" senseid="early_days-0"/>
<context>
More hours did generally mean more advertising revenue for ITV, and the companies frequently pressed the government for expansion.
In 1972 restrictions were lifted.
ITV and BBC1 were both soon broadcasting some 13 hours a day (the main change being an extension of afternoon hours) &mdash; double the amount 20 years earlier.
Breakfast time TV and Channel 4 doubled them again, so that by the late 1980s each network was putting out 200 hours a week.
Viewers thus went from a choice of less than 30 hours a week in 1946 to more than 400 in the late 1980s.
By 1990 you could watch TV round the clock. [ptr][pb] [/p] [note]
pp. 137&ndash;138: TABLE(S) [/note] [p]
The programme categories in Tables 6.7 and 6.8 reflect the broadcasters' need to demonstrate that they were &bquo;informing, educating and entertaining&equo;.
The tables give an idea also of the kind of programming that was practical in the early <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40307" docsrc="bnc_A0R_1952">
<answer instance="day.40307" senseid="day_off-0"/>
<context>
The television showed two children chasing each other round a car, shrieking.
A woman and a man were packing a hamper, blankets and Wellingtons into the car.
&bquo;Trevor Newsom,&equo; said Derek Carlisle, &bquo;is now on Luctia, having just arrived from Vasca where he earlier recorded the interview we have just seen.&equo; [/p] [p]
An exhausted-looking Trevor walked into the picture.
He approached the man.
&bquo;Today is Tuesday,&equo; he said, &bquo;a working day.
Could you tell us why you are not at work?&equo; [/p] [p]
The man replied.
&bquo;Nothing to preserve now the Vascars have no limbs to sell to us.
May as well live in the present, that's what I say.
You ought to have a <head>day</head> off yourself.&equo; [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40308" docsrc="bnc_ALC_987">
<answer instance="day.40308" senseid="time_of_day-0"/>
<context>
Five areas &mdash; Derbyshire, Leicestershire, Cumbria, Powys and Wester Ross &mdash; all demonstrated a marked preference for afternoon meetings.
The first four of these had mainly family farms and the pattern was understandable but the Wester Ross response was more difficult to explain. [/p] [p]
For most of the farmers time off would have to be taken, either as holiday or unpaid leave.
Their willingness to do so indicated a strong desire to participate in training.
Wives also chose afternoons: the bulk of the outside work and the housework being finished they could attend knowing they would arrive home in time for the children returning from school. [/p] [p]
Although fewer chose mornings, some areas &mdash; South Wales, North Yorkshire and Orkney &mdash; gave as much weight to this rime of <head>day</head> as the afternoon.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40310" docsrc="bnc_B34_570">
<answer instance="day.40310" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The stage costumes were ornate, the hemline above the knee and worn with knickers massed with frills so that no outline of the leg could be seen.
That would have been considered vulgar.
Often the skirt was frilled as well making it impossible for the audience to see where the skirt ended and the knickers began.
Tights, which Jane had to pay for herself, were made of thickish cotton and fastened with a coin each side and taped.
They rarely showed their hair on stage as enormous head-dresses or wigs were worn. [/p] [p]
As well as her tights, Jane had to bear the cost of tipping the callboy and dresser every week.
The other Girls would have had to send money home but Jane set aside a similar sum to tide her over periods of unemployment.
The morning rehearsals each <head>day</head> were a Tiller rule not demanded by the management and so were not paid for.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40311" docsrc="bnc_CA7_1226">
<answer instance="day.40311" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40311" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
After Canhas there is a road to the right &mdash; which it is very easy to miss &mdash; which leads up to Pa&uacute;l da Serra and one of the alternative routes through to Porto do Moniz.
On the way up we pass the statue of &bquo;Senhor da Montanha&equo; which was begun in 1962 and weighs six tonnes.
The plateau of Pa&uacute;l da Serra itself is an extensive moorland area where there was once a proposal to build an international airport.
There are good or bad weather days here, and nothing in between.
On good days there is glorious sunshine with clear, cloudless skies, and in summer the air is pleasantly fresher and cooler than down at sea-level.
Then you can picnic, play football or cricket or just walk across the moorland and look at the sheep.
On bad <head>days</head> it rains and the mist covers everything in silence &mdash; you can see only a few yards in front of you and, if you wander from the road, can easily get lost.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40313" docsrc="bnc_AR8_1183">
<answer instance="day.40313" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Aircraft landing at LG 05 were seen and a recce of LG 121 confirmed that it was only used as a decoy at night.
Captain Schott's party was picked up by Timpson on the night of 13 July, but Warr's failed to arrive. [quote] [p]
The following night a recce. party went out to see if Capt. Warr had arrived.
He had not.
In the meantime, Timpson and myself had planned to strafe the road at Bug Bug on the night 15/16 July.
We set out to carry this out and passed through our old rendezvous on route.
There we found Capt. Warr and party, all very tired and [pb] fatigued owing to lack of food and water for four days. [/p] [p]
We set out the same night for Bug Bug, but failed to make our objective owing to the bad nature of the ground for the vehicles.
We all returned to the RV and spent next <head>day</head> servicing vehicles etc&hellip;.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40314" docsrc="bnc_ASC_527">
<answer instance="day.40314" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
John described it to many interviewers as if the free lessons were a concession in return for taking part in performances, but it would be more realistic to regard the performances by the University of Cape Town Ballet as a valuable part of his ballet education. [/p] [p]
Before joining the Cape Town school, John had seen performances by the Cape Town Ballet Club, which paid its first visit to Johannesburg for a week at the Empire Theatre from 6 December 1943.
It had only one skilled male dancer on its strength, Lionel Luyt, and in the first of their two programmes he had to partner the ballerina in the second act of [hi]Swan Lake [/hi], then dance both the Prince and Bluebird in [hi]Aurora's Wedding [/hi] (with just three minutes to change costumes) and finally lead the cast of [hi]Prince Igor [/hi].
Cecily Robinson brought her three leading dancers, Patricia Murphy, Lillian Graham and Luyt, to Johannesburg four <head>days</head> early, so that they could become used to the high altitude, which would affect their breathing, and to the steep rake of the stage.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40316" docsrc="bnc_AA9_201">
<answer instance="day.40316" senseid="early_days-0"/>
<context>
O SAMBA: Brazil Classics II, compiled by David Byrne (WEA 926019). [/p] [p]
LITTLE RICHARD: The Speciality Sessions (Ace AboxCD1). [/p] [p]
IT SEEMS appropriate to end the Eighties with the band that decided that this decade was quite enough.
Felt started out 10 years ago and recorded 10 albums before breaking up this week after a final show in their home town, Birmingham, thus concluding the curious master-plan that was apparently drawn up early in their career by the band's singer and song-writer, who is known simply as Lawrence. [/p] [p]
Before departing, they recorded a final album that, in their typically quirky style, proves to be their best since the early <head>days</head> of Crumbling The Antiseptic Beauty, even if there are moments when Lawrence comes close to outclassing Morrissey in the annals of wimp rock.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40317" docsrc="bnc_A7J_1498">
<answer instance="day.40317" senseid="early_days-0"/>
<context>
He was worried about her silence.
It wasn't like her.
He would be coming over by boat and a male nurse would come with him as far as D&uacute;n Laoghaire.
He could travel well enough on his own, if only they'd let him.
But that was the way they did things over there &mdash; well-meaning but fussy. [/p] [p]
She would have to drag herself out of her lethargy and write.
Some patients got others to write for them when they were low, but there was nothing Lily wanted to say to Vincent that she [pb] could ask anyone to write.
She seemed to lack all will or decision.
In the early <head>days</head> after the operation, when she was tightly bound in a many-tailed bandage to which weights were sometimes attached, and with drainage tubes still trailing from her, she had managed to scribble notes to him almost every other day.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40319" docsrc="bnc_BPG_499">
<answer instance="day.40319" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
But these days most people would agree that regular whole body continuous exercise, such as brisk fitness walking, is an effective way of losing weight, particularly fat. [/p] [p]
And it works for several reasons: [list] [label]
1 [/label] [item] [p]
IT'S AEROBIC &mdash; The key to walking aerobically is to walk at a pace of 3.5 &mdash; 4.0 miles per hour for a minimum of 20 minutes, during which time the heart rate is elevated to 60&ndash;85 per cent of its [/p] [/item] [/list] [pb] [list] [item]
maximum.
Below 60 per cent the exercise will not have an aerobic effect and only very fit people can gain any aerobic effect above the 85 per cent level (see Table 3). [/item] [/list] [gap] [/p] [p]
If you think about it, air is essentially the &bquo;breath of life&equo;.
We cannot live without it, but many of us are living each <head>day</head> with too little of it.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40320" docsrc="bnc_CL1_341">
<answer instance="day.40320" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
Jim Wharton for example, born in Virginia in 1813 (five years before Molyneux's death in Scotland at the age of 34), campaigned in England in the 1830s.
In the second half of the century, Britain received, amongst others, Bob Smith from Washington DC and Bob Travers, who was noted for his contests against Jem Mace and Patsy Reardon. [/p] [p]
Slightly later came heavyweight Peter Jackson, born in St Croix, West Indies, in 1861, four years before emancipation.
He travelled as a seaman to Sydney where he won the Australian heavyweight title before transferring to San Francisco where he was persuaded by the Earl of Lonsdale to operate in England, a move which enhanced his status greatly, as a contemporary noted: &bquo;I knew him in the <head>days</head> of his greatness when sitting on top of the pugilistic world, f&ecirc;ted and lionized, he might well have been excused some slight vanity&equo; (quoted by Henderson, 1949, pp.20&ndash;1).
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40322" docsrc="bnc_CEE_295">
<answer instance="day.40322" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Always, though, whether immediately or eventually, she would acquiesce, and I resented her acquiescence, not only because of its consequences for myself, but because I didn't understand why she, an adult, would not or could not stand up to him.
Erikson sums up the situation well: [quote] [p]
The polarity adult-child is the first in the inventory of existential oppositions (male-female being the second) which makes man exploitable and induces him to exploit.
The child's inborn proclivity for feeling powerless, deserted, ashamed and guilty in relation to those on whom he depends is systematically utilised for his training, often to the point of exploitation. [/p] [/quote] [/p] [p]
The Eleven-plus, like all crises, threatened the pattern of family relationships, and all the family could do in order to maintain equilibrium was to ensure that each member remain entrenched in or return to his or her habitual role.
And I should perhaps add that to this <head>day</head> I am practically innumerate. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40323" docsrc="bnc_A7Y_329">
<answer instance="day.40323" senseid="U"/>
<answer instance="day.40323" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Stephanie cannot duplicate the essential therapies and stimulation the school provides.
&bquo;What will happen to his small world when it all stops?&equo; she asks.
&bquo;He'll just have me.&equo;
Doctors say Jonathan will have a normal life-span and she is worried for the future and what will happen to him after her death.
There are community therapists, but not enough to go around.
They are poorly paid, mainly young and female, have little chance of career progression and no incentive to remain in the profession.
Those available will be busy rehabilitating stroke patients, who take priority. [/p] [p]
Fears that handicapped youngsters will deteriorate are well founded.
Ian Squires, severely autistic, returned to Islington in 1986 from a residential school where he'd been happy.
He waited months for a <head>day</head> centre place; when he got one it was unsuitable and he refused to go.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40325" docsrc="bnc_CAL_138">
<answer instance="day.40325" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The proposal leaves open the possibility of criminal proceedings in Britain against anyone who leaks EC information.
People working for the commission will be vetted, according to the procedures of their own country &mdash; which means, in Britain, secret vetting by MI5.
This week, the civil liberties group, Statewatch, has published the text of the EC's proposal. [/p] [p]
The reason for a new secrecy law is that, post-Maastricht, the EC is getting more and more involved in contentious areas like defence, foreign affairs, and asylum policies &mdash; part of the famous &bquo;ever closer union between the peoples of Europe&equo;.
But there doesn't seem to be much in it for the peoples themselves. [/p] [/div2] [/div1] [div1] [head]
FOURTH ESTATE A regular monitor of the Tory press [/head] [p]
[hi]6 May: [/hi] The <head>day</head> before the local elections.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40326" docsrc="bnc_CEP_5250">
<answer instance="day.40326" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Swimming is probably the best form of exercise you can get, and I doubt Sutton will be able to beat us for fitness.&equo; [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Yeovil out for revenge [/head] [p]
YEOVIL TOWN seek their 15th Football League scalp at Torquay United today. [/p] [p]
Player-manager Steve Rutter is quietly confident.
He said: &bquo;We played Torquay three years ago and were very unlucky to go out 1&ndash;0 at their place after a replay.
We've got a better side now and Torquay are struggling a bit. [/p] [p]
&bquo;I would put our chances at 50&ndash;50 &mdash; and you can't really ask for more than that. [/p] [p]
&bquo;There's not a lot between us now.
A lot of players are being released by League clubs these <head>days</head> that would have been kept on before, so they end up in the Conference. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40328" docsrc="bnc_CLS_143">
<answer instance="day.40328" senseid="early_days-0"/>
<context>
At first they were a novelty and a fad but, perhaps even to the surprise of many in the trade, they were a novelty that did not fade.
There was something about the movies although not too many people stopped to ask what it was.
Analysis only came later.
It was in 1927 for example that Kenneth Macpherson speculated whether those early film audiences had not just been distracted and drawn mindlessly from the streets but rather it might have been a case of &bquo;the people getting in some dim way the fact that there was something under their eyes, a sense of life and expectancy&equo;. [/p] [p]
Whether we take Lorentz's view that the masses were bored and ready to be distracted or Macpherson's notion that they had sensed that the movies were at least hinting at new possibilities, it is difficult to avoid being swept along by the romance of those early <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40329" docsrc="bnc_CRD_179">
<answer instance="day.40329" senseid="day-4"/>
<context>
The centralised technical control, exercised by the chief engineer's department at headquarters, meant that the men who had accepted these posts were to find their room for independent and creative action significantly more constrained than was the case for their colleagues in the Area Boards.
The extent to which management powers over generation were devolved depended on the central triumvirate of Citrine, Self and Hacking, and not on a statutorily entrenched position.
It is a measure of the fundamental instincts of Citrine and his colleagues that, where they had the greater power to centralise, it was centralisation, and not devolved responsibility, which was their watchword. [/p] [p]
As vesting <head>day</head> , 1 April 1948, approached, the shape of the organisations which were to take over the industry, and the men who were going to lead them at national and regional level were known.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40331" docsrc="bnc_CEK_4006">
<answer instance="day.40331" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Eleven-year-old Michelle Redshaw from Yorkshire hadn't been swimming since part of her small intestine was removed and she had an ileostomy bag fitted. [/p] [p]
But by the second day of the adventure, her escort was having trouble getting her out of the pool. [/p] [p]
Many of the children had never been away from home before and there were inevitable bouts of homesickness but the Dreamflight team worked hard to make them feel at ease. [/p] [p]
Lorna Marsh initially turned down the chance to go on the trip when she found out that Bingo The Clown would be joining them. [/p] [p]
Bingo, alias Trevor Pharo, said: &bquo;Lorna had a clown phobia.
In particular, she didn't like clowns' mouths.
So I went to meet her without my make-up on and demonstrated how I made myself up. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Gradually she got used to the idea.&equo; [/p] [p]
By the second <head>day</head> of the trip, Lorna was laughing and joking with Trevor in his clown gear. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40332" docsrc="bnc_CH5_3066">
<answer instance="day.40332" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40332" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
It'd be best if Tony died [/head] [head]
STEPHEN WHITE [/head] [p]
IT'S the nightmare no parent should face&hellip; wishing their own son would die. [/p] [p]
But for Allan and Barbara Bland a daily visit to their son's hospital bedside makes them wish for an end to his twilight world. [/p] [p]
Tony Bland didn't die in the Hillsborough soccer tragedy, but he didn't [corr] survive [/corr] it, either. [/p] [p]
Since he was pulled from under a pile of 40 bodies over three years ago he has been in a coma, unlikely ever to recover.
A life support machine pumps liquid food into his body. [/p] [p]
And every day Allan and Barbara and the doctors treating him have to face the dilemma of keeping alive the boy they feel would be better off dead. [/p] [p]
Tony is one of two silent victims of that fateful <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40334" docsrc="bnc_BNW_237">
<answer instance="day.40334" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
[hi]Voluntary unemployment can be defined as consisting of all those persons who are not in paid employment and are receiving some form of social security benefit, but are not actually seeking jobs at the prevailing rate of real wages [/hi].
This includes those who are temporarily between jobs and drawing unemployment benefit to tide them over until the new job is taken up.
It also includes those who prefer to remain unemployed, believing that their incomes from social security benefits do not make it worthwhile to take up a job. [/p] [p]
In the UK since October 1982, the number of people unemployed has been measured for official purposes as the number of &bquo;people claiming benefit (that is, unemployment benefit, supplementary benefits or national insurance credits) at Unemployment Benefit Offices on the <head>day</head> of the monthly count, who on that day were unemployed and able and willing to do any suitable work&equo;.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40335" docsrc="bnc_CBC_5835">
<answer instance="day.40335" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40335" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
For although thousands of people meet their partners in the workplace, an office affair is a sackable offence. [/p] [p]
As many couples have found, often only one half of the relationship will be asked to leave.
And it's nearly always the woman. [/p] [p]
But an employer can legally sack you or your partner if he can prove it is disruptive of other work relationships, it could harm business or that it affects job performance. [/p] [p]
Even married couples working for the same firm can be fired if the boss can prove that their relationship makes their employment impractical, or that it is against company policy. [/p] [p]
Ann Tomen, a marketing assistant, knows all about that.
She married a colleague who then left to work for a rival firm.
Within <head>days</head> , Ann was demoted because of the risk of an &bquo;inadvertent information leak&equo;. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40337" docsrc="bnc_ABR_344">
<answer instance="day.40337" senseid="rest_day-0"/>
<context>
The start was delayed for three hours partly because the bowlers' run-ups were damp and partly because vandals, protesting about the omission of Deryck Murray, the local captain, had left wet patches on the pitch &mdash; and thrown a good few bottles around as well.
With this in mind, Botham chose to field first, only for Greenidge and Haynes to put on 168 for the first wicket.
On the second day, Emburey bowled forty overs for 81 runs and five wickets, but Lloyd, David Murray and Roberts all batted well.
Roberts's fifty included an over from Botham from which he hit twenty-four runs (462660), a new Test record for a six-ball over, and Lloyd finally declared on the third morning at 426 for 9.
The rest <head>day</head> , incidentally, was taken after two days for the lovely Caribbean reason of avoiding a clash with a steel-band festival. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40338" docsrc="bnc_A6L_1673">
<answer instance="day.40338" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40338" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Some people are very good at it; some people aren't.
Some people communicate easily; some don't.
In some respects, you have to determine what your strong characteristics are and then use them. [/p] [/quote] [/p] [p]
In Pearce's experience it is easy for top management to become remote from the shop floor and lose contact with the centre of operations. [quote] [p]
It's just the pressure you work under.
The things you have to do make it progressively more and more difficult for you to really get around and see what's going on in your factories. [/p] [/quote] [quote] [p]
Take British Aerospace with its twenty different locations. [pb] [/p] [/quote] [quote] [p]
Each of them requires a complete <head>day</head> out to go and visit them and it's very difficult to find a complete day because there are so many other things, so many other demands on your time.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40340" docsrc="bnc_CEK_6851">
<answer instance="day.40340" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
We used a bit of sign language, and that and &bquo;goo' shot&equo; was the only communication we had &mdash; and all we needed, because we were golfers. [/p] [p]
Come to think of it, it was a real pain, that round. [/p] [p]
In January, Jasper Carrott will star in his new BBC1 Comedy series, The Detectives, along with friend and fellow golfer Robert Powell. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Murder on the 13th hole at scenic Silloth [/head] [head]
Mark Simpson [/head] [p]
NOWADAYS it is rare to find classic golf courses which not only welcome visitors but charge reasonable green fees.
Silloth on Solway is one of them. [/p] [p]
Situated west of Carlisle on the shores of the Solway Firth, Silloth boasts superb views of the Lake District on one side, Scotland on the other.
On a clear <head>day</head> you can even see the Isle of Man. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40341" docsrc="bnc_AN9_1026">
<answer instance="day.40341" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Over a thousand people brought wooden crosses in the shape of the radiation hazard symbol and planted them along the grass verge entrance to the power station.
Many bore poignant personal messages.
A flotilla of small boats arrived off the coast from South Wales, a few braving the rocky shallows to land.
A biplane buzzed overhead trailing a banner reading &bquo;No More Chernobyls.&equo;
Paddy Ashdown, Liberal MP for the Yeovil constituency, addressed the crowd under the shadow of the plant and surrounded by children in radiation suits.
There was a final windswept song dedicated to the Rainbow Warriors &mdash; the spiritual defenders of the earth according to North American native legend &mdash; who had inspired Greenpeace.
By the end of the <head>day</head> , the stark nuclear presence set in bold defiance on the Bristol Channel had been suitably upstaged.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40343" docsrc="bnc_CCD_140">
<answer instance="day.40343" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
We could refurbish it and it would remain your property, a place of your own to go to whenever you so desired.
I doubt not it holds many happy memories for you. [/p] [p]
&bquo;It does indeed, Your Grace.&equo;
Tears again filled Joan's eyes but she brushed them away.
&bquo;Yea, I'd like to keep it &mdash; if it's possible.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;It is indeed, Joan &mdash; and keep it you shall,&equo; smiled Elizabeth Mowbray.
&bquo;Whilst you remain here with us &mdash; and let me say here and now that there will be a place here for you for as long as you wish &mdash; you will share in the life of the household and have all provided.
Furthermore, it would please me to give you an allowance for your personal use.&equo; [/p] [p]
&bquo;Your Grace, I don't understand &mdash; why are you doing all this for me?
Has it to do with what you said as you'd tell me one <head>day</head> ?&equo; [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40344" docsrc="bnc_ASJ_1162">
<answer instance="day.40344" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The best chance is often away from the tourist lodges on a tented safari and although wildlife programmes on television are enthralling viewing, nothing beats the excitement of seeing a live leopard in the headlights or an elephant at a waterhole.
It makes your heart beat at an invigorating pace. [/p] [p]
Flicking through the travel brochures the browser is confronted by an astonishing number of photographs of whales' flukes.
There is a bewildering array of environmental and wildlife holidays to choose from.
The real enthusiast has been doing it for years.
Like the ornithologist who has to reach an impossibly remote island by a certain <head>day</head> in the rainy season only to find it overflowing with ornithologists from all over the world choking the woodland tracks with cameras and tripods, trying to catch a fleeting glimpse of a small bird as it hops about in the dripping undergrowth.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40346" docsrc="bnc_BNF_1058">
<answer instance="day.40346" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
We have already referred to those who find it difficult to give up &bquo;playing the field&equo; and continue to behave as if they are still single.
Ordinary friendships and activities outside the marriage can also cause tension if they take no account of marital commitments, as another young woman found out: [/p] [p]
&bquo;Christopher got this money and spent it on a holiday skiing.
I was put out, but not drastically put out.
But then, afterwards, I learned that the other members of the party had accepted him as a bachelor and he had gone along with that.&equo; [/p] [p]
Becoming a couple takes time; commitment has to be made to a joint identity. [/p] [p]
Some people, brought up in the expectation of forging a career and getting near the top if not right to the top in their profession, may be deeply committed to their work.
(These <head>days</head> people are often less committed to the actual firm they work for than in the past.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40347" docsrc="bnc_C8L_1469">
<answer instance="day.40347" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Around 25 per cent of those gathered will be distracted anyway; they may be upset by their home situation; concerned by some event which occurred on their way in; confused by the absence of someone they were expecting to see.
In short, all kinds of mundane concerns will be encountered as the church gathers.
It is good for leaders to be aware of these if only to see that to gather together towards the Lord may take some time. [/p] [p]
In all this, the role of the worship leader is important.
Traditional models of &bquo;leading the service&equo; may need to be broken.
Lay readers or elders who have traditionally been given this job may well not be gifted to lead the congregation in the way described above.
Many will need to pray that they might grow into this new role.
The way to do this is to be a worshipper at home.
It may be helpful to use the structure of Psalm 95 in your quiet time as a pattern for [pb] half an hour to an hour or more of worship each <head>day</head> for a while.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40349" docsrc="bnc_CEJ_744">
<answer instance="day.40349" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
COMMENT ON THE BIRTH OF JESUS AS RECORDED BY LUKE [/head] [item]
At first sight, Luke, far more than Matthew, seems to be concerned to set the events of Jesus' birth in a historical setting.
Yet the question must be asked as to how much Luke is writing an historical record, and how much, he, like Matthew, is more concerned with the importance of this new-born baby. [/item] [item]
Though not as obvious as Matthew, Luke also writes his story with Old Testament overtones, combining them with basic historical facts. [/item] [item]
The whole story of Jesus' birth seems to be an expansion of an Old Testament prophecy found in Micah: [quote] [p]
&bquo;But you, Bethlehem&hellip; small as you are to be among Judah's clans, out of you shall come forth a governor for Israel, one whose roots are far back in the past, in <head>days</head> gone by.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40350" docsrc="bnc_AR3_1154">
<answer instance="day.40350" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
As I hastened to go upstairs, I happened to encounter Miss Kenton in the back corridor &mdash; the scene, of course, of our last disagreement &mdash; and it was perhaps this unhappy coincidence that encouraged her to maintain the childish behaviour she had adopted on that previous occasion.
For when I inquired who it was that had arrived, Miss Kenton continued past me, stating simply: &bquo;A message if it is urgent, Mr Stevens.&equo;
This was extremely annoying, but, of course, I had no choice but to hurry on upstairs. [/p] [p]
My recollection of Mr Lewis is that of a gentleman of generous dimensions with a genial smile that rarely left his face.
His early arrival was clearly something of an inconvenience to his lordship and his colleagues who had reckoned on a <head>day</head> or two more of privacy for their preparations.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40352" docsrc="bnc_BMG_1628">
<answer instance="day.40352" senseid="day-2"/>
<answer instance="day.40352" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Anything considered holy by a previous religious faith must automatically be damned by a new religion.
In this way began the darkest chapter in the cat's long association with mankind.
For centuries it was persecuted and the cruelties heaped upon it were given the full backing of the Church. [/p] [p]
During this bleak phase of its history the cat became firmly linked in the popular mind with witches and black magic.
As late as 1658 Edward Topsel, in his serious work on natural history, followed detailed descriptions of the cat's anatomy and behaviour with the solemn comment that &bquo;the familiars of Witches do most ordinarily appear in the shape of Cats, which is an argument that this beast is dangerous to soul and body.&equo; [/p] [p]
Because the cat was seen as evil, all kinds of frightening powers were attributed to it by the writers of the <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40353" docsrc="bnc_BNL_125">
<answer instance="day.40353" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
It is estimated that approximately 500,000 adults in Great Britain suffer from agoraphobia to some extent.
Women are particularly at risk, the majority of agoraphobics are women in the 18&ndash;35 age group.
The Institute of Psychiatry at the Royal Bethlem and Maudsley Hospitals in London reports that men who live alone are more prone to alcoholism or social phobias (such as fear of meeting people). [/p] [p]
It is too easy to lose control when one lives alone; the aim must always be to be &bquo;alone but not lonely&equo;.
Social contact with others is a necessity and will be considered in greater depth in a later chapter. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
BANISHING ANXIETIES [/head] [p]
One of the psychiatrists I spoke to while preparing this book said that in his therapy groups for people with anxieties, he [pb] asked them to make lists of their <head>day</head> 's worries.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40355" docsrc="bnc_ABF_1103">
<answer instance="day.40355" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
The belated correction: investment in agriculture will be increased by 30%; curbs on the money supply will be relaxed; loans will be given to exporters and indebted state enterprises; &bquo;specialised groups&equo; will be set up to break &bquo;debt chains&equo; between enterprises.
It sounds suspiciously like a &bquo;stop-go&equo; recipe for the alternation of inflationary booms and resource-misallocating busts. [/p] [p]
What happens next?
The great fear of China's leaders is not that western conspirators will weave more plots but that China's people, enraged by corruption and scornful of slogans, will take to the streets, as they did last June, to demand instant solutions that the government cannot possibly provide. [/p] [p]
In the <head>days</head> of Chairman Mao, author of the disastrous Great Leap Forward and the Cultural Revolution, the party could belittle such dangers.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40356" docsrc="bnc_CJT_2018">
<answer instance="day.40356" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The Captain of KGB begins an investigation.
The Major in command is at first flustered, then morose. [/p] [p]
There is labour in Zone I, and to spare.
In a few days there will be a new office for Major Kypov at the end of the Administration block. [/p] [p]
For nearly half a century the camp has survived the storms.
More than fire is required to break the regimen of ZhKh 38S/3/I. [/p] [p]
Later, those who were to piece together the events at the camp of the early months of that year, from the time of snow till the approach of spring, were to wonder what was the ambition of Michael Holly, prisoner of Hut 2 in Zone I of Camp 3 in the [hi]Dubrovlag [/hi] complex. [/p] [p]
For a few <head>days</head> there was a swirl of conversation in the camp about the fire and its likely cause, and then the talk slipped.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40358" docsrc="bnc_CHH_616">
<answer instance="day.40358" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Apart from Ennerdale, Grisedale is the largest roadless valley in the Lakes.
it is striking and overlooked by impressive crags. [/p] [p]
From Grisedale Tarn pass through the gap between Seat Sandal and Dollywagon Pike and descend to Dunmail Raise, the pass between Grasmere and Thirlmere. [/p] [p]
From the very top of the pass take the path to Thirlmere (0.75 mile).
This parallels the main A591 road and links to a forestry track which you follow until you join a minor road running along the western side of the reservoir.
From here you can continue along the main route as described above. [gap] [/p] [p]
Pubs and eating places: both hotels have public bars. [ptr][/p] [caption]
Grisedale &mdash; the largest roadless valley in the Lake District [/caption] [/div3] [/div2] [div2] [head]
<head>DAY</head> 4 [/head] [head]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40359" docsrc="bnc_CK9_470">
<answer instance="day.40359" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
After the door shut behind him, she sat looking at it, wondering what she would have done over the years without him.
She, too, remembered the day he had come into the yard and cheeked her father, telling him he could choose his name from Smith, Jones, or Robinson.
He had said he thought he must have been eight but that he didn't really know.
At that time he would have been like many thousand of other youngsters, the sweepings of the hungry &bquo;forties. [/p] [p]
He must have been born in the middle &bquo;thirties, when hunger was already rampant.
The corn laws had seen to that.
He had been with them for some time; two or three years before, he had told her that he didn't know where he had been born, or who his parents were.
He only knew of the life he had led in the baby-farming house, one of seventeen young children.
He had made his escape on the <head>day</head> he later confronted her father in the yard.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40361" docsrc="bnc_CJK_1374">
<answer instance="day.40361" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The outbuildings, once stables and tack rooms, have been converted into superior self-catering cottages with a meal service from the main house If required. [/p] [p]
Your hosts have a wealth of experience in catering and the evening meal is prepared to a very high standard making good use of fresh vegetables, fruit and herbs from the garden.
Jams, chutneys and marmalade are home-made. [/p] [p]
[hi]Easily Accessible [/hi]: Winchcombe is a charming town with many 16th-century buildings and a fine church containing an altar cloth embroidered by Catherine of Aragon.
Two miles away lies [corr] Sudeley [/corr] Castle where Henry VIII's widow, Catherine Parr, once lived; she was buried in the castle chapel.
Cheltenham Spa, a fine Regency town, lies 6 miles to the south and is enjoyable for its shops, architecture and nearby racecourse.
There are famous horse trials at Badminton, 38 miles away.
Take a <head>day</head> trip to Bath, Stratford, Oxford or Winchester.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40362" docsrc="bnc_CA9_1696">
<answer instance="day.40362" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
I've never collapsed &mdash; on stage or anywhere else. [/p] [p]
Sitting up in bed, I scanned the article, which the [hi]News of the World [/hi] claimed was an exclusive interview.
Apparently not only had I collapsed on stage last night, but I was having intravenous chemotherapy between shows, sobbing and grimacing in agony in my dressing room. [/p] [p]
It was a nightmare, anyone reading the papers would think I was on my last legs.
I'll never work again.
Where did they get their information?
I haven't even told the majority of my friends yet.
They'll be worried sick.
I sat by the phone and rang as many of them as I could, reassuring the ones who were home. [/p] [/div2] [div2] [head]
Friday 23 December [/head] [p]
It's been a very trying few <head>days</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40364" docsrc="bnc_B33_628">
<answer instance="day.40364" senseid="day_off-0"/>
<context>
For example, it can be stated that &bquo;By the end of the ward allocation the student will be able to catheterise a female patient, using an aseptic and atraumatic [pb] technique&equo;, or &bquo;By the end of the ward allocation the student will be able to identify five potential problems associated with catheterization&equo;.
These guidelines for learning should be given to the student at the beginning of her time on the ward.
More precise objectives for individual teaching and tutorials should also be listed.
These are of particular value when a student misses a session.
She is then able to cover the same ground, using the objectives set by the ward. [/p] [p]
The length of the whole learning programme must be determined.
If students are allocated to the ward for eight-week periods, it is sensible to have a rotating cycle of an eight-week programme.
The content of the programme should follow a logical sequence.
In practice, the student will necessarily miss some continuity because of <head>days</head> off and night duty.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40365" docsrc="bnc_A7C_38">
<answer instance="day.40365" senseid="working_day-0"/>
<context>
And these were the conditions under which [hi]Screwtape [/hi] and indeed all his books were produced. [/p] [p]
How, it may be asked, could any serious work be done in those circumstances?
The answer is that in the years when Minto was in her fall vigour, Lewis's flow of words was limited.
A glance at the shelf containing his long list of books shows us immediately that the bulk of his work was completed when Minto was in her dotage or after she died.
He was a fluent and rapid prose writer.
But his first major prose work &mdash; [hi]The Allegory of Love &mdash; [/hi] took about eight years to complete.
This was the price he paid far having thrown in his lot with a person who with all her virtues &mdash; generosity, warmth of character, genuine and passionate admiration, as well as love, for Lewis himself &mdash; did not have the concept of a working <head>day</head> .
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40368" docsrc="bnc_ASA_1101">
<answer instance="day.40368" senseid="day-4"/>
<context>
How I got round for the four days of the tournament, I don't know.
I've seen the video tape of Tom and I coming down the 18th.
Tom's got his arm around me, hugging me, and the commentator says, &bquo;Look at the smile on that caddie's face.
No wonder, he's just bringing home the British Open champion.&equo;
Little did he know that it wasn't a smile, but a grimace of pain.
I was gritting my teeth, thinking, &bquo;Thank god we're going down the 18th.&equo; [/p] [p]
I don't think any other caddie in the history of the British Open has worked harder than I did that week.
There were some light-hearted moments in practice with the big four, though.
The Tarbuck ice-cream incident, for instance.
Jimmy Tarbuck and his mate Kenny Lynch followed us around for one of the practice <head>days</head> and, unusually for Tom and I, it was a sunny day.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40369" docsrc="bnc_ACA_1147">
<answer instance="day.40369" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
By the spring of 1833 the first onrush of the epidemic had subsided and the government marked the occasion in the way thought most appropriate, as Judith Holt's diary records: [quote] [p]
&bquo;14th April 1833: Appointed for a day public thanksgiving on the cessation of that dreadful scourge &mdash; the Cholera Morbus.
I hope we did feel truly grateful for our merciful preservation&hellip;
May God grant that the lives he has spared may be devoted to His glory and service! [/p] [/quote]
&bquo; [/p] [p]
The respite was not long, especially for those living not [pb] far from a seaport, and at the beginning of August there is another apprehensive entry: [quote] [p]
&bquo;Laurence Taylor died at Stubbylee of Asiatic Cholera, having arrived from Liverpool only on Saturday last; he was interred the same <head>day</head> at the old Baptist Chapel.&equo; [/p] [/quote] [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40371" docsrc="bnc_AP0_1111">
<answer instance="day.40371" senseid="field_day-0"/>
<context>
[hi]Myra Breckenridge [/hi], the sizzling exposure of sex in Hollywood by Gore Vidal had just made its appearance in London, along with Norman Mailer's [hi]The Armies of the Night [/hi], about the invasion of the White House the previous October of pacifists and hippies protesting at the war.
John Lennon and Yoko allowed the world's media into their hotel suite in Amsterdam for their bed-in, a honeymoon to epitomize the institution of love not war.
Mick Jagger put on a charming little Greek skirt and gave a free performance to thousands in London's Hyde Park, while Bob Dylan headed down to the Isle of Wight for a three-day festival of dope, sex and rock &bquo;n&equo; roll attended by 150,000 fans.
It was the wildest party Britain had seen, and the media had a field <head>day</head> with a revelling of nude and painted bodies, cavorting to fine music under a dense cloud of cannabis smoke and punctuated by the occasional screams of an acid drop gone wrong. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40372" docsrc="bnc_C9E_341">
<answer instance="day.40372" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Moments later he drew up at Hell Bunker, a deep, sprawling dune that once was the most famous bunker in all of St Andrews. [/p] [p]
&bquo;At one time, maybe 67 years ago,&equo; began Woods, his guide-like voice snatched away in the wind, &bquo;Hell Bunker was allowed to ramble.
No banks, no faces &mdash; look at the old photographs &mdash; just an unkempt hole in the ground, probably made by sheep.
Over the years, though, it's been made smaller and also shallower.
More sand has been put in to cover the high water table.&equo; [/p] [p]
Hell, indeed, was a handsome bunker, Woods agreed.
But in recent years it has lost its fury.
It no longer beckoned an ambitious second shot.
&bquo;It is no longer regarded a hazard by the pros,&equo; he concluded.
&bquo;The balls fly so far these <head>days</head> that Hell's been taken out of play.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40374" docsrc="bnc_CF9_2126">
<answer instance="day.40374" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
DEFENDING champions Ajax Amsterdam were knocked out of the UEFA Cup last night when a 1&ndash;0 home victory was not enough to claw back a 4&ndash;2 first leg deficit to French club Auxerre in the quarter-finals. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
Squash [/head] [head]
Harris faces tough task to qualify [/head] [p]
DEL Harris of Colchester, for so long in the top three of the British squash rankings, has dropped down the list because of injury and a recent loss of form. [/p] [p]
Surprisingly he must take part in the qualifying section of the Daily Express Newspapers and Pursers inaugural British Squash Players' Championship to be played between March 23 and 28 at Bromley, Beckenham and Cheshunt. [/p] [p]
This event sprung up following the failure of the Squash Rackets Association to secure a sponsor for this year's national championships and a resultant boycott from most of the leading professionals. [/p] [p]
Harris faces a tough opener against fast improving Surrey youngster Tim Garner at noon on the opening <head>day</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40376" docsrc="bnc_AMC_972">
<answer instance="day.40376" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The new book was to be handed to me by the minister, the Revd Dr Adam Burnet, only after we had signed the register &mdash; no self-respecting hotel would have accepted us with different names. [/p] [p]
But the date remained the real problem.
Leslie had first to undergo a stiff P.T. course at Hardwick, but he found to his relief that he had not deteriorated from the peak physical condition which, despite those months of idleness, had achieved for him in [pb] North Africa his acceptance into the Parachute Regiment.
&bquo;You'll be amused to hear that I'm very stiff and sore.
I've carried weights, swung on beams and parallel bars, jumped ditches, scrambled over walls, scaled rather terrifying cliffs by rope, and generally behaved in the fashion of an anthropoid ape.
And my hands are rather cut about, but I'm still cheerful.&equo;
A few <head>days</head> later he confided: [quote] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40378" docsrc="bnc_CH2_5152">
<answer instance="day.40378" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
It reminded them of when Labour Chancellor Denis Healey turned back at the airport in 1976 over a sterling crisis. [/p] [p]
Lord Healey said last night that Mr Major must blame himself because &bquo;he went into the ERM at far too high a rate&equo;. [ptr][pb] [/p] [caption]
BUNKER JIBE: Blair [/caption] [/div1] [div1] [head]
BANKS RUSH TO CASH IN [/head] [head]
NEIL SIMPSON [/head] [p]
THE High Street banks were blasted for profiteering as they rushed to cash in on the interest rate jump. [/p] [p]
They instantly raised charges for borrowers &mdash; but are delaying any rise in the interest they pay savers. [/p] [p]
While extra millions will immediately start flooding into the Big Four's coffers, spokesmen would only say that savings rates &bquo;will be reviewed over the next few <head>days</head> .&equo;
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40379" docsrc="bnc_BPG_1239">
<answer instance="day.40379" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
freshly ground pepper and salt [/item] [/list] [pb] [p]
Cook the leeks and onion in a steamer for 10 minutes.
Arrange in an ovenproof dish and put slices of hardboiled egg on top.
Add salt and pepper.
Make a white sauce with the milk and cornflour and add most of the grated cheese.
Pour the sauce over the leeks and egg.
Scatter the remaining grated cheese over the top.
Bake in a pre-heated oven, Gas Mark 5 (190C/375F) for 15 minutes.
Brown under the grill.
Serve with jacket potatoes and a green salad. [/p] [/div3] [div3] [head]
<head>DAY</head> 12 &mdash; PASTA SALAD [/head] [list] [item]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40381" docsrc="bnc_CD0_343">
<answer instance="day.40381" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
It can play havoc with your bookkeeping and create chaos with your VAT.
It means your statements or invoices must show both the lesser amount due with VAT if the discount is taken, as well as the amount due with VAT if the discount is not taken. [/item] [label]
2. [/label] [item]
It often results in late payments with the discount still being taken.
This in turn can lead to disputes. [/item] [label]
3. [/label] [item]
It can give away too much profit.
If your net margin on sales is 10 per cent and the discount offered for early payment is 2.5 per cent, you are effectively giving away a quarter of your profit. [/item] [label]
4. [/label] [item]
It is expensive.
Giving a 2.5 per cent discount to get your money in 30 <head>days</head> instead of 60 means that your money is costing you 2.5 per cent for 30 days.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40382" docsrc="bnc_CEP_4282">
<answer instance="day.40382" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
ADRIAN MAGUIRE's meteoric rise to the top of his profession overshadowed the emergence of another exceptional talent last season. [/p] [p]
Fellow Irishman Mick Fitzgerald would have stood out as the &bquo;find of the season&equo; in any normal year. [/p] [p]
Maguire's remarkable exploits rightly grabbed most of the headlines, but Fitzgerald impressed as a horseman of the highest quality with 38 successes from limited opportunities. [/p] [p]
He has carried on the good work this term and is well on the way to establishing himself in the top 10 with 16 wins in the current campaign. [/p] [p]
His booking could well make all the difference for Romola Nijinsky in the Orchard Portman Selling Handicap Hurdle (2.50) at Taunton. [/p] [p]
Good enough to finish fifth in a Listed race at Goodwood last year, Romola Nijinsky mixes in rather less exaltic circles these <head>days</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40384" docsrc="bnc_A7C_1164">
<answer instance="day.40384" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
In staunch Irish fashion, he laid on transport for Fox's supporters to be &bquo;bused&equo; into Oxford on.
the appropriate days and rewarded them for their votes with meals and refreshments at Magdalen.
Fox was a nice man, much liked among a wide circle of his fellow-clergy.
He romped home. [/p] [p]
The election did much to harm Lewis's reputation in Oxford.
The dons felt that he could not be trusted: that he was populist, bullying, showy, and hostile to them.
By his campaign for Fox, Lewis probably destroyed his own chances of promotion in the University, even though he was very obviously the most distinguished member of the English Faculty. [/p] [p]
It is certainly easy for those who did not belong to Lewis's group of friends, and who merely come upon the record of it in after <head>days</head> , to see its faults.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40385" docsrc="bnc_AC2_2537">
<answer instance="day.40385" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
He was a redundant executive and nobody rang a redundant executive, except to say &bquo;Goodbye&equo;. [/p] [p]
He opened the door which led to the secretary's annex.
Her chair was empty and would remain empty until he left the company.
The electric typewriter was covered by its hood and would remain covered while he was still there. [/p] [p]
There was just no point in remaining on the premises when you knew you had to go, as Muldoon had said.
It was too painful. [/p] [p]
&bquo;Use the remaining few weeks to say your goodbyes and to find another job,&equo; he had said. [/p] [p]
Mark smiled the bitter smile of a disillusioned corporate executive and walked out of the office, closing the door slowly and carefully behind him. [/p] [p]
Two <head>days</head> later, Mark arrived back at his temporary office to check the in-tray and tie up any loose ends.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40387" docsrc="bnc_APR_100">
<answer instance="day.40387" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Roland opened these delicately.
They were both letters in Ash's flowing hand, both headed with his Great Russell Street address and dated, June 21st.
No year.
Both began &bquo;Dear Madam&equo;, and both were unsigned.
One was considerably shorter than the other. [quote] [p]
Dear Madam, [/p] [p]
Since our extraordinary conversation I have thought of nothing else.
It has not often been given to me as a poet, it is perhaps not often given to human beings, to find such ready sympathy, such wit and judgment together.
I write with a strong sense of the necessity of continuing our &mdash; talk, and without premeditation, [hi]under the impression that you were indeed as much struck as I was by our quite extraordinary [/hi] to ask if it would be possible for me to call on you, perhaps one <head>day</head> next week.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40388" docsrc="bnc_CDC_1563">
<answer instance="day.40388" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
I carried Rachel, and Margaret held on to me, and I hoped Tim would be hanging on to Mig, but when we reached the small steamer Tim was missing.
So many refugees had panicked and he was lost in the throng.
Having settled Rachel in a corner and piled our luggage round her and left you, Mig, on guard, I struggled back against the refugees and climbed the gangway again to find Tim looking a little bewildered in the midst of a seething mass of humanity but remarkably calm, and soon we were back on the small boat.
When the tide turned, we all had to struggle back to the large Irrawaddy steamer again.
In two <head>days</head> ' time we reached Pakoku where many of the Anglo-Burmans begged me to disembark and try to walk out of Burma with them, but Rachel was still very sick and I said I would go on to Mandalay and hope to find a doctor there. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40390" docsrc="bnc_A5J_85">
<answer instance="day.40390" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
It is fashionable among rich Americans to buy art, donate art, exhibit art and appreciate art.
But they would not be so rich if they were not adept at minimising tax and maximising profits. [/p] [p]
The schemes they have dreamed up for art-related asset-manipulation are being imitated throughout the world, notably in Europe and Japan.
This makes the precedents that have been set in America important to anyone who is interested in playing the market. [/p] [p]
At the end of September, 35 English dealers and 15 from the Continent joined 35 American dealers to hold the first International Antique Dealers' Show at the Seventh Regiment Armory on Park Avenue, in the heart of Manhattan.
In the course of five <head>days</head> , during which the super-rich flooded through the hall, the Europeans learned just what American collectors want. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40391" docsrc="bnc_CA9_706">
<answer instance="day.40391" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Deciding that attack was the best form of defence, I knelt beside him and lowering my head to within inches of his, said, &bquo;Next time, It'll be the bread knife.&equo; [/p] [p]
He believed me and the next day suggested that I moved out. [/p] [p]
I moved back in with my Grandfather, changing schools once again and seeing my Mom at week-ends. [/p] [p]
I adored my Pop, and loved playing the role of &bquo;little mother&equo;, cleaning, washing and darning his socks.
On the <head>day</head> I moved in my Mother had warned me not to let him rule my life like he'd ruled my Father's, but it never occurred to me to disobey him and seemed natural to follow the &bquo;week planner&equo; he'd written out and pinned to the notice-board in the kitchen: Monday &mdash; Washing Tuesday &mdash; Ironing Wednesday &mdash; Youth Club etc. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40393" docsrc="bnc_ABH_2723">
<answer instance="day.40393" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
(Islam, incidentally, has almost identical rules covering the decent treatment of victims of war.) [/caption] [p]
Article 13 of the Third Geneva Convention, specifically on prisoners of war, repeats the limits on the information they may be required to give.
They may be questioned, but must be &bquo;at all times protected, particularly against acts of violence or intimidation and against insults and public curiosity.&equo; [/p] [p]
If torture was involved in the pilots' remarks this week &mdash; and many remember the UN investigations of Iraq's treatment of prisoners during the war with Iran &mdash; the rules were broken.
If not, Iraq's television show was not technically worse than the photographs that same <head>day</head> in western newspapers, showing the backs of Iraqi prisoners, forlorn beside a fence. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40394" docsrc="bnc_ADP_2090">
<answer instance="day.40394" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
So many television transmissions, and some of these are now on CD video, provide endless, often arbitrary, shots of the conductor at the expense of the musical developments going on around him.
There's a Bruckner CD video where at one point the conductor is filmed doing absolutely nothing, whilst the orchestra is busy starting up a new paragraph of the music. [/p] [/sp] [sp] [spkr]
HvK [/spkr] [p]
Yes, I have seen this kind of thing and it is something we avoid completely.
In my films the conductor is more or less in one position throughout.
But, you see, we have the resources to create an image not just of the conductor or the orchestra but of the whole ensemble of the music and the performers.
First of all, we have three banks of cameras: left, right, and diagonally.
And there are five cameras in each group.
At the start of the filming we bring in a students' orchestra and we rehearse for three <head>days</head> , six sessions in all.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40396" docsrc="bnc_A68_2191">
<answer instance="day.40396" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Ramsey's long memory always regarded the decision to leave academic life as the hardest of his life.
To the observer this decision of 1955 looks as hard or harder; to agree to accept a post which he expected to hate, and for which he regarded himself as unsuitable, and in which he would have to neglect that scholarship which was essential to his happiness and to his sense of vocation and to the reason why he ever became a bishop at all, if the leaders of the Church declared that this was where he was needed.
His long memory also told him that this was a moment of his life when he felt a total rapport with Fisher. [/p] [p]
On 14 December 1955 Fisher repeated his recommendation to Anthony Eden that Ramsey should become the Bishop of London. [/p] [p]
On the same <head>day</head> , knowing nothing of what Fisher was doing, Ramsey drove to Bishopthorpe outside York to see his frail and dying archbishop.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40397" docsrc="bnc_CLG_1307">
<answer instance="day.40397" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
For more information, contact your tax office. [/p] [/div3] [/div2] [div2] [head]
REGULATIONS [/head] [div3] [head]
INSPECTION NOTICES [/head] [p]
The new Building Regulations, which came into force in June, contain some new rules concerning the giving of notices at the various stages of building works.
They are the notices which you are required to give to your local council's Building Control department, to enable them to inspect your work for compliance with the appropriate regulation requirements. [/p] [p]
The main change is that the periods laid down for these notices are now in days instead of hours: two days notice is required for the commencement of building works.
Excavations for, and the concreting of foundations, the laying of damp-proof courses, and of site concrete, and the covering of new drains require one <head>days</head> notice.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40399" docsrc="bnc_ABL_1110">
<answer instance="day.40399" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
It always has been so with me, and will be.
Also, in my thought it is neither vulgar nor stupid.
&mdash; I get an extraordinary pleasure thus.
And let me explain what I meant by that silly passage in my last letter, about expensively dressed girls.
It was this.
My cousins are rather wealthy, and so wear rich dresses, which [/p] [p]
I am never tired of hearing &mdash; oh, those sounding silks, so uncomfortable, so gorgeous.
Yet I like comfortable dresses, too: why not?
All I don't like is, rags, ill taste, ill-shapes&hellip;.
My feeling for girls has still the same nervous reverence of childhood or earliest boyhood, rather increased if anything, and only too excessive to be chivalrous.
In my childish <head>days</head> I remember I used to fear to touch the little girls' sleeves; so it is now.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40400" docsrc="bnc_A67_1056">
<answer instance="day.40400" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Risking everything he grabbed two tomatoes and the biggest apples before bedding down for another night under cover of trees.
Next day, footsore, he saw a bicycle beside a house and, with nobody in sight, he quickly mounted it and rode &bquo;like the clappers&equo;, feeling that every time a car passed him, it might be the police.
After two or three hours, Harry say a sign indicating that Hamburg was 300 kilometres away, and he took this road as he knew Lubeck might be an alternative if no vessels for Sweden were berthed in the larger port. [/p] [p]
That night he was woken by planes and saw flares over Berlin, bringing a moment of &bquo;homesickness&equo; that he wasn't up there too.
Next <head>day</head> , in Schwerin, after drenching rain, he listened to a band, German soldiers ignoring him, and restocked with apples, standing on the cycle's crossbar to reach them.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40402" docsrc="bnc_CHB_663">
<answer instance="day.40402" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
1982 was the definitive Reading ROCK festival: Budgie, Iron Maiden and Michael Schenker headlined with a supporting cast of such acned arseholes as Terraplane and Praying Mantis, and old stagers Blackfoot and Tygers Of Pan Tang.
The spirit of Chilli Willi was dutifully upheld by Wilko Johnson and Dave Edmunds, but these were lone voices of dissent. [/p] [p]
The following year was billed as the last ever and saw Steel Pulse canned off after 15 minutes by a typically broad-minded Stranglers crowd and Black Sabbath playing in front of an unfinished replica of Stonehenge. [/p] [p]
&bquo;It was too big for the stage,&equo; remembers Myra.
&bquo;They were sawing it in half and heaving all these rocks around on the Saturday morning trying to make it look like anything other than a total abortion.
In the end we just let the audience in or we'd have been there all <head>day</head> .&equo; [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40403" docsrc="bnc_BPG_869">
<answer instance="day.40403" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
DAY 24 &mdash; Walk aerobically for 45 minutes.
See the world at 4 miles an hour; this is what your body was designed for. [/p] [p]
DAY 25 &mdash; Repeat Day 24.
Cultivate awareness: savour the sights and sounds of the journey.
Walk to break out of the pattern and routine of normal daily living. [/p] [p]
DAY 26 &mdash; Rest day. [/p] [p]
DAY 27 &mdash; Walk aerobically for 45 minutes.
Try inner walking and walking meditation (see Chapter 8).
Discover who you are.
Walk for the inner benefits as well as the fitness and slimness benefits. [/p] [p]
<head>DAY</head> 28 &mdash; Repeat Day 27. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40405" docsrc="bnc_AK9_1445">
<answer instance="day.40405" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
That will not happen this time, though the election was very bad news for the polling organisations.
Most of them earn their bread and butter from market research, and political polling is the decorative jam on top.
The organisation that calls the general election closest is the one that is most attractive to Tesco or Finefare or whomever it might be when they want to discover what the public thinks of their baked beans. [/p] [p]
In the beginning was Dr George Horace Gallup.
This &bquo;tweedy, rumpled&equo; mid-Westerner (as Time once described him) was a professor of journalism and advertising.
In 1935 he joined the advertising agency Young and Rubicam to apply his academic expertise to practical matters.
In the following year Alfred Landon ran against Roosevelt.
The nearest thing to accurate soothsaying in those <head>days</head> was the &bquo;straw poll&equo;.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40406" docsrc="bnc_BMR_1814">
<answer instance="day.40406" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40406" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
If she hadn't yielded to a guilty passion then she would have been a better wife to Denny.
The implication was that with a bit more happening in the sack, hubby wouldn't have felt he was getting past it and tried to prove his virility by punting up the north face of the Thames. [/p] [p]
&bquo;If I'd been more, you know, responsive and that, then Denny'd still be here today.
And the only reason I wasn't is, well, because of us.&equo; [/p] [p]
I assaulted this position from every angle, ranging from thoughtful analyses of the male mid-life crisis, its nature and origins, to sweeping [hi]ad absurdum[/hi] dismissals in which I demonstrated that by the same token Trish and Brian were equally culpable, because if they'd gone out for the <head>day</head> I would have stayed at home and we would never have met in the first place.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40408" docsrc="bnc_CBF_3340">
<answer instance="day.40408" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
A YOUNG paratrooper was critically ill in hospital last night after being shot by a fellow sentry. [/p] [p]
The two were apparently on guard duty at the Lille Barracks, Farnham, Surrey, when 19-year-old Robert Smith was blasted at point-blank range. [/p] [p]
An Army spokesman said: &bquo;We believe the shooting was a tragic accident.&equo; [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
She took down her Christmas cards and went out.
We never saw Johanna again [/head] [head]
By Adrian Lee [/head] [p]
A SEX monster battered a 14-year-old girl before dumping her in a freezing gravel pit and leaving her to drown. [/p] [p]
Johanna Young's semi-naked body was found floating in the icy water after a four-day search.
She had been sexually assaulted. [/p] [p]
The dark-haired schoolgirl, who split with her boyfriend two <head>days</head> before disappearing, left home last Wednesday evening to meet friends. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40409" docsrc="bnc_A64_1057">
<answer instance="day.40409" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
I saw the corpses of eight, photographed some of them.
More than 50 per cent of these [hi]enfants trov&eacute;s [/hi] perish in spite of the care that is given them.
But if the children some under the care of the relief agencies, little ones, who were emaciated, hollow-eyed, and listless, become after about a fortnight's feeding quite plump again and begin to laugh and sing. [/p] [/quote] [quote] [p]
Since beginning this letter I have been with Nansen in the Samara district, where the conditions are even worse than in Saratov, in spite of the very good work done by the ARA in Samara and by the Friends in Bouzoulouk. [/p] [/quote] [quote] [p]
We saw awful conditions in Bouzoulouk, where, out of a population of 35,000 they are dying at the rate of 100 a day.
Corpses are found lying almost every <head>day</head> , and murders are frequent.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40411" docsrc="bnc_A3C_107">
<answer instance="day.40411" senseid="working_day-0"/>
<context>
Campbells' Richard Nelson has it right.
Today's kids &bquo;are being imprinted with the microwave, not the stove&equo;.
The hearth as metaphor is dead.
But the Journal also comes up with some curious contradictions: 36 per cent blame the microwave for poorer flavour, 20 per cent think it makes food soggy. [/p] [p]
The Journal's final lament is to the grilled cheese sandwich or the croque monsieur.
Once a golden brown staple, crisp on the outside and creamy within, it has gone the way of all flesh.
But in this rather frightening vision of the present and future, so have all the things I learnt to care about in eating: flavour, texture, invention, subtlety, companionship &mdash; and leisure, which marks the end of the working <head>day</head> and the use of time, not its gobbling. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [head]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40412" docsrc="bnc_CH0_2412">
<answer instance="day.40412" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Mostyn's M-29 spat, and somebody rolled down the dunes.
The soldier gave Rodriguez the thumbs-up.
First kill.
That gave him dibs on the scav, not that there would be much worth looting in this sandhole. [/p] [p]
Susie Terhune's crew laid down some heavy fire.
Buildings started burning.
The incendiary charges Manolo's experts had set up earlier in the day went up on schedule.
By the time they got to town, most of the heavy stuff should be over. [/p] [p]
Despite his bulky Kevlar Hell-and-Back suit, Rodriguez moved fast.
He jogged every morning with lead weights slung on his chest, back and thighs to get him used to the extra poundage of the armour.
The IR visor of his helmet [pb] showed him the desert as if by the light of an overcast <head>day</head> . [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40414" docsrc="bnc_A6A_1229">
<answer instance="day.40414" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
This is income which increases as the artist gains greater success and begins to release such items as compilation videos comprising selected promotional videos, or full length videos of live concert performances. [/p] [/div3] [/div2] [div2] [head]
After the Deal: What Next? [/head] [p]
After capturing the all-important record contract, the artist is left to work with the A&amp;R person who made their introduction to the company.
&bquo;In those early days,&equo; says Gatfield, &bquo;the A&amp;R person is everything to a new act &mdash; they hold the purse strings and there is a very special relationship because it was the A&amp;R person who offered them the way into a record company, which is very, very special.&equo; [/p] [p]
However, the <head>days</head> of moulding artists (&equo; wear that, play this, look like this, get your hair cut like that') have gone.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40415" docsrc="bnc_A06_1841">
<answer instance="day.40415" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Her recent television credits include leads in the series [hi]Buccaneer, The Professionals, The Consultant, Into the Labyrinth, Lytton's Diary, Magnum, Seagull Island [/hi], and her film credits include [hi]The First Great Train Robbery, The Bitch [/hi], Morecambe and Wise's [hi]Night Train to Murder [/hi], Miss Moneypenny in [hi]Never Say Never Again, Universal City, After Darkness [/hi], and she has just completed [hi]Salome [/hi], playing Herodias. [/p] [sp] [spkr]
A.R. [/spkr] [p]
Would you say that things have changed a great deal from the days when you finished your drama school training at Central in 1966? [/p] [/sp] [sp] [spkr]
P.S. [/spkr] [p]
I think the profession has changed because the opportunities are different.
first of all I'm absolutely against having the controlled entry into Equity.
It is much worse these <head>days</head> than it was in 1966.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40417" docsrc="bnc_B0G_927">
<answer instance="day.40417" senseid="day-2"/>
<context>
Again in 1699, criticism was levied of, &bquo;&hellip; the Mayor and Constables for not punishing of wicked and lazy persons, both old and young, who absent themselves from the service of God and profane the Sabbath Day&equo;. [/p] [p]
Some did fall foul of the constables on a Saturday night.
In 1653 William Hill was in trouble for, &bquo;&hellip; suffering disorder in his house to the great disturbance of his neighbours&equo;.
Also that year trouble came to Mr Nicholas Foote for being &bquo;&hellip; a common ale-house haunter&equo;.
&bquo;Thomas White, a tippler, for keeping shuffle board play&equo; came before the Court during the stern <head>days</head> of the Commonwealth, while in 1666 were charged, &bquo;John Parson, James his son, Stephen Parker and Sidney Randall for not going to church on the Lord's day&equo;. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.40418" docsrc="bnc_A6R_510">
<answer instance="day.40418" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.40418" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Local Gary Austin landed a 3 lb 2 oz 8 drm flattie during a Flounder League match and then topped it with a 3 lb 10 oz specimen while pleasure fishing. [/p] [p]
Both flounder came from the Evening Hill shore mark to ragworm fished in just six feet of water on a size 2 hook to 15 lb line. [/p] [p]
The Flounder League also produced a 3 lb 6 oz 12 drm fish for Southborne's Nich Edwards and a 2 ob 14 oz flattie for Reg Clough from Bowerchalk. [/p] [p]
Ragworm was again the successful bait fished over the extensive lugworm beds at Evening Hill. [/p] [p]
The same approach also brought a 3 lb 7 oz 8 drm flounder for Andy Stevens from Bournemouth. [/p] [/div1] [div1] [p]
&bull; Bradford specimen hunter Eddie Harrison banked this 2 lb 2 oz roach during a session on the Rive Aire in the Keighley area on a <head>day</head> when everyone else was blanking. [/p] [p]
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30005" docsrc="wsj_1322.mrg_79">
<answer instance="day.30005" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30005" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
The issue was oversubscribed and ``doing very well,'' according to an
official with lead underwriter Morgan Stanley.  Activity quieted in the New
York City bond market, where heavy investor selling last week drove yields
on the issuer's full faith and credit backed bonds up as much as 0.50
percentage point.  Foreign Bonds Japanese government bonds ended lower
after the dollar rose modestly against the yen.  The turnaround in the
dollar fueled bearish sentiment about Japan's bond market.  The benchmark
No. 111 4.6 % bond due 1998 ended on brokers 'screens at a price of 95.39,
off 0.28.  The yield rose to 5.38 %.  West German bond prices ended lower
after a <head>day</head> of aimless trading.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30008" docsrc="wsj_1870.mrg_34">
<answer instance="day.30008" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
California state transportation officials interviewed by telephone say they
nevertheless do n't expect serious problems for commerce in and out of the
Bay area.  All major roadways except Interstate 880, known as the Nimitz
Freeway, and the Bay Bridge were open by 1 p.m. yesterday.  Officials
expect difficulty routing traffic through downtown San Francisco.  The
earthquake caused many streets to buckle and crack, making them impassible.
Other roads were obstructed by collapsed buildings and damaged water and
power lines, an emergency relief spokesman says.  San Francisco Mayor Art
Agnos estimated the damage to his city alone at $2 billion.  But many
predicted that the commercial disruption would be short-lived.  Of the
scores of companies contacted by this newspaper, few reported any damage
that they did n't expect to have remedied within a <head>day</head>
or two.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30016" docsrc="wsj_1128.mrg_38">
<answer instance="day.30016" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30016" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Some 500 insects and 150 diseases wiggle, chew and romp through growers '
nightmares, including maggots, mites, mildew, thrips, black rot and the
flat-headed borer.  Even if a grower beats them back, his $2,000 rented
bees might buzz off to the neighbors 'orchards instead of pollinating his,
Mr. Broderick says.  Though growers ca n't always keep the worm from the
apple, they can protect themselves against the price vagaries of any one
variety by diversifying -- into the recently imported Gala, a sweet New
Zealand native; the Esopus Spitzenburg, reportedly Thomas Jefferson's
favorite apple; disease-resistant kinds like the Liberty.  ``I 've ripped
out a lot of Delicious'' and grafted the trees with many different shoots,
says Steve Wood, a West Lebanon, N.H., grower, tramping through his
100-acre Poverty Lane Orchard on a crisp autumn <head>day</head>
recently.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30020" docsrc="wsj_1698.mrg_3">
<answer instance="day.30020" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30020" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
Mercury also said it extended its two-year advisory relationship with
Montgomery Securities of San Francisco.  Mercury's stock closed yesterday
at $4.875, unchanged in composite trading on the New York Stock Exchange.
Watching Congress sweat and grimace through its annual budget labors,
fighting the urge to spend more, we 're reminded of those late-night movies
in which the anguished serial killer turns himself in to police and says, ``
Stop me before I kill again.'' The Members know they 're doing wrong, but
they need help to restrain their darker compulsions.  Arkansas Democrat
David Pryor spilled his guts on the Senate floor the other
<head>day</head> after he 'd joined the Finance Committee's
early-morning pork-barrel revels: ``I must tell you ...
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30024" docsrc="wsj_1457.mrg_47">
<answer instance="day.30024" senseid="election_day-0"/>
<context>
It has n't helped that he's waffled on abortion and gay rights, sought the
support of both the Liberal and Conservative parties (he won the Liberal
endorsement) and that he turned to comedian Jackie Mason for help with
Jewish voters.  Mr. Mason left the campaign after telling reporters Mr.
Dinkins is ``a fancy'shvartzer 'with a moustache.'' Shvartzer is a
derogatory Yiddish word for a black person.  Mr. Dinkins concedes nothing
in his ability to stumble and bumble.  He can match Jackie Mason with his
own Robert ``Sonny'' Carson, an angry street organizer who was convicted of
kidnapping in 1974.  The Dinkins campaign paid Mr. Carson close to $10,000
to get out the vote on primary-election <head>day</head>.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30026" docsrc="wsj_0361.mrg_10">
<answer instance="day.30026" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
MiniScribe has said that its financial results for the past three fiscal
years would have to be restated because of the allegedly fraudulent
accounting and marketing practices that inflated revenues and net income.
MiniScribe also has n't filed any financial statements for 1989.  Mr.
Rifenburgh said such statements should be ready by the end of November.  He
said he expects the company to have $500 million in sales for this year.
He did n't say what the company expected to report for year-earlier sales,
which will be restated from the previously reported $603 million.  The
release of MiniScribe's new balance sheet came one <head>day</head>
after it introduced its new line of one-inch disk drives, on which it is
pinning much of its hope for survival.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30028" docsrc="wsj_1055.mrg_7">
<answer instance="day.30028" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30028" senseid="U"/>
<answer instance="day.30028" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
After being trampled in Tuesday's selling stampede, the Nasdaq
over-the-counter market dusted itself off and moved on in moderate trading.
But while the Composite gained 1.19, to 462.89, many issues did n't
participate in the advance.  ``It was a mixed bag,'' said Richard Bruno,
who heads over-the-counter trading at PaineWebber.  ``We played catch-up in
some areas, and sold off in some others.'' Volume totaled 132.1 million
shares, which is about average for the year.  Of the 4,348 issues that
changed hands, 1,074 advanced and 866 declined.  Big financial stocks
carried the <head>day</head>.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30030" docsrc="wsj_0766.mrg_69">
<answer instance="day.30030" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Recently, a contractor saved her from falling three stories as she
investigated what remained of an old Victorian house torched by an arsonist.
``I owe that contractor.  I really do,'' she says.  As Ms. Johnson stands
outside the Hammack house after winding up her chores there, the house
begins to creak and sway.  The ground shakes underneath her.  It is an
aftershock, one of about 2,000 since the earthquake, and it makes her uneasy.
The next day, as she prepares a $10,000 check for the Hammacks, which will
cover the cost of demolishing the house and clearing away the debris, she
jumps at the slightest noise.  On further reflection, she admits that
venturing inside the Hammacks 'house the previous <head>day</head>
was n't ``such a great idea.''
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30033" docsrc="wsj_1863.mrg_27">
<answer instance="day.30033" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Futures trading resumed a half-hour later, but the session ended shortly
thereafter, leaving the stock market set up for more sell programs, traders
said.  By Monday morning, they said, stock-index arbitrage sell programs
helped re-establish the link between stocks and futures.  But stunning
volatility was produced in the process.  The Dow Jones Industrial Average
plunged a breathtaking 63.52 points in the first 40 minutes of trading
Monday as stock-index arbitrage sell programs kicked in.  At about 10:10
a.m. EDT, the market abruptly turned upward on stock-index arbitrage buy
programs.  By <head>day</head>'s end, the Dow industrials had
rebounded 88.12 points, or nearly half of Friday's drop.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30034" docsrc="wsj_2231.mrg_20">
<answer instance="day.30034" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
But if rational science and economics have nothing to do with the new
environment initiative, what is going on?  The first place to look under
these circumstances is at the ways in which the sponsors themselves will
benefit.  The key here is the ambition of state Attorney General John Van
de Kamp.  He's running for governor.  Mr. Van de Kamp is the one who
collected the plans from the various radical environmental groups and
cobbled them into a single unwieldy initiative to be placed on the ballot
for election on Nov. 6, 1990.  That's also the <head>day</head> of
the gubernatorial election.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30036" docsrc="wsj_0585.mrg_24">
<answer instance="day.30036" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30036" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Of course, there were sell programs in past years, too, but they seem to
hurt market makers more painfully these days.  That's largely because of
defensive measures they adopted after the 1987 crash, when individual
investors fled the market and trading activity dwindled.  Market makers, to
cut costs, slashed inventories of stocks they keep on hand to sell
investors when other holders are n't selling.  And to protect their reduced
capital investment from eroding further, market makers became quicker to
lower price quotes when sell programs are in progress.  On days when prices
are tumbling, they must be willing to buy shares from sellers when no one
else will.  In such an environment, market makers can suffer huge losses
both on trades made that <head>day</head> at steadily dropping prices
and in the value of their inventories of shares.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30037" docsrc="wsj_0725.mrg_74">
<answer instance="day.30037" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
One of its wells, in southwestern Oklahoma, is a ``rank wildcat,'' a risky
well where oil previously has n't been found.  ``At this price, $18 plus or
minus, and with costs being significantly less than they were several years
ago, the economics are pretty good,'' says George Kadane, head of the
company.  ``If you know you 've got stability in price, you can do things
you would n't do with the volatility of the past few years.'' The activity
is enough to move some oil-service prices back up a little.  Some drill-bit
prices have risen 5 % in the past month.  In the Gulf of Mexico, a boat to
deliver supplies to offshore rigs now costs around $3,000 a
<head>day</head>, up nearly 60 % since June.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30039" docsrc="wsj_1699.mrg_57">
<answer instance="day.30039" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
For interstate highways, the federal share normally would drop to 90 % of
the cost of repairs, and the state would have to pick up the remainder of
the cost.  But lawmakers want to extend the period for 100 % federal
funding for several months.  Those changes also would apply to two areas
hit hard by Hurricane Hugo -- South Carolina and the U.S. Virgin Islands,
according to an aide to Rep. Fazio.  Meanwhile, the FEMA announced a
toll-free telephone number (800-462-9029) to expedite service to victims of
the earthquake.  Lines will be available 24 hours a <head>day</head>
to take applications for such disaster relief as temporary housing and
emergency home repairs by phone.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30040" docsrc="wsj_1000.mrg_10">
<answer instance="day.30040" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Several big securities firms backed off from program trading a few months
after the 1987 crash.  But most of them, led by Morgan Stanley &amp; Co., moved
back in earlier this year.  The most volatile form of program trading is
index arbitrage -- the rapid-fire, computer-guided buying and selling of
stocks offset with opposite trades in stock-index futures and options.  The
object is to capture profits from fleeting price discrepancies between the
futures and options and the stocks themselves.  Index arbitrage recently
has accounted for about half of all program trading on the New York Stock
Exchange.  Last month, program trading accounted for 20.9 million shares a
<head>day</head>, or a record 13.8 % of the Big Board's average daily
volume.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30043" docsrc="wsj_2300.mrg_86">
<answer instance="day.30043" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
But the exchange will ``look at the performance of all specialists in all
stocks.  Obviously we 'll take a close look at any situation in which we
think the dealer-community obligations were n't met,'' he said.  (See
related story: ``Fed Ready to Inject Big Funds'' -- WSJ Oct. 16, 1989) But
specialists complain privately that just as in the 1987 crash, the ``
upstairs'' firms -- big investment banks that support the market by trading
big blocks of stock -- stayed on the sidelines during Friday's blood-letting.
Mr. Phelan said, ``It will take another <head>day</head> or two'' to
analyze who was buying and selling Friday.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30044" docsrc="ibm_44.cmb_22">
<answer instance="day.30044" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
If a CL variable is used to specify the value for a character type system
value, the CL variable must be character type and may be of any length.
4306.  Date and time system values must always be enclosed in apostrophes.
4307.  A change made to this value takes effect immediately.  4308.  When
you specify the date in CL commands, you can specify only 2 digits for the
year in the date format.  4309.  The system assigns the first 2 digits for
the year (xx) based on the following rules: 4310.  The following table
shows the various values provided by the CL character variable.  4311.  (Y
= year; M = month; D = <head>day</head>.)
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30046" docsrc="wsj_0671.mrg_65">
<answer instance="day.30046" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
``It shows that there are buyers of high-quality assets at high prices in
today's market,'' said Robert Long, managing director and head of the
high-yield research department at First Boston Corp.  Many of the RJR
securities, which had been trading near their 52-week lows earlier in the
session, bounced back after the company's announcement that it agreed to
sell its Baby Ruth, Butterfinger and Pearson candy businesses to Nestle
Foods, a unit of the Swiss-based food concern.  The sale, expected to close
before the end of the year, also includes a manufacturing plant in Franklin
Park, Ill.  RJR's subordinated discount debentures of 2001, which traded as
low as 45 Friday, finished the <head>day</head> at 46 7\/8.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30047" docsrc="wsj_2300.mrg_15">
<answer instance="day.30047" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30047" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Once again -LCB- the specialists -RCB- were not able to handle the
imbalances on the floor of the New York Stock Exchange,'' said Christopher
Pedersen, senior vice president at Twenty-First Securities Corp.  Countered
James Maguire, chairman of specialists Henderson Brothers Inc.: ``It is
easy to say the specialist is n't doing his job.  When the dollar is in a
free-fall, even central banks ca n't stop it.  Speculators are calling for
a degree of liquidity that is not there in the market.'' Many money
managers and some traders had already left their offices early Friday
afternoon on a warm autumn day -- because the stock market was so quiet.
Then in a lightning plunge, the Dow Jones industrials in barely an hour
surrendered about a third of their gains this year, chalking up a
190.58-point, or 6.9 %, loss on the <head>day</head> in gargantuan
trading volume.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30050" docsrc="wsj_2446.mrg_11">
<answer instance="day.30050" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
According to notes taken by one of the participants at the meeting, the
regulators said Lincoln was gambling dangerously with depositors 'federally
insured money and was ``a ticking time bomb.'' Mr. Keating had complained
that the regulators were being too zealous.  The notes show that Sen.
DeConcini called the Federal Home Loan Bank Board's regulations ``grossly
unfair,'' and that Sen. Glenn insisted that Mr. Keating's thrift was ``
viable and profitable.'' For the next two years, the Bank Board, which at
the time was the agency responsible for regulating thrifts, failed to act
-- even after federal auditors warned in May 1987 that Mr. Keating had
caused Lincoln to become insolvent.  Lincoln's parent company, American
Continental Corp., entered bankruptcy-law proceedings this April 13, and
regulators seized the thrift the next <head>day</head>.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30051" docsrc="wsj_1213.mrg_74">
<answer instance="day.30051" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The bonds were won by a Goldman, Sachs &amp; Co. group with a true interest
cost of 7.17 %.  They were priced to yield from 6.00 % in 1990 to 7.20 % in
2009.  The Massachusetts deal had an unsold balance of $84.3 million in
late trading, the underwriter said.  Mortgage -, Asset-Backed Securities
Mortgage securities gained 3\/32 to 9\/32 point after a hectic session,
with Government National Mortgage Association 8 % securities as the
standout issue.  The Ginnie Mae issue rose amid talk of large purchases of
the securities by institutional investors.  The derivative markets remained
active as one new issue was priced and talk circulated about more offerings
in the next <head>day</head> or two.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30053" docsrc="wsj_0108.mrg_13">
<answer instance="day.30053" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
You can do all this even if you 're not a reporter or a researcher or a
scholar or a member of Congress.  And my newspaper can print the text of
those broadcasts.  Until the other day, you as an ordinary citizen of this
democracy had no right to see what your government was telling your cousins
around the world.  That was the law.  And I apparently had no right to
print hither what the Voice was booming to yon.  It was censorship.  It was
outrageous.  And it was stupid.  The theory was that the Voice is a
propaganda agency and this government should n't propagandize its own people.
That sounds neat, but this government -- any government -- propagandizes
its own people every <head>day</head>.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30055" docsrc="wsj_0142.mrg_9">
<answer instance="day.30055" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30055" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
The size of IBM's issue was increased from an originally planned $500
million as money managers and investors scrambled to buy the bonds.  In the
investment-grade corporate market, ``it's rare that you get an opportunity
to buy a name that has such broad appeal and has such attractive call
features,'' said James Ednie, a Drexel industrial bond trader.  Money
managers ranked IBM's offering as the most significant investment-grade
sale of the year because large issues of long-term debt by companies with
triple-A credit are infrequent.  Syndicate officials at lead underwriter
Salomon Brothers Inc. said the debentures were snapped by up pension funds,
banks, insurance companies and other institutional investors.  In the
Treasury market, investors paid scant attention to the
<head>day</head>'s economic reports, which for the most part provided
a mixed view of the economy.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30057" docsrc="wsj_2276.mrg_72">
<answer instance="day.30057" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30057" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
German and Dutch investors reportedly loaded up on Kellogg Co.  Then,
traders say, corporations with share buy-back programs kicked into high gear,
triggering gains in, among other issues, Alcan Aluminium and McDonald's.
Walt Disney Co., which had one of the biggest sell-order imbalances on
Friday and was one of seven stocks that halted trading and never reopened
that day, opened yesterday late at 114.5, down 8.5.  But then it suddenly
burst upward 7.5 as Goldman, Sachs &amp; Co. stepped in and bought almost every
share offer, traders said.  By 10:25, the Dow had turned up for the
<head>day</head>, prompting cheers on trading desks and exchange
floors.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30058" docsrc="wsj_1271.mrg_3">
<answer instance="day.30058" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
A new Maryland law frees store owners of liability if a customer trips or
otherwise gets hurt on the way to the restroom ....  Only 4 % of Missouri
small businesses surveyed say they 've tested an employee or applicant for
drug or alcohol use ....  By 52%-36 %, Tennessee NFIB members favor laws to
limit foreign ownership of land and facilities in the state.  About 400,000
commuters trying to find their way through the Bay area's quake-torn
transportation system wedged cheek-to-jowl into subways, sat in traffic
jams on major freeways or waited forlornly for buses yesterday.  In other
words, it was a better-than-average Manhattan commute.  City officials
feared widespread gridlock on the first <head>day</head> that normal
business operations were resumed following last Tuesday's earthquake.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30061" docsrc="wsj_1852.mrg_12">
<answer instance="day.30061" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30061" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
In addition, specialists on the exchanges agreed to provide backup capital
for market-making in Pacific exchange options traded on the exchanges.
Trading was light on the Pacific Stock Exchange yesterday, with workers at
the exchange's main floor in San Francisco struggling to execute orders by
flashlight as a result of a continuing power outage.  The most pressing
problem was the suspension of options trading.  The Pacific exchange has
options for 129 underlying stock issues, including highly active Hilton
Hotels Corp., which is listed on the Big Board.  Investors were concerned
that they might be unable to exercise options that expire tomorrow.  But
professionals said throughout the <head>day</head> that the shutdown
would n't be a cause for alarm even if it were to persist for several days.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30062" docsrc="wsj_0970.mrg_1">
<answer instance="day.30062" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Labor Secretary Elizabeth Dole named a mediator to help resolve the lengthy
labor dispute between the United Mine Workers and Pittston Co.  W.J. Usery
Jr., labor secretary during the Ford administration, was named to mediate
talks to settle the six-month strike by the UMW.  Previous talks between
Pittston, of Greenwich, Conn., and the union have been sporadic and
unsuccessful.  The union called the strike in April after Pittston refused
to sign the UMW's national labor pact.  Pittston seeks changes in health
and pension benefits, among other things.  No schedule for formal talks was
set, but meetings are expected to begin soon.  One <head>day</head>
after Delmed Inc. made top management changes and disclosed the end of an
important business tie, its stock did n't trade and the company forecast a
``significant'' drop next year in sales of its core product.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30064" docsrc="wsj_1394.mrg_70">
<answer instance="day.30064" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Until then, they expect the cost of integrating the two carriers to
continue crimping profits.  For now, the union issue is the most nettlesome
of Federal's Tiger problems, management believes.  Although encouraging
dialogue between managers and workers, Mr. Smith does n't countenance what
he considers insubordination.  When a large group of pilots once signed
petitions opposing work-rule and compensation changes, he called a meeting
in a company hangar and dressed them down for challenging his authority.
He then made most of the changes, pilots say.  That sort of approach,
however, has n't worked since the addition of Tiger.  Its 6,500 workers,
who had battled Tiger's management for years over givebacks, were union
members until the <head>day</head> of the merger, when most of their
unions were automatically decertified.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30065" docsrc="wsj_1142.mrg_5">
<answer instance="day.30065" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
The Nasdaq over-the-counter market did n't fully recover from a selling
stampede, and closed down 1.2 %.  The effects on the market of the mostly
computer-driven sell-off among exchange-listed stocks irked many market
makers, who watched the Nasdaq Composite Index tumble in sympathy with the
Dow Jones Industrial Average, and then saw it get left behind in the
subsequent rally.  After plummeting 1.8 % at one point during the day, the
composite rebounded a little, but finished down 5.52, at 461.70.  In
contrast, the industrial average recovered almost completely from its skid
and closed down 0.1 %.  The New York Stock Exchange Composite was 0.4 %
lower for the <head>day</head>.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30067" docsrc="wsj_1767.mrg_4">
<answer instance="day.30067" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Salespeople also could get a precise reading on when products could be
delivered -- in much the same way that Federal Express has marketed its
ability to tell exactly where a package is in the delivery system.  Ford
Motor Co.'s Merkur, the company's first new car franchise in the U.S. since
the Edsel was unveiled in 1957, now will share Edsel's fate.  Ford said
yesterday it will halt imports of the Merkur Scorpio, a $28,000 luxury
sedan built by Ford of Europe in West Germany.  The cars are sold under a
separate franchise with its own sign in front of Lincoln-Mercury dealers --
as opposed to new models such as Taurus or Escort, which are sold under
existing Ford divisions.  The move to halt imports -- announced 29 years
and 11 months to the <head>day</head> after Henry Ford II declared
that the Edsel division and its gawky car would be scrapped -- kills the
four-year-old Merkur brand in the U.S. market.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30068" docsrc="wsj_1002.mrg_1">
<answer instance="day.30068" senseid="work_day-0"/>
<context>
Kingdom of Morocco -- $208 million (redemption amount) of zero-coupon
government trust certificates, with maturities stretching from May 15, 1990,
to Nov. 15, 1999, priced at yields ranging from 8.23 % to 8.43 %.  All the
issues were priced at a spread of 37 basis points above the Treasury strips
with similar maturities.  Proceeds from the offering are about $160.4
million.  Rated triple-A by Moody's and S&amp;P, the issue will be sold through
underwriters led by BT Securities, a subsidiary of Bankers Trust New York
Corp.  At a time when Jon Levy should be planning the biggest spring season
in his dress company's 17 years, his work <head>day</head> is studded
with intense moments of concern about one of his biggest customers, Campeau
Corp.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30070" docsrc="wsj_2428.mrg_70">
<answer instance="day.30070" senseid="day-3"/>
<context>
What we 're seeing now is the wrenching readjustment of asset values to a
future when speculative-grade debt will be hard to obtain rather than easy.''
Friday's Market Activity Prices of Treasury bonds surged in the biggest
rally of the year as investors fled a plummeting stock market.  The
benchmark 30-year Treasury bond was quoted 6 p.m. EDT at 103 12\/32,
compared with 100 27\/32 Thursday, up 2 1\/2 points.  The yield on the
benchmark fell to 7.82 %, the lowest since March 31, 1987, according to
Technical Data Global Markets Group.  The ``flight to quality'' began late
in the <head>day</head> and followed a precipitous fall in the stock
market.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30071" docsrc="wsj_2210.mrg_35">
<answer instance="day.30071" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
A 16.3 % drop for Mannesmann AG and Dresdner Bank AG's 9.6 % decline were
especially problematic for their respective boards, whose plans for major
rights issues in November could now be in jeopardy.  Dresdner Bank last
month said it hoped to raise 1.2 billion marks ($642.2 million) by issuing
four million shares at 300 marks each.  Yet yesterday's market cropped
Dresdner's share price by 33 marks to 309 marks a share, leaving little
incentive for investors to subscribe to the standing price unless the
market recovers quickly.  LONDON: Headed toward a record drop at midday,
the London stock market recouped two-thirds of its losses in the wake of
New York's early rally.  The Financial Times-Stock Exchange 100 Share Index
closed off 70.5 points, at 2163.4, its high for the <head>day</head>,
after having plunged 204.2 points at 12:49 p.m.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30073" docsrc="wsj_1271.mrg_32">
<answer instance="day.30073" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Bechtel Group Inc., the giant closely held engineering concern, says it has
instituted a 6 a.m. to 8 p.m. flextime arrangement, whereby employees may
select any eight-hour period during those hours to go to work.  Of Bechtel
's 17,500 employees, about 4,000 work in San Francisco -- one-third of them
commuting from stricken East Bay.  Pacific Gas &amp; Electric Co. is offering
its 6,000 San Francisco employees a two-tier flextime schedule -- either 6
a.m. to 2 p.m. or 10 a.m. to 6 p.m.  The flextime may cut by almost a third
the number of PG&amp;E employees working conventional 9-5 hours, a spokesman
says.  Some of the utility's employees may opt for a four-day workweek, 10
hours a <head>day</head>, to cut the commute by 20 %.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30074" docsrc="wsj_1302.mrg_64">
<answer instance="day.30074" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
By that, he means low-margin but low-risk products such as certain types of
primary property insurance.  The exchange, he says, must find new products
and new markets.  That wo n't be an easy task.  Tradition is dictator at
Lloyd's.  Three years ago, the exchange took up residence in a space-age
tower of steel and glass -- evocative of the kind of modern architecture
that Britain's Prince Charles has denounced.  (Some exchange wags call the
building ``the oil rig.'') But along with such treasured artifacts as Lord
Nelson's spyglass, Lloyd's also brought its outmoded ways of doing business.
The Lloyd's market actively underwrites insurance just 4 1\/2 hours a
<head>day</head>, brokers say.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30076" docsrc="wsj_1758.mrg_2">
<answer instance="day.30076" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
MCA said net also included certain reserves related to the restructuring of
its LJN Toys 'international operations.  These items were partly offset,
MCA said, by an unspecified gain on the sale of its Miller International
unit, a maker and distributor of budget-priced audio cassettes.  In New
York Stock Exchange composite trading, MCA rose $1.50 to $64.  In the nine
months, net rose 35 % to $120.1 million, or $1.64 a share, from $89.2
million, or $1.22 a share, a year earlier.  Revenue increased 22 % to $2.5
billion from $2.1 billion.  Past Due Impasse I never pay my bills Till the
very last <head>day</head>; I lose far less interest By proceeding
that way.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30077" docsrc="wsj_2300.mrg_17">
<answer instance="day.30077" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Speculators are calling for a degree of liquidity that is not there in the
market.'' Many money managers and some traders had already left their
offices early Friday afternoon on a warm autumn day -- because the stock
market was so quiet.  Then in a lightning plunge, the Dow Jones industrials
in barely an hour surrendered about a third of their gains this year,
chalking up a 190.58-point, or 6.9 %, loss on the day in gargantuan trading
volume.  Final-hour trading accelerated to 108.1 million shares, a record
for the Big Board.  At the end of the <head>day</head>, 251.2 million
shares were traded.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30079" docsrc="wsj_0742.mrg_41">
<answer instance="day.30079" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Despite the current outcry over stock market volatility, few people expect
stock futures to disappear.  For one thing, the Chicago futures exchanges
have political and financial clout -- including many friends in Congress.
And traders say that futures have become an accepted part of the financial
landscape.  ``All life is about change -- either you adapt or die,'' says
one Chicago futures trader.  ``If futures are n't permitted here, we 'll
take it to Australia or Tokyo.'' Average daily volume in S&amp;P 500 futures
last year was 44,877 contracts.  Based on yesterday's closing price of the
S&amp;P, the average value of one <head>day</head>'s trading amounts to $
7.6 billion.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30080" docsrc="wsj_2428.mrg_76">
<answer instance="day.30080" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30080" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Treasurys opened lower, reacting negatively to news that the producer price
index -- a measure of inflation on the wholesale level -- accelerated in
September.  Bond prices barely budged until midday.  Many bond market
participants will be closely eying the action of the Federal Reserve, which
might repeat its October 1987 injection of huge amounts of liquidity to
buoy the financial markets and keep the economy from slowing into a
recession.  Prices of municipals, investment-grade corporates and
mortgage-backed bonds also rose, but lagged behind their Treasury
counterparts.  Mortgage securities rose in hectic trading, with most of the
activity concentrated in Government National Mortgage Association 9 %
coupon securities, the most liquid mortgage issue.  The Ginnie Mae November
9 % issue ended at 98 25\/32, up 7\/8 point on the <head>day</head>,
to yield about 9.28 % to a 12-year average life assumption.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30082" docsrc="wsj_0400.mrg_88">
<answer instance="day.30082" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
The benchmark 11 3\/4 % bond due 2003\/2007 rose 10\/32 to 111 14\/32 to
yield 10.14 %, while the Treasury's 12 % notes due 1995 rose 7\/32 to 103
5\/8 to yield 11.04 %.  West German government bonds fell as much as 0.60
point in light, nervous trading.  The 7 % Treasury bond due October 1999
ended off 0.60 point to 99.35 to yield 7.09 %, while the 6 3\/4 % notes due
1994 fell 0.35 point to 97.25 to yield 7.45 %.  Japanese government bonds
continued to erode as the dollar remained resilient against the yen.  Japan
's No. 111 4.6 % bond due 1998 ended the <head>day</head> on brokers
screens at 95.11 to yield 5.43 %.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30083" docsrc="wsj_1562.mrg_51">
<answer instance="day.30083" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Specific-Time Order: This type of order couples many of the orders
described above with instructions that the order must be carried out at or
by a certain time.  ``On the close'' can be added to many types of orders.
For example, ``market-on-close orders'' must be filled during the last few
minutes of trading for the day at a price that is within the official
closing range of prices as determined by the exchange.  ``Stop-close-only
orders'' are stop orders that only become active during the closing minutes
of trading.  ``Day orders'' expire at the end of the day on which they are
entered, ``good-till-canceled orders'' have no expiration date.  Most
brokers assume that all orders are <head>day</head> orders unless
specified otherwise.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30085" docsrc="wsj_1457.mrg_2">
<answer instance="day.30085" senseid="election_day-0"/>
<context>
Burlington's operating profit grew to $9.2 million from $3.8 million a year
earlier, Pittston said.  While ``the tone'' of domestic and international
air-freight markets remains sound, seasonal factors are likely to hinder
Burlington Air from matching third-quarter results in the fourth quarter,
Pittston said.  Brink's operating profit was about flat with the
year-earlier period, reflecting continued pricing and cost pressures.  In
New York Stock Exchange composite trading Friday, Pittston closed at $18.50
a share, down 12.5 cents.  Does n't anybody here want to win this mayor's
race?  As they stumble and bumble toward election <head>day</head>
two weeks from tomorrow, both Democrat David Dinkins and Republican Rudolph
Giuliani are in trouble.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30086" docsrc="wsj_2308.mrg_3">
<answer instance="day.30086" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Ripples from the strike by 55,000 Machinists union members against Boeing
Co. reached air carriers Friday as America West Airlines announced it will
postpone its new service out of Houston because of delays in receiving
aircraft from the Seattle jet maker.  Peter Otradovec, vice president for
planning at the Phoenix, Ariz., carrier, said in an interview that the work
stoppage at Boeing, now entering its 13th day, ``has caused some turmoil in
our scheduling'' and that more than 500 passengers who were booked to fly
out of Houston on America West would now be put on other airlines.  Mr.
Otradovec said Boeing told America West that the 757 it was supposed to get
this Thursday would n't be delivered until Nov. 7 -- the
<head>day</head> after the airline had been planning to initiate
service at Houston with four daily flights, including three nonstops to
Phoenix and one nonstop to Las Vegas.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30088" docsrc="wsj_1442.mrg_35">
<answer instance="day.30088" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Now, annual population growth is running at about 2 % a year, some desert
tracts bought three years ago for $90,000 an acre are being sold at $25,000
an acre and Phoenix has a seven-year supply of unoccupied office space.  ``
It's horrible to say, but it's unfortunate that earthquake was n't in
Phoenix -- it might have knocked out some of our empty buildings,'' said
C.W. Jackson, a prominent Arizona businessman with interests in real estate,
banking and many other businesses.  Many Arizona real-estate experts think
the worst may be yet to come.  Ralph Shattuck, publisher of Foreclosure
Update newsletter, said foreclosures have climbed to about 1,482 a month
just in Maricopa County, where Phoenix is located.  That's up from about
687 a month in 1985, and it's accelerating: So far this month, foreclosures
are averaging about 85 a <head>day</head>.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30089" docsrc="wsj_2265.mrg_20">
<answer instance="day.30089" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Platinum behaved more like an industrial metal, easing early on concern
over a possible weaker economy, but recovering later, as the stock market
strengthened.  Gold was nowhere the spectacular performer it was two years
ago on Black Monday.  For one thing, last Friday, precious metals markets
closed before the stock market went into its late-in-the-day nose dive, so
it could n't react to it.  Back on Friday, Oct. 16, l987, the stock market
declined during the day, and gold prices surged as the stock market fell.
The October 1987 contract that <head>day</head> rose as much as $8.70
to as high as $471.60, and the more deferred positions, due to mature as
late as March 1989, rose as much as $9.60.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30092" docsrc="wsj_0983.mrg_47">
<answer instance="day.30092" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Other funds have recently sold weak junk bonds to raise cash.  At the
50%-leveraged Zenith Income Fund, portfolio manager John Bianchi recently
dumped Mesa Petroleum, Wickes and Horsehead Industries, among others, to
raise his cash position to a record 15 %.  ``That's a problem because cash
is n't earning us very much money,'' Mr. Bianchi says.  He concedes: ``This
is the most difficult market that I 've been involved in.'' Because of the
recent junk-market turmoil, the fund is considering investing in other
issues instead, including mortgage-backed bonds.  ``We 're looking at the
leverage factor every <head>day</head>,'' says Robert Moore,
president of Bernstein-Macaulay Inc., a Shearson Lehman Hutton Inc. unit
and the fund's adviser.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30093" docsrc="wsj_2252.mrg_6">
<answer instance="day.30093" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Agip S.p.  A. and Societe National Elf Aquitaine, the state oil companies
of Italy and France, respectively, submitted an offer to buy Gatoil Suisse
S.A.  The price was n't disclosed.  A spokesman for Gatoil said that the
Swiss oil concern was examining the offer, submitted last Friday, along
with two other offers, also submitted last week.  Those two offers were
private and the spokesman refused to identify the bidding companies.  The
spokesman further said that at least two more offers are expected from
other companies within two weeks.  Gatoil Suisse owns an oil refinery in
Switzerland with a capacity of 70,000 barrels a <head>day</head>,
along with a network of gasoline retailing outlets.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30098" docsrc="wsj_1685.mrg_8">
<answer instance="day.30098" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
An incinerator is also probably better than having nobody next door -- on
our farm there are four unoccupied houses.  On my four-mile drive to farm
headquarters each morning, I drive by another four empty houses.  A
community of abandoned farmsteads, failing businesses, and crumbling roads
and bridges is hardly a desirable one ....  The loss of 40 jobs by a
depressed county in rural Missouri is hardly of national importance except
for this: If the most environmentally safe way of dealing with a national
problem can not be built in Atchinson County, what hope have we for dealing
with the wastes our economy produces?  After all, farmers here work with ``
hazardous'' chemicals every <head>day</head>, many of them the same
chemicals that would have been destroyed in the incinerator.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30099" docsrc="wsj_0121.mrg_37">
<answer instance="day.30099" senseid="day-0"/>
<answer instance="day.30099" senseid="day-1"/>
<context>
Arbitraging on differences between spot and futures prices is an important
part of many financial markets, he says.  He adds that his shares in a
company savings plan are invested in a mutual fund, and volatility, on a
given day, may hurt the fund.  But ``I 'm a long-term investor,'' he says.
``If you were a short-term investor, you might be more leery about program
trading.'' Jim Enzor of Atlanta defends program trading because he believes
that it can bring the market back up after a plunge.  ``If we have a real
bad <head>day</head>, the program would say, ` Buy, ''' he explains.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30101" docsrc="wsj_0730.mrg_32">
<answer instance="day.30101" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
Before the law went into effect last month, car rental companies were
charging as much as $12 a day for the waiver in Texas.  Now, they 're
charging as little $3 a day.  ``If they 're telling the truth now, then
they 've been charging 300 % more than what is reasonable,'' says Steve
Gardner, an assistant state attorney general in Texas.  A spokesman for
Hertz Corp. acknowledges, ``The waiver is n't a source of protection for
consumers, but a source of revenue.'' But Hertz points out that at least it
's now charging only $3.95 a <head>day</head> in Texas, while some
competitors are charging $6.99.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30102" docsrc="wsj_0700.mrg_40">
<answer instance="day.30102" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
The Hibor contract ``solves quite a bit of the problem of interest-rate
risk in the interbank market,'' says Eric Cheng, a director of James Capel (
Far East) Ltd., the Hong Kong arm of the British brokerage firm.  Despite
the initial support expected, trading in the contract is likely to start
slowly.  The wounds from the 1987 crash have n't yet healed, and not all
claims against the exchange clearinghouse -- by those who bet the Hang Seng
index would fall -- have been settled.  Companies and financial
institutions familiar with Hong Kong remain wary of trading in its futures
market.  And Mr. Gilmore cautions that there may be limits on how much the
contract can grow because the Hong Kong dollar is n't a widely traded
currency.  He says the contract will be considered a success if it starts
trading 500 to 1,000 lots a <head>day</head>.
</context>
</instance>

<instance id="day.30105" docsrc="wsj_0655.mrg_15">
<answer instance="day.30105" senseid="day-0"/>
<context>
And important U.S. lawmakers must decide at the end of November if the
Contras are to receive the rest of the $49 million in so-called
humanitarian assistance under a bipartisan agreement reached with the Bush
administration in March.  The humanitarian assistance, which pays for
supplies such as food and clothing for the rebels amassed along the
Nicaraguan border with Honduras, replaced the military aid cut off by
Congress in February 1988.  While few lawmakers anticipated that the
humanitarian aid would be cut off next month, Mr. Ortega's threat
practically guarantees that the humanitarian aid will be continued.  Senate
Minority Leader Robert Dole (R., Kan.) said yesterday on ``Meet the Press'':
``I would hope after his -LCB- Mr. Ortega's -RCB- act yesterday or the
<head>day</head> before, we 'd have unanimous support for quick
action on remaining humanitarian aid.''
</context>
</instance>

</lexelt>

  </corpus>